[faint cheering]
[faint chanting]
[crowd cheering]
- [whistle blows]
- [crowd noises abruptly end]
["Dancing with Myself"
by Billy Idol playing]
♪On the floors of Tokyo ♪
♪Or down in London town to go, go ♪
♪Well, I wait so long
for my love vibration ♪
♪And I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪Oh, oh, dancing with myself ♪
♪When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪Well, I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪If I looked all over the world ♪
♪And there's every type of girl ♪
♪But your empty eyes seem to pass me by ♪
♪Leave me dancing with myself ♪
♪So let's sink another drink ♪
♪'Cause it'll give me time to think ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪And I'd be dancing with myself, oh, oh ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪If I looked all over the world ♪
♪And there's every type of girl ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪And I'd be dancing with myself, oh, oh ♪
♪Dancing with myself, oh, oh ♪
♪Dancing with myself ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪And if I had the chance
You looking for someone?
Fuck. N-No, I...
S-Sorry.
[upbeat rock music playing]
[sighs]
[professor] In my class,
average actually means average.
That is why 70% of you got a C+ or lower.
It's a fucking jock class.
Like, why am I being forced to try?
- I probably failed.
- Oh, I definitely did.
[laughs]
You think we can still drop it, bro?
I can't. I need this for my major.
Relax. I'm sure your coach
will convince Tolbert
to get creative with their grading system.
Jocks. So pretty.
So entitled.
Aren't you above stereotypes?
Babe, I'm trying to be below
one of those stereotypes.
Maybe behind.
And none of you star athletes
should expect any special treatment.
You knew what
your practice schedule looked like
before you signed up for this class,
Mr. Maxwell.
Me? No, I was just curious
about extra credit opportunities
to, you know, learn more.
You can learn from your next assignment.
Oral presentations.
- [students groaning]
- Okay, yeah. Definitely dropping.
Thanks.
[Dexter] Perfect. Another D.
So, how'd you do?
Not good.
Girl, really?
Yeah, I wrote it in like an hour, so...
Fucking hell, you aced it?
I knew it. Show me.
- Do you mind?
- What?
Only you get to look at things
you shouldn't?
[professor]
Okay, now that we got that covered,
anybody want to hazard a guess
as to what we will be discussing today?
[inaudible]
[Dexter]
There goes your manic pixie dream boy.
[Hannah] Justin Kohl is not my anything.
- It's not too late.
- [chuckles]
It's not too late.
[Hannah] You are intolerable.
Did she do it?
Did she talk to Justin Kohl?
No, no, she's too busy
pining wistfully from afar.
He has literally no idea who I am, okay?
Am I supposed to just fling myself at him?
- [both] Yes.
- [Garrett] Mona!
I've said maybe two words to the guy,
and they weren't even good words.
Hannah, you love his music
and you've been crushing on him for weeks.
Sound check's at five. You're on at nine.
Okay, eight words ever.
- [chuckles]
- Hey, Mona.
Who-- Who's Mona?
I think you.
I-I'm not Mona.
It is an M, though, right?
Not even close.
What do you want, Garrett Graham?
Petals to walk on?
Maybe another fancy gym
that costs thousands of dollars,
even though the theater department
is literally falling apart.
So, uh, I failed that paper.
It sounds like a lot of people did.
And I was thinking it'd be great
if I didn't fail again.
So...
Was there a question in there?
A question, I don't think
I heard a question, no.
You guys are late for scene study.
Go, I'll see you at dinner.
- [laughs]
- Bye, Mona.
I need your help.
Wow.
What?
See, usually with questions,
voices kind of go up at the end.
And your voice didn't do that, so...
Okay, could you,
pretty please with sugar on top,
help me study
so that I don't fail spectacularly?
Better. But no.
[chuckles]
Come on. Do me a solid.
I mean, you kind of owe me
for that sneak peek.
- That was an honest mistake.
- Was it?
I mean, tons of girls would have paid
good money for the view you got, so...
I'm scarred for life.
If anything, you owe me.
[scoffs]
Well, I have to ace the oral presentation,
or I can't play.
Believe it or not, I have priorities
that have nothing to do with hockey.
Find another tutor, dude.
["Rich" by Bea and Her Business playing]
♪Turns out I'm still 20♪
♪When I'm acting middle-aged ♪
♪Same old conversation ♪
♪All the small talk that I hate ♪
♪And I never thought I'd say it ♪
♪But I'm sick of everyone ♪
♪I need to sweat it out ♪
♪I need to have some fun ♪
♪Get the girls in the car
take the car to the club ♪
♪Girls gonna dance
and the boys gonna love ♪
♪This, licking their lips ♪
♪Wishing they had
their big-boy hands all on my hips ♪
♪Everybody's on some drugs,
everybody wants some love ♪
♪I don't want shit
I don't need to chase that hit ♪
♪Long as I got my boys and girls
I'm rich...♪
Shit.
[orchestra playing classical music]
[mouthing]
Hey. You wanted to talk to me?
If this is about being late,
I have a new idea for a shortcut.
Oh.
Oh, you have your bad news face.
It's your scholarship.
It's not happening this year.
- What?
- Budget cuts.
Don't even get me started.
No, we're three weeks into the semester.
How-- How can--
No. No, they can't. No.
We'll get you an appointment
with the financial aid office.
They can help.
They're just gonna give me
another work-study job.
I can barely do
all my schoolwork as it is.
Oh, my God.
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't stop breathing.
You need air to process and live.
Yeah, I also need money.
Is there another scholarship
I could apply for?
Another classical composition scholarship?
Well, I could switch concentrations.
Performance?
Girl, we both know you're a much
stronger composer than clarinetist,
and there's no money in classical.
Well, jazz. Jazz. I could write jazz.
Even less money, right?
What do I do?
Well, let's chat again on Monday after
you've had a few days to sit with this.
Hey, Hannah, we're gonna
get through it, okay?
I could write pop.
First place comes
with a scholarship, right?
Right, but--
You just said that I'm a stronger composer
than clarinetist moments ago.
And I wrote an outstanding piece
on pop harmonies in your
music theory class freshman year.
- I mean, your word, "outstanding."
- [laughs] It's true.
Not many people can write so eloquently
about the harmonic vocal identities
in the work of One Direction.
Yeah, see? Yeah, I can totally pop.
How hard can it be, really?
Famous last words,
because the competition,
it's pretty steep.
No, I can do this.
I will do this.
Okay.
Bring some ideas into class.
- And we'll talk.
- Okay.
[breathing heavily]
[Tucker] Dean!
[rock music playing]
Dean!
Where are you at?
Do not give me the silent treatment.
He's taking the world's longest shower.
- Still?
- At least the door's shut this time.
Logan, drain's clogged again.
No shit. Finish your fucking shower,
I'll come fix it.
Dean, come help with the kegs.
I told you, I'll be right down.
Yeah, but when?
You want me to come down naked, Tucker?
Because I'll do it.
He sure will.
Never mind. Forget I asked.
Maybe Garrett will help.
Where the fuck is Garrett?
- Hmm.
- Guys?
- [Garrett] Hey, what's up, buddy?
- [man 1] What's up, G?
- [woman] Hi, Garrett.
- [man 2] Garrett!
- [woman 2] Hey!
- [Garrett] Hey.
[woman 3] Hi.
- Yo, Garrett. What up?
- What's up, bud?
Can't wait for the
Eastwood game tomorrow.
- Ladies.
- Hey.
Oh, it's Garrett.
Deanie.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [loud music blaring]
- Smells good, Tuck.
- Thank you.
Dean? Dean.
Dude, can't you see I'm cooking, man?
Same, bro.
[Logan] I just fixed the shower. Again.
Give you one guess.
Oh, jeez.
Well, that could be anyone.
Fuck, dude.
It's obviously yours, bud.
- Don't look at me.
- What?
Shower sex is hot.
So the next time a drain gets clogged
in this house, you get to fix it.
Yeah, like Dean's ever snaked a drain.
Have you ever snaked a drain?
I know what snaking a drain is.
I mean, that counts, right?
Hey, what are these dainty
fucking sandwiches you're making, Tuck?
It's a house party. We need dippables.
[Logan] I'm sorry, did you just--?
Yeah, he just said "dippables"?
- Dippables.
- Dippables!
Okay.
Dippables.
[overlapping chatter]
None for you, Logan,
if you're gonna make fun of my food.
Dude, it's beautiful, man.
They look great.
- [music blaring]
- What are we listening to?
[turns music off]
["Nothin' but a Good Time"
by Poison playing]
There we go.
Hey, can you play something
from this millennium, please?
This is a classic.
♪Now listen ♪
♪Not a dime, I can't pay my rent ♪
♪I can barely make it through the week ♪
I would not have pegged you
for an oldies guy.
Kendall.
Graham.
I brought you a refill.
One's my max
night before a game.
So strict.
Are you also strict about
non-alcoholic kinds of fun?
Like what?
[band playing rock music]
♪I'm so into you I can barely breathe ♪
♪And all I want to do
is to fall in deep ♪
♪Close ain't close enough
til we cross the line...♪
Hey, so for your pop showcase
tour de force,
are we feeling vocal vibes or mayhem?
I don't know. I feel like I'm more
of a Taylor than a Gaga.
You haven't fallen in love
enough times to be a Taylor.
Yes, I have.
With who?
- Okay, fine.
- Exactly.
You never have crushes.
The fact that you are down bad
for Justin Kohl
is totally a sign that he's special.
So be Taylor and do something about it.
♪A little less conversation ♪
♪And a little more touch my body ♪
♪'Cause I'm so into you ♪
♪Into you, into you...♪
Have you seen him?
He's so much easier
to look at than talk to.
Come on, just because he can
play the guitar and has tiny tattoos
doesn't make him
some untouchable rock god.
What are you afraid of?
I-I don't know.
Okay, maybe I talk to him,
and his accent makes me melt,
and it goes terribly.
Or he's just not interested,
and then I never feel this way
about anyone ever again.
Or maybe...
Or maybe?
I'm not you, Allie
I can't just find a husband
day one of college.
I can't talk to a guy
like it's no big deal.
I walked in on Garrett Graham
in the shower,
and I fell over a laundry cart.
- You did what?
- I don't want to talk about it.
You saw Garrett Graham naked?
- What did he look like?
- He looked naked.
And then I fell, which is my point.
I can't do this.
Oh, okay. I have an idea.
Literally everyone's going
to block party tomorrow,
including Justin, probably.
When's an easier time
to talk to a guy than a party?
Well, I don't like parties.
But you love music.
No, I need to work on my showcase song.
- That's an excuse, and you know it.
- No, it's not.
I want to present a demo
in my class next week.
So pull an all-nighter.
I think I'm spending the night
at Sean's anyway.
You'll have the place to yourself.
- But I--
- No, Hannah.
I'm not letting you
off the hook this time.
If you want to be a Taylor,
you have to take a risk.
♪I'm so into you ♪
♪Into you, into you ♪
♪Into you, into you...♪
["Body on Me" by Nxidia playing]
♪I want you like the pills
behind the counter that hit ♪
♪I want you so bad
my fingers shook with it ♪
♪And we could have
all of the money in the world ♪
♪But all the money the in world
couldn't buy us this ♪
♪You're somebody else ♪
[singing in Arabic]
♪They don't know, but we will ♪
♪I change my hair,
you change your clothes ♪
♪My cheap tattoos, they feel like home ♪
♪Kiss me 'til my lips are bruised ♪
♪I promise no one's watching you ♪
♪Not just a body, you're somebody,
what a body ♪
♪You're somebody to me ♪
♪Not just a body, you're somebody,
what a body ♪
♪Want your body on me ♪
♪Not just a body, you're somebody,
what a body ♪
♪You're somebody to me ♪
♪Not just a body, you're somebody,
what a body ♪
♪Want your body on me ♪
♪It's ironic and it might take you
by surprise ♪
♪My boxer shorts are super dry ♪
♪I change my hair,
you change your clothes ♪
♪My cheap tattoos, they feel like home ♪
♪People talk but I don't care ♪
♪So can you run your fingers
through my hair?♪
♪People talk, I know they do ♪
♪Let's let them talk about me and you ♪
♪Not a body, not a body ♪
♪You're somebody to me ♪
♪Not just a body, you're somebody ♪
♪What a body, you're somebody to me ♪
- ♪What a body, you're somebody to me ♪
- Oh!
Ugh! [sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
I've missed you.
- [laughs]
- [cell phone chimes]
I've been busy at practice.
Yeah, no, it's-it's not a judgment.
I just missed you.
Hm.
Did you miss me?
Um... [chuckles]
Wow.
Okay, guess I misread this.
No.
Well, I mean, yeah, you kind of did.
But, you know, Kendall,
I've been very up-front.
My whole life is morning workouts,
class, practice, repeat.
The whole team has practice,
Garrett, okay?
- They still have lives.
- Yeah.
I mean, well, none of them
were drafted by the Bruins.
So you're special.
That's not...
No, I was just made captain.
So the Bruins are watching every game.
How I play, how I behave.
I can't lose focus.
So like I said before,
all I can offer is casual.
Yeah, well, I don't
want that anymore, okay?
I... I want to be your girlfriend.
Why?
Hey, I mean, like, what I mean is...
What's my favorite band?
My major?
How do I like my coffee?
What's my mother's name?
Look, I don't know
any of those answers about you either,
so maybe...
you just want to be with the guy
headed to the NHL,
or you've deluded yourself
into thinking that I'm someone
I never pretended to be.
But, um, either way,
you deserve better.
Fuck you, Garrett.
[door opening]
Yeah, fuck me.
[door closes]
[sighs]
["Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap"
by AC/DC playing]
[TV host 1] There's a lot of hype
around these young guys.
The Bruins are putting a lot of faith,
a lot of stock in Garrett Graham.
[TV host 2] He has the ability
and the potential
- to be a generational player.
- [TV host 1] Wow, really?
Garrett is the type of player
who has that tenacity,
but I'm betting
that Garrett Graham proves me right.
♪If you got a lady and you want her gone ♪
♪But you ain't got the guts ♪
♪She keeps nagging at you night and day ♪
♪Enough to drive you nuts ♪
♪For a fee, I'm happy to be ♪
♪Your backdoor man ♪
♪Whoo ♪
♪Dirty deeds ♪
♪Done dirt cheap ♪
♪Dirty deeds done dirt...♪
That was a good one, that was a good one.
Oh, I take it back!
♪Dirty deeds and they're done dirt cheap ♪
Move! Move! Come on! Come on!
♪Oh ♪
Go big, bro!
Bang, bang.
You know what I mean?
Come on!
Move! Move! Come on!
♪Dirty deeds ♪
♪Dirty deeds done dirt cheap ♪
♪Yeah ♪
We weren't dating.
You kind of were.
Yeah, you and Kendall
have been hooking up all semester.
- House says...
- [all] Aye!
Nay.
- Nay.
- Okay, Dean agrees with you.
Which kind of just proves you're wrong.
- Fuck.
- You know,
I don't have to take this slander.
I am a responsible,
upstanding member of society.
[woman] Dean?
I'll be ready in 30 minutes.
Thirty minutes?
- [Dean] Maybe an hour?
- [Tucker] That's ambitious.
All right, he gets a half hour.
If he's any longer, we're leaving.
- [Logan] Thanks, Tuck.
- Yes, sir.
[Logan] Is it your dad?
Yeah.
[clears throat]
Yeah, he's got a new girlfriend.
Wants me to meet her.
Ah. That's inevitable, right?
Look, I know he can be a dick.
- Oh, he's more than a dick.
- Okay.
But he's still your dad.
All he cares about is hockey.
You know, I only matter
because I am him.
I'm just a mini fucking Phil Graham.
Yeah, man. I mean, all you'd have to do
is win a Stanley Cup,
a Norris Trophy or two,
spend more time on your hair
than a Kardashian,
and bam, yeah, just like him.
[laughs]
Hey.
Your dad was great.
Everybody knows it.
But no one is expecting you to be him.
He is.
All our parents have expectations, G.
Shit, I'd kill for my dad
to be into hockey,
let alone a damn legend.
All right?
But we're not doing this for them.
We're doing this because we love it.
Right?
- [horn blows]
- [crowd cheering]
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
- [glasses clink]
- Now take a shower. You smell like shit.
[sighs]
[playing piano notes]
- Hi.
- [both chuckle]
You're in here.
Yeah, I can't pull an all-nighter
in my room or I'll fall asleep.
Fair enough.
How's it going?
I have a melody. No lyrics, though.
Well, that's great.
That's like halfway done, right?
No, not really.
Lyrics are kind of a big thing in pop.
That's why classical is easier.
Dude, I have seen your sheet music.
Classical is not easier.
Definitely is.
Have you ever written a pop song before?
Not since high school.
It'll come back to you.
Like riding a bike.
Yeah, maybe. [sighs]
Hey.
Be nice to my friend Hannah.
You just started writing.
These things take time, right?
[sighs]
What if I can't, Al?
What if I write a terrible song
and I fail the pop showcase
and I can't afford
my tuition next semester?
Like, what if you're right?
If I don't fall in love,
I can't be a Taylor
that can write a perfect song
about love and life and heartbreak.
Hey, hey, you are setting the bar
way too high.
I mean, of course
you're gonna fall in love.
Someday.
Maybe it'll be with Justin.
Maybe someone else.
No, I've just been staring
at this blank page all night,
and I have literally no idea
what it should be about.
What did you write about in high school?
- What?
- You said you wrote in high school.
What did you write about?
[breathing heavily]
Hannah?
Uh... nothing.
It's dumb.
Well, something will come to you, okay?
- Just give it time.
- Yeah.
Hey, out of curiosity,
you weren't supposed to open
at Malone's today, right?
Shit!
[upbeat music playing]
[Della] There you are.
Sorry, Della.
[Della] It's about time.
I ain't as young as I fucking used to be.
I can't handle this
all on my own, you know?
I know. I'm sorry.
Hey.
[inaudible]
Uh, hello.
Hi.
Hi. Hi.
Picking up a takeaway order
for Justin Kohl.
Y-Yeah. No, I-I know who you are.
We've spoken kind of. Um...
Your-- Your band is really good.
Yeah, thanks.
I'm not like a creepy stalker fan
or anything.
I work here, so I've heard you.
Figured. The uniform.
Right. [laughs]
"I carried a watermelon."
- [laughing]
- What?
It's Dirty Dancing?
Um, Jennifer Grey has this really
awkward moment with Patrick Swayze
when, uh...
Sorry, never mind. Obviously, I work here.
[laughs]
Look, I'm kind of in a rush. Can I...?
Oh, my God, yeah. Yeah, sorry.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Bye.
Smooth.
"I carried a watermelon"?
Did anyone ever tell you
that eavesdropping is rude?
that your references are dated?
It's a classic.
I just came over here to see
if I could place an order.
Or is it like a self-serve kind of day?
I'll be right with you.
You shouldn't fawn over him.
- What?
- That guy.
You're too available.
Like the girls throwing themselves
at you over there.
That's a different scenario.
I don't do girlfriends. They know that.
Okay, well, congratulations, Casanova.
But I don't need your help.
- Refill?
- Yeah, please.
What if I paid you?
To take your dating advice?
To tutor me, nerd.
You could just ask my name.
Usually, girls just tell me.
Come on. I'll pay you anything.
You're the only one who got an A.
So?
So, I need to play.
Why? Because you get off
on beating people up?
What?
Hockey is the only non-combat sport that
doesn't eject its players for fighting.
It celebrates it.
When a team is down in points,
an actual strategy
is to pick a fight for morale.
Sorry.
I'm sure you're not a bad guy.
I just don't like hockey.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
[hip-hop music playing over radio]
Hey.
Just talk to him.
You'll be all right.
[keys jingle]
[Dean] Papa Graham.
Di Laurentis.
Great hit on McManus last week.
Bet that kid felt it in his bones.
Well, you know, got to keep them
off my boys' back.
I like it.
Tucker, you're looking good out there.
You're really finding
your rhythm with the line.
Thanks, Mr. Graham.
Will we see you in the stands
this afternoon?
Wouldn't miss it.
[Logan] Mr. Graham.
Logan.
[Phil] Looking handsome as ever.
You too, man. Good to see you.
[Phil] Oh.
[chuckles]
Saw that you made captain.
About time.
- I'm a junior.
- Well, better late than never.
Did you drive out here to congratulate me,
or make me feel like I fucked up somehow?
Look, I tried calling you earlier,
but you don't answer...
I'm not here to fight.
Can we just go inside?
No. No, thanks.
- Garrett.
- Dad.
Fine.
Cindy and I are getting married.
You've been dating for, like, two seconds.
- Six months.
- That's not any better.
Does she even fucking know you?
- Watch it.
- I don't have any time for this.
- We have a game today.
- I know.
Eastwood. Our biggest rivals.
- She wants to meet you.
- Your timing is fucking shit.
If you would just--
I didn't answer my phone
because I don't want to talk to you.
You told me your news. Congratulations.
I'll see you at the wedding.
♪Make you a man and make you an animal ♪
- ♪Boy ♪
- ♪For real ♪
♪Boy ♪
♪Starin' at fate,
I'm in the lead and I'm breaking away ♪
[announcer]
Please welcome your very own
Briar U Hawks!
♪...playin' it safe ♪
♪Surveillance the way
that they runnin' my tapes ♪
♪Got hoes in a craze like the old B2K,
chaos whenever I touch down, no brakes ♪
♪Me and HB, it's an instant slap
an instant plaque, a system crash ♪
♪I pitched it black and risked the max
and anything less, I can't live with that ♪
♪Hunger for more
and I still got the cravin'♪
♪What you know 'bout
when the walls get to cavin'?♪
♪What you know 'bout stayin' silent
and patient ♪
♪And workin' out kinks before kinks
work their way in...♪
[TV host 2]
I think he has the potential, honestly,
to have a bigger impact
than Phil ever had.
[TV host 1] All right, I can't wait
to hear what Phil has to say about that.
♪Starin' at fate
I'm in the lead and I'm breaking away ♪
♪If you not working
you takin' up space ♪
♪I'm at the table, a thousand a plate ♪
♪How you gon' tell me this isn't a date ♪
♪Down the street from the Denzel estate ♪
♪Right 'round the corner from Babyface
Not my dawg Babyface Ray, I mean--♪
♪I mean, swerve ♪
♪I know money ain't everything, fuck it,
we still want it...♪
[TV host 2]
Garrett Graham is a bigger player.
I think he can play that mean,
physical, game.
But he needs to be consistent.
[Logan] Bring it home, G!
[crowd groans]
Hey, come on, bro. Get your head in it.
♪This ain't a tour, this a tournament ♪
♪If I was stuck in a room
with your shit on repeat...♪
[TV host 1] His dad certainly taught him
everything he knows, right?
Phil Graham's physicality was brutal.
I mean, he's always on the warpath.
Making Daddy proud, Graham?
♪Take this shit where I wanna go...♪
Fuck!
♪Make you a million
and make you a hunnid more...♪
- [thudding]
- [grunting]
[slamming and crunching]
[whistle blows]
[referee]
Boarding, five minutes.
Let's go, Graham. Get in the box.
- [yelling]
- [crowd] Oh!
[TV host 1] I am curious to see what kind
of player Garrett Graham turns out to be.
♪Yeah, fuck you expect, bitch?♪
- He said that?
- You know Garrett,
he doesn't do the girlfriend thing.
He also doesn't do
the repeat hookups thing.
- You've been hooking up since summer.
- Whatever.
And honestly, he's playing like shit.
[man] Yo, Graham's playing like shit.
[Delaney]
I told you they're fucking losers.
Ha-ha. Let's hope they keep at it.
We'll destroy them.
Hell, yeah, let me get some of that,
Delaney.
Gotcha, bro.
[distorted audio playing]
[pulsing sound]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[overlapping chatter]
- [grunts]
- [all] Whoa.
Hey, Garrett!
- Hey, the game's not over!
- [door slams]
[sighs and sniffles]
["The Bitch Is Back"
by Elton John playing]
[inhales deeply and exhales]
[playing along with the song]
[music playing faintly]
♪I was justified when I was five ♪
♪Raising Cain, I spit in your eye ♪
♪Times are changing, now the poor get fat ♪
♪But the fever's gonna catch you
when the bitch gets back ♪
♪Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪Eat meat on a Friday, that's all right ♪
♪I even like steak on a Saturday night ♪
♪Ooh, oh ♪
♪I get high in the evening
sniffing pots of glue ♪
♪Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch ♪
♪Oh, the bitch is back ♪
♪Stone-cold sober, as a matter of fact ♪
♪I can bitch, I can bitch,
'cause I'm better than you ♪
- ♪It's the way that I move ♪
- Whoo!
♪It's the things that I do, oh-oh-oh ♪
[crowd cheering]
♪Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪I entertain by picking brains ♪
♪Sell my soul by dropping names ♪
♪I don't like those, my God, what's that?♪
♪Oh, it's full of nasty habits
when the bitch gets back ♪
♪Oh-oh-oh ♪
[song cuts out]
[sighs]
♪I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch,
oh, the bitch is back ♪
♪Stone-cold sober, as a matter of fact ♪
♪I can bitch, I can bitch...♪
[Garrett] Thanks, Deanie!
Logan, Logan.
Here we go. Here we go.
- Hey, Tuck.
- ♪Whoa ♪
- ♪Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
- Your sub!
Whoo!
- Yes!
- [crowd cheers]
♪Oh, oh, oh ♪
Welcome back, man!
Yeah, I thought we lost you
for a minute there.
♪I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch,
oh, the bitch is back ♪
♪Stone-cold sober, as a matter of fact ♪
♪I can bitch, I can bitch,
'cause I'm better than you ♪
♪It's the way that I move ♪
- ♪The things that I do, oh-oh-oh ♪
- [buzzer sounding]
♪Hey, hey, yeah ♪
Whoo!
♪Bitch, bitch ♪
♪The bitch is back ♪
♪Oh, hey, bitch, bitch ♪
♪Oh, bitch, bitch...♪
[players cheering]
[man on video]
It's not on the one. It's not the mambo.
It's a feeling. A heartbeat.
[imitating heartbeat]
Don't try so hard.
- [imitating heartbeat]
- [knock on door]
Close your eyes.
- What are you doing?
- Watching a movie.
I mean, why are you in bed?
- [knock on door]
- Because I'm watching a movie.
[Allie] But we talked about this.
You promised.
Sean, convince Hannah
to come out with us.
Sean, tell Allie I have zero interest.
Also, I've had a long day,
and I'm watching a movie.
No, you're watching Dirty Dancing,
which means you're burrowing.
Hi, babe. Good to see you too.
Whatever. Hi. I love you.
Now convince Hannah to come out.
It's block party, Hannah.
[Sean] If you don't give in now,
she'll just keep at it until you do.
And if you still don't,
she'll text you all night,
distracting you.
Well, the power of "do not disturb."
That doesn't matter. She's coming.
I don't--
What just happened?
Justin Kohl just happened.
- Uh, Dexter's already there.
- And so is Justin fucking Kohl.
And he's there alone,
which means Hannah's gonna slide right in.
- No, no, I have nothing to wear.
- [Allie] Okay.
Well, that's not even remotely true.
Come on, I'll pick out your outfit.
You just do your makeup.
But really try to look hot, Hannah.
Do I not normally?
You just look...
Sean, help me.
I plead the Fifth.
Fine, okay, I'll do your makeup too.
Just hustle before Justin leaves.
[upbeat rock music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[band playing "Soup" by Remi Wolf]
♪Stay, stick around ♪
♪Please don't...♪
- Hey.
Oh! Ooh!
Yes, bitch!
That is what I'm talking about, honey.
Okay, don't look now,
but Justin is right--
I just said don't look now.
Now you have to go over there.
No, I talked to him earlier.
It was not good.
Just-- Just stop overthinking this.
You know, this is why we pregame.
Now put on your big-girl pants
and go talk to him.
I can get us more shots if you need them.
Liquid courage.
- No peer pressure.
- How is that--?
Hannah's friend from high school
that got roofied?
We are not pressuring Hannah
to drink in public.
We are only pressuring Hannah
to finally talk to Justin fucking Kohl.
Right?
Fine. But can we dance first?
[Allie] Hell yeah, we can.
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪I don't want to live without you ♪
- ♪I don't want to live without you ♪
- Thank you so much.
[continues singing]
You know, if you pick your head
up three inches,
there's a party.
The waitress from Malone's,
what's her name?
It's Hannah.
[laughs] What?
Idiot.
Dude, she's waited on us
like 17,000 times.
Who, she has?
Yeah, you seriously haven't noticed her?
[laughs]
All right, we're doing shots.
We're doing shots, boys.
Come on.
Bro, I'm watching you spill it.
- Come on, buddy.
- Have some faith.
[Logan] Thank you very much.
- Take your tampon out and relax.
- Okay. Yep.
Got a little bit of luck goin' on.
[laughter]
You drinking tonight, G?
Uh, yeah. So it seems.
Okay.
Here's to me, here's to you.
Fuck the rest, we're Briar U.
- Yes, sir. Come on.
- Good one, Deanie.
- ♪Hoping that I'm getting better ♪
- Cheers, boys.
♪Till I'm ♪
♪Doing business on the top of the roof ♪
♪They told me to leave ♪
♪But I don't want to leave without you ♪
♪You're so patient with the animals too ♪
♪If you give me your keys,
I'll go and pick up the soup ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪I don't want to live without you ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪I don't want to live without ♪
Thanks so much!
[all cheering]
[band playing laid-back percussive music]
Fuck yeah!
[band playing "Alone in Miami"
by Remi Wolf]
♪So good, the sound of crypto bros ♪
♪Eat in Cubanos by myself ♪
♪Met up with Maine, bought cocaine ♪
♪Clothes in the lobby waiting for me ♪
♪And I'm on the list with that girl...♪
[Allie] Um, hello?
♪We're on the rocks but now we're okay ♪
♪Playin' DJ...♪
[Dean] All yours, princess.
♪...in the Escalade ♪
♪Yeah, we're okay eatin' sushi
long as Playboy pays ♪
♪Alone in Miami...♪
[faint singing]
[band continues playing]
♪Alone in Miami ♪
♪Alone, alone ♪
♪Alone, alone, alone ♪
- [music ends]
- [crowd cheers]
Okay, you're ready.
- No, I'm not.
- Don't worry, we'll be watching.
Perfect.
Okay, give me your coat.
[band playing "Toro" by Remi Wolf]
- [Dexter] Mm-hmm!
- [Allie] Ooh!
- [Dexter] You got this.
- [Allie] You got it, go!
[sighs]
♪Dancing around and spilling wine ♪
♪You look good...♪
- Yes.
- Fuck.
[crowd cheering]
♪Steam in the shower, singing Sly,
wash your bone ♪
♪We're gonna need a little bit more soap...♪
[laughter]
[man 2]
Yeah, wet T-shirt contest.
Hey, you-- You okay?
Yeah, uh...
[Hannah clears throat]
[stammers]
Stupid shoes.
[both laugh]
I think we got off
on the wrong foot earlier.
I'm a musician too.
Writer, not performer.
Sick, yeah.
What kind of stuff do you write?
Uh, classical, mostly.
Classical.
Uh, but I'm trying out other styles too.
Like pop, folk, R&B.
Uh...
rock, electronic.
Uh, but mostly pop, though.
- And classical...
- [Garrett] Wellsy.
- Garrett?
- Babe.
I am always telling you to wear
your jacket. You never do.
Oh, no!
No, no, no. You come here.
What...?
Hey.
- I'm, uh...
- I know who you are, man.
Yeah, you were gnarly at Eastwood today.
- Yeah. Thanks, man.
- [Justin] No worries.
You're a hockey fan?
Uh, yeah. My dad played.
Nothing like Phil Graham
but, uh, yeah, we'd watch together.
You're Hannah, right?
- Yeah.
- Hannah Wells.
Right.
Yeah, well, it was nice
to meet you officially.
- Aww.
- Oh, okay.
[inaudible dialogue]
- See you around.
- [Garrett] Sweet.
Yeah.
What the hell was that?
And how do you suddenly know my name?
Don't worry about it. And you're welcome.
For?
Now Jacob knows you who are.
- Justin.
- [laughs] Whatever.
Look, guys like that only want
what someone else has,
especially when that someone
is a Briar U athlete.
You really have a healthy opinion
of yourself, don't you?
I actually thought that was pretty modest.
I could have said starting center,
team captain,
highest scorer for two seasons straight.
[laughs]
It worked, didn't it?
[romantic music playing]
Why do you care?
I haven't been particularly nice to you.
You're a music major, right?
I saw your Instagram.
You, uh...
You sort of disappear when you play.
I don't mean that in a bad way.
I mean, uh, you love it. I can tell.
Don't you love hockey like that?
I don't know.
It's just something...
I've always done...
to impress my dad.
And does it?
Nothing impresses him.
[laughs]
Not really.
What about your mom?
She, um...
uh, she died.
A while back.
Cancer.
Oh, I...
Look...
I don't believe in favors or shortcuts.
I don't want to pass this class
because somebody handed me the grade.
I want to earn it.
And I'm pretty sure you're the only one
that can help me do that.
So what? I help you study for the midterm,
and you play my fake boyfriend
to get Justin's attention?
Something like that.
Well, you'd still have to pay me.
Obviously.
Don't forget.
I'm not your girl, Graham.
"This is my dance space,
this is your dance space.
I don't go into yours,
you don't come into mine."
You've seen Dirty Dancing.
It was my mom's favorite movie.
Still a dated reference, though.
[laughs] Asshole!
See? Hey, this is why this is perfect.
You're not interested in me,
and I'm not interested in a relationship.
So this arrangement
is mutually beneficial?
Purely transactional.
So?
Deal.
["Dancing with Myself"
by The Donnas playing]
♪Oh, oh, dancing with myself ♪
♪Dancing with myself ♪
♪When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
[Garrett] For this plan to work,
we have to sell it.
If we're gonna be fake dating,
there needs to be real kissing.
Whoa, easy. I just met you.
[Garrett] What are we gonna do,
hold hands?
You seriously think that's gonna get
Justin's attention?
- Is he looking?
- No.
[clanking]
He's looking now.
[upbeat music]
This won't make your friendship
weird at all?
[Garrett] If we're gonna convince anyone
that we're hooking up
you can't blush
whenever I come near you.
Get over yourself, I don't blush.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah?
See? Nothing.
Not bad.
[cheering]
Me and you on the Bruins.
That's the dream, right?
Garrett Graham doesn't do girlfriends.
What's really going on?
Oh, my God. Justin's here.
Be cool. You're with me.
[Hannah] He is not just some random guy
I want to hook up with.
He is a talented musician
who I respect.
Why don't you tell me
what you think the song is about.
Like being in love with someone
who doesn't see you.
[Garrett] She's not my girlfriend.
But you clearly want her to be.
[upbeat music continues]
[cheering]
You're not taking us, this, seriously.
[Garrett] Watch the player, not the puck.
[Hannah]
What the hell does that mean?
[Garrett]
It means, trust me.
["Dancing with Myself"
by The Donnas continues]
♪If I looked all over the world ♪
♪And there's every type of girl ♪
♪But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪So let's sink another drink ♪
♪It'll give me time to think ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪Oh, oh, dancing with myself ♪
♪If there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪I'm dancing with myself ♪
- ♪Oh, oh-oh ♪
- ♪Sweat! Sweat! Sweat!♪
- ♪Sweat! Sweat!♪
♪I've looked all over the world ♪
♪And there's every type of girl ♪
♪But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪You left me dancing with myself ♪
♪So let's sink another drink ♪
♪It'll give me time to think ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪I'd be dancing! Dancing!♪
♪Dancing with myself ♪
♪Oh, oh-oh, dancing with myself ♪
♪If I had the chance
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh!♪
- Five p.m. Tuesday.
- Rehearsal.
Two p.m. Thursday.
A class, then work, then rehearsal.
- Seven a.m. Tuesday?
- Practice.
Seven a.m. Wednesday? Also practice.
See? This is why I told you
I can't help you.
- You're busy, I'm busy.
- That's fine, we'll make it work.
The pop showcase needs to be
my top priority.
Well, passing this class is mine.
[sighs]
- Give me your phone.
- What?
Just...
- Thanks.
- [camera shutter clicks]
Thank you.
All right.
Nine p.m. tonight.
After "The sounds of wind and fog."
Is that a class or a haiku?
[laughs] It's a class.
I want to be a film composer.
Oh.
That's cool.
All right, phone?
Hold on.
[camera shutter clicks]
Nice.
Okay, now you have my number.
I sent myself a text, so I have yours.
Oh, and actually...
- [camera shutter clicks]
- Whoa! Easy.
Wellsy, you're gonna have to loosen up
if we're dating.
- It's Hannah.
- I like Wellsy.
- [scoffs]
- We're gonna have to take that again.
Okay, no, we don't.
You can't just kiss me out of the blue.
Actually, you can't kiss me at all.
If we're gonna be fake dating,
there needs to be real kissing.
I just met you.
So, what are we gonna do? Hold hands?
I mean...
I mean, heh, it's cute,
but it's not gonna work.
- Well, why not?
- Because we have to make him jealous.
And no guy gets jealous
about holding hands.
We'll agree to disagree.
You seriously think that's gonna
get Justin's attention?
Just walk down the hall holding hands?
Problem is, I don't do girlfriends.
Everyone that follows Fifth Line
knows that.
Am I supposed to know
what Fifth Line is?
How have you never...
It's the Briar gossip account.
Like, mostly hockey team shit.
Oh, because your lives are so interesting?
I mean, yeah, kinda.
Trust me, if we're gonna convince Justin,
we gotta convince Jules.
Who?
My best friend's younger sibling.
They run the account.
If Jules believes we're real,
we make it onto Fifth Line.
- And if we make it onto Fifth Line--
- No, okay, I get it.
But why can't we just tell Jules?
Get them in on it?
They don't do fake gossip.
For this plan to work,
we have to sell it.
Classic first period strategy.
♪So one, two, three
take my hand and come with me ♪
♪Because you look so fine
that I really wanna make you mine ♪
[Garrett] Maintain possession of the puck
and establish a rhythm.
Throw your opponent off his game,
get the crowd on your side.
[Hannah]
Wait, sorry, I'm the puck?
It's a metaphor, Wellsy.
Who's the tutor here?
Okay, whatever. Is there a phase two?
Offensive zone pressure.
Find opportunities to crash the crease
and look for rebounds.
[Hannah]
Sure. Crash. Crease. Rebounds. Totally.
[Garrett] We showboat our relationship
in front of crowds, in front of Justin,
and especially in front of Jules,
whenever we can.
[Hannah] And phase three?
We break up, you cry.
You expect me to cry over you?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Wellsy, this fake relationship
is going to destroy you.
I mean, your life will never
be the same again.
And then, Justin will swoop in
and pick up all the pieces.
You're gonna fake cry over me, too, right?
Oh, I'll be inconsolable.
Well, that part I like.
You gotta admit, it's kind of genius.
So, when do we start?
♪I said, are you gonna be my girl ♪
- [loud pop music playing]
- [video game playing on TV]
[music continues]
[Logan] Pause it, guys.
Hi. I'm...
Hannah, right?
Garrett's tutor?
Yeah, sorry it took me so long.
No one ever really knocks.
[Simms exclaims in Czech]
Dude, I told you to pause it.
- There's no pausing in hockey.
- Bullshit.
You get gassed after, like, a minute.
[Simms] You guys take pauses all the time.
I'm the one out there all the time.
[Tucker]
To be fair, you just stay in one spot.
[Simms speaking Czech]
[Tucker] You gotta work on
your transitions, bro.
Honestly, I'm doing better
without you, so...
Fuck you. I'm carrying your ass.
Hey.
I'm Jules.
Pillow chucker's sibling.
Who are you? What's your deal?
Careful, don't tell Jules anything
you don't want the whole school knowing.
I only report the facts.
Wellsy.
Hey.
We can study in my room.
Uh, down here is fine.
No, no, it's better up there. No worries.
Jules.
[indistinct squabbling]
Semi-nudity was not part of the deal.
Oh, please. Don't flatter yourself.
It's for Jules' benefit, not yours.
- [woman laughing]
- Dean, dude,
I told you
to shut your fucking door, man.
- We have company.
- [giggling]
Sorry about him.
He's a heathen.
This is me.
[both laughing]
Okay, uh,
for your oral presentation,
you're gonna have to argue the viewpoints
of one of our first unit philosophers
and how they relate to modern society.
[cell phone notification chimes]
- What was that?
- [chiming continues]
Oh, nothing.
Just a snap from a puck bunny.
- Is that what you actually call women?
- They call themselves that.
Wait, are people gonna think
I'm a puck bunny?
No one is going to think
you are a puck bunny.
[notifications chime]
Okay, let's just start with Nietzsche.
[notifications continue]
Um, no, actually, I don't need your notes.
Nietzsche believed that morality
was defined by the individual.
God is dead, or whatever.
Kant, on the other hand, was trying
to find what morality was itself.
What the duties and obligations
of the individual were to begin with.
If you know that already,
why do you need my help?
Well, I mean, memorizing is easy, right?
What I don't understand is how
they can be saying different things
and both still be right.
- It's not about being right.
- [notifications chime]
Oh, my God.
[chiming continues]
Okay.
This is Garrett's tutor.
Please leave him alone.
He'll fuck you later.
[Garrett laughs] Damn.
Now I have to fuck her later.
Oh, only if you believe in obligations.
You want my head where?
Just in between my, uh...
Hey, is that even your head?
Doesn't matter.
I'm not doing August 19th.
All right. Uh...
Ooh! June 28th is kind of hot.
You can do a back bend?
No, you're doing the back bend.
I don't know about this.
Okay. Um, yeah.
- I'll just find a better one.
- No, I--
I mean any of this.
The calendar, the sex positions.
Do you not like what we've been doing?
No, I just, like, thought it might be fun
to try something different.
You know, I just-- After two years, I
don't want us getting boring.
Our sex is boring?
No, no. I didn't--
We're just a little predictable, is all.
I mean, like, we do the same things,
and we see the same people,
and we break up and get back together.
Like, I'm just trying to shake us
out of our routine here.
I like our routine.
Okay, not the break-up part,
but the rest of it is...
We see the same people
because we're in college.
We eat at the same places
Life's not gonna be like this forever, Al.
Yeah, so let's go out
and hook up on the dance floor
and make out in the back of an Uber.
- We're not those people.
- No, but we could be.
Right?
I mean... don't you want more?
Okay, let me see August 19th again.
No. No, it's fine. Fine.
The usual stuff is fine.
I can put a pillow under your butt.
You said that felt good last time, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's just do that.
[Hannah's composition playing]
Okay, what did we love
about Hannah's piece?
[muttering throughout]
Come on. It's Hannah's first time
going for the pop showcase.
How do we help make it stronger?
We're classical comp majors.
We don't do pop.
I commend your intellectual flexibility.
Truly.
Anyone?
It's a nice melody.
There we go. Thank you.
- Aren't there lyrics?
- I haven't finished it yet.
Hannah. Just, uh, try to listen.
Okay.
I think what we are looking for here
is constructive criticism.
Honestly, sounds a lot like
Hannah's film score work.
Background music for someone else's story.
Like you're afraid to really
get under the surface
of what the song wants to be about.
[breathing heavily]
[woman] Just write, Hannah.
I am sure it went better
than you think it did.
No, it really didn't.
Cutting it close, Mr. Graham.
Sorry. Had to stop
and grab coffee for my girl.
[mouthing]
[laughs]
What's in this?
I think you meant to say, "Thanks, baby."
Baby?
So, for those of you
who were remotely paying attention...
Drink the damn coffee.
...you'll remember where we left off...
- I'm lactose intolerant.
- Just pretend.
What, pretend I'm not lactose intolerant?
Hannah...
pretend you like me.
[professor] ...how it can be used
to disrupt industries it purports to aid.
These disruptions...
Is he looking? I can't tell.
...vary in both severity and morality.
Nope.
[professor] Now, technology has always
been a driving force in progress...
What about now?
...but what is the morality...
No.
...technology designed solely
to divert wealth...
Okay, well, I can't take notes like this.
Nobody said you had to.
...push back against perceived progress
of those disruptions...
[loud crash]
[clanging]
And that's a great example
of an unwanted disruption.
[students chuckle]
He's looking now.
[Tucker] Don't miss.
- Don't miss.
- I ain't gonna miss.
[Tucker]
Don't miss. Don't miss. Don't miss.
Oh!
Fuck you.
Told you not to miss.
Come on. It wasn't that bad.
It was like a car crash
exploded into a volcano
and then fell down the stairs loudly.
[drumming]
[blowing kazoo]
Hear me! Hear me!
We have a proclamation
Stand by for the proclamation.
[Dean] The annual Maxwell Di Laurentis
birthday festivities
will take place this year
at the Maxwell summer home in...
- Cape Cod.
- [Logan] Whoo!
Thank you.
[Dean]
As it is our 22nd year gracing the earth,
the theme shall be twofers, right?
So please come dressed
as your second-favorite dynamic duo...
after us, of course.
The party bus departs
shortly after the team bus,
which shall bring ye there
and bring ye back the following morning.
Mm-hmm. So be there or...
Be there. There is no other option.
- [Bo] Drumroll, please.
- [Dean] Yes.
[blows kazoo]
[cell phones vibrating and chiming]
[sighs]
- That is all.
- That is all. Thank you.
- That was a lot.
- That's Dean and Bo for you.
They do the same kind of thing every year.
♪I look like a star, I'm shining ♪
Wait.
Justin is in Bo's frat.
♪They feel so inclined ♪
♪They're asking...♪
I got it.
Gonna need more words.
I'll give you two.
Hard launch.
♪Oh, I'd be jealous ♪
♪Oh, I'd be jealous if I met me too...♪
Hey, I would just like to say
this is the most absolutely unhinged plan,
and I'm obsessed with it.
And you. None of the hockey people know?
Hockey people?
Okay, Jules can't know.
This has to seem real.
[woman]
Is that Garrett Graham?
[woman 2] It is!
[giggling]
Okay, well, you've convinced
half the theater department.
[both chuckle]
We could be Beetlejuice.
What? No, you need to show up
as someone hot.
How dare you? Winona Ryder is beautiful.
Yeah, but she's not hot.
And don't you have any of those boots
that go up past the knee?
You mean "fuck me" boots?
We wear those
when we don't feel like shaving.
[Garrett] Ha. Well, I'm just saying.
I mean, you've got it, so flaunt it.
Okay, don't talk about my "it."
Not all women want to get dressed up
for the male gaze.
Yeah, but the women I'm with do.
Okay, enough. Listen, hockey man,
let's just get one thing straight.
My best friend is right
about literally everything, always,
now until the end of time.
- Thank you.
- But in this case,
you do gotta whip them thighs out.
Judas!
But if you want to get Justin's attention,
we have to be boy hot, not girl hot.
Wait, "we"?
Oh, yeah. Sean and I are coming.
I just decided.
A wild hockey party's exactly what we need
to shake us out of our funk.
You're already in a funk again?
You just got back together.
Even soulmates have ruts.
Or a series of ruts.
Okay, well, it'll be more fun to drive out
to the party with you, anyway.
Yeah, no, you're coming to the game.
That wasn't part of the deal.
Well, if you're into me,
you're into hockey.
[Allie] He's got a point.
And besides, you'll need to spend
the night anyway, right?
For fake sex reasons.
Yeah. Fake sex. So much fake sex.
Ugh! I want to be having fake sex.
You're having real sex.
Whatever. My point is, fake is fun.
Um, okay, what's my deadline
for this costume?
Uh, puck bunny bus leaves
at 4:00 p.m. Saturday.
- You said I'm not a puck bunny.
- You're not.
Doesn't mean you can't act like one.
Mm!
[Logan] Come on.
We dominated the Frozen Four last year
and the year before that.
To all the cocky sons of bitches out there
who think they can beat us,
I'd like to see you--
Give 110%.
- We practice at 110. We--
- Read each other's minds.
- What are you doing tonight? You wanna...
- Give 100%.
And then, um, give ten more.
Could you repeat the question?
[interviewer] How do you plan
to adjust to the challenge
of being Briar's new captain?
I don't think there's a need
to change anything.
My teammates expect
the best out of me,
and that's not a problem,
because I expect the best of myself.
[interviewer] Do you have
any other pregame rituals
or superstitions?
[Garrett]
Yeah, I'm pretty particular...
[calming keyboard music playing]
[distorted sounds playing]
[hockey stick cracks]
[sticks slapping on ice]
[sighs]
Hey.
Can I help you?
Uh, no. I'm here for Garrett.
Oh, I don't usually let girlfriends watch.
Definitely not a girlfriend.
I'm his philosophy tutor.
Oh, then you can stay.
[laughs]
- Not going easy on him, are you?
- No, sir.
Good. Do your best.
We need him out there.
Sorry, can't you just speak
to his professor, or dean, or whatever
if it's so important that he play?
I mean...
He didn't want me to.
What? Why?
Do you know who his dad is?
Some hockey player.
One of the best defensemen
in NHL history.
Garrett's last name carries weight.
He knows the spotlight's on him.
So he busts his ass to prove
that he's earned his place.
[Garrett]
...and build your own identity.
[interviewer] Thanks for your time.
Wait. Hey. I thought we had a session?
Weight room.
["Howlin' for You"
by the Black Keys playing]
Better hurry, Garrett's tutor.
♪All right ♪
♪Yeah ♪
♪I must admit ♪
♪I can't explain ♪
♪Any of these thoughts
racing through my brain ♪
♪It's true ♪
♪That, baby, I'm howling for you...♪
Hey, you know I don't appreciate
being made to wait 45 minutes.
I'm sorry. Sitting down for that long
must be so draining.
We'll reschedule.
Okay, okay. Hold on, hold on.
I can multitask.
I'll just be, uh, locking out
while studying Locke.
Really? You can?
Got a lot to cover, and I've never
met a guy who can genuinely do
two things at once.
Well, then you've been sleeping
with the wrong guys, Wellsy.
♪Da-da da-da da, da-da da-da da ♪
♪Da-da da-da da...♪
That was a joke.
Jesus.
If we're gonna convince anyone
that we're hooking up,
you can't freak out when I tease you.
We need to practice.
Practice what? Teasing?
We'll be fine as long as you stop
force-feeding me dairy products.
Forget your oat milk. This is serious.
You blush whenever I come near you.
- Get over yourself. I don't blush.
- [laughs] Oh, yeah?
See?
Nothing.
Not bad.
But what about when we kiss?
You're very sure of yourself.
Oh, right.
Your terms.
No kissing.
What's wrong, Graham?
I thought you said we needed practice.
[seductive percussive music playing]
Don't blush.
[Logan] So, this is tutoring?
What? No.
Uh...
Yes. [laughs]
Uh, he was just trying to prove a point.
It kind of feels like I just did.
And now it's my turn.
I'm gonna kiss you.
[hesitant] Okay.
[sighs]
Am I blushing now?
[door opens and closes]
[rock music playing]
It's here, folks.
Our first away game of the season.
The Briar Hawks have dominated
the Chatham Clovers in the past,
but since it's Di Laurentis's
birthday today,
we all know his mind
is already on the after-party.
Am I right?
But, we've got a good crowd here tonight.
Briar's most faithful bunnies
in attendance, as always.
[excited chatter]
First game?
- Yeah.
- I know we can seem like a lot,
but we don't bite, I swear.
Just stick by Jules.
I mean, their play-by-play
was a lifesaver my first time.
Thanks.
[laughs]
[whistle blows]
[Dean] Let's go! You got this, boys!
- Come on, now.
- This is a tough game for the Clovers.
- [player] Hey! Hey!
- [man] Graham! Graham!
[Garrett] Let's fucking go!
[slamming]
[man] Come on, baby!
Hey! Hey, chief! I'm open! I'm open!
All right, here we go.
- [Jules] Briar has control of the puck.
- Logan!
- [Jules] Logan back to Graham.
- Move it! Move it!
[Jules] Graham back to Logan.
Passing it back and forth
like chlamydia during Welcome Week.
Come on, guys.
Let someone else have a turn. It's fair.
[Garrett]
Go. Go. Top! Come on, baby!
Denied! Damn, so close.
Chatham tries to get the puck
the fuck out of town.
[player 1] Yeah, baby!
But Graham's right there
with the interception.
[player 1] Come on, G, pass it up.
- [player 2] Here! Over here! Come on!
- [player 1] Good. Take it up!
[Jules] Graham takes it alone. In...
- [buzzer sounds]
- Yes!
[all cheer]
[player] Goal!
[Jules] Hawks absolutely pounding
the Chatham Clovers.
- [excited chatter]
- All day! All day! Whoo!
He's good.
Yeah.
Problem is, he knows it.
[crowd chanting]
Hawks! Hawks! Hawks!
Fuck 'em up! Fuck 'em up!
[all cheering]
[roars]
Alright, Deany, baby.
- Hey.
- Let's go, set 'em up for them.
[all cheer]
- And-- [chuckles]
- Right here.
Ca-caw!
[all] Oh!
You fucking douche!
Hey! Zamboni!
- Seriously?
- Hey, waste not,
lest he be wasted.
- Come on.
- [all chanting] Zamboni!
Zamboni!
Zamboni! Zamboni! Zamboni!
Zamboni! Zamboni!
[all cheer]
[cheers and applause]
- Goose!
- Maverick!
- Come out!
- Come on, baby!
- Oh!
- Oh, boy.
["Deeply Still in Love"
by ROLE MODEL playing]
♪But it still bleeds ♪
♪I'm sorry, but I'm deeply still in love ♪
♪In love with you now ♪
♪Yes, ma'am ♪
♪Oh, yeah ♪
♪Well, I heard...♪
[chuckles]
♪I still can't swallow it...♪
- What?
- Holy shit.
I mean...
you totally nailed boy hot.
Good, because I feel like
an absolute cliché.
Any sign of Justin?
No. Not yet. But he'll be here.
Sig Tau takes birthdays very seriously.
[party-goer]
Yo, Garrett.
Oh, hey. Thanks, man.
Oh, no, thanks. I don't drink at parties.
Oh, yeah?
No worries, I'm not a big drinker either.
One on practice nights,
five after a game, no exceptions.
Seems pretty strict.
Do you think I was born with these abs?
- So, what's next?
- It's your favorite, actually.
Are you ready for this?
♪I'm sorry, but I'm deeply still in love ♪
♪In love with you...♪
[Tucker] Hockey shots!
- [partygoer] Whoo!
- Garrett, hockey shots.
Oh, shit. Yeah, I get it now.
- You're not a vampire.
- I am.
Yeah, sorry, Garrett's tutor,
but we need you, let's go.
It's a starting line tradition
when we win.
Bad luck if we don't.
Exactly, so we're doing it
because we beat Chatham's asses.
- That's right.
- [Tucker] Let's go.
- All right, come on.
- Come on! Come on!
Sorry.
[laughing] It's okay.
♪I'm sorry, but I'm deeply still in love...♪
[partygoers chanting]
Fuck them up! Fuck them up!
- Fuck them up! Fuck them up!
- You ready? Let's go.
- Come on.
- Fuck them up! Fuck them up!
[all cheer]
[inaudible]
[cheering fades]
[ominous music playing]
[Jules] Not a vampire.
Uh... what?
Garrett.
We all thought he was just
a very bad vampire,
but here you are looking like Elle Woods.
And you're Peter Pan's shadow?
Yeah, Peter's around here somewhere.
There's just one thing
I can't quite figure out.
Garrett Graham doesn't do girlfriends.
Dynamic duo's not his style.
Even when it is the theme.
So, Garrett's "tutor,"
what's really going on?
["like JENNIE" by JENNIE playing]
[boisterous shouting]
[car horn blaring]
Someone already blocked me in.
Come on, it looks so fun.
♪Special edition
and your AI couldn't copy ♪
[music continues indistinctly]
Hey, babe, where's your Dunkin' cup?
Uh, must have left it in the car.
Okay, well, without the cup
you don't look like Ben Affleck.
You just look like
some sad guy from Boston.
So, Ben Affleck?
Babe, get the cup.
So we can dance.
- Do we have to?
- Yes!
A house like this? A floor like that?
A dress like mine?
Come on.
Okay, I'll find the cup.
Thank you.
[squeals]
You know, it's sort of tutoring,
but have you looked at him?
I mean, he's John's best friend,
so not really.
- John?
- My brother, John Logan.
Right. Um, but I mean, objectively,
Garrett's a reasonably
attractive-looking human being
and sparks flew as they do
when people, um...
Sorry, what-what don't you get?
Any of it, really.
Because a guy like him couldn't possibly
be into a girl like me?
Oh, my God, no. You're just... different.
Not what I would have expected
for Garrett.
[bottle cap tinks]
So are you guys, like, "dating," dating?
Well, I mean, we're not, like,
exclusive or anything.
And she's cool with that?
Yeah, man. I guess so.
[chuckles]
It's just that last week,
you didn't even know her name, right?
[laughs]
Yeah, you know, I don't know.
Sometimes, people sneak up on you.
Hmm.
Jesus. Do you see anything non-alcoholic?
It's for Hannah.
She doesn't drink.
She said not at parties.
Oh.
[boisterous cheering]
Cute. Uh...
Here, try this.
Closed cans are safer, bro.
Thanks.
Go be the hero.
I can say this because Garrett's
basically my brother,
but he can be kind of a dick sometimes.
You know that, right?
Yeah, but, I mean, he's also funny
and really hardworking.
Kind of nice when he wants to be.
Hey, uh, sorry that took so long.
I couldn't find any mixers.
But I thought maybe...
I don't know.
You know, in case you change your mind.
No pressure, though.
Yeah, actually, thanks.
♪Oh, I can't see straight
and my hands are tied ♪
♪I could be your type
from your zombie bite ♪
♪No, I can't see straight
but the feeling's right...♪
Okay.
That was totally cute.
My single ass needs another drink.
[laughs]
Bye, Jules.
♪You zombie boy...♪
- Good work. Really.
- Thanks.
♪Like a lion on the hunt
for this kitten over here ♪
♪This kitten over here ♪
♪Bar is getting dry
and you staring at the sunrise ♪
♪Bet you're thirsty over there
bet you're thirsty over there ♪
♪'Cause you're an animal, an animal ♪
♪And you're closing in on me ♪
♪You animal ♪
♪Yeah, you're an animal, an animal ♪
♪And it just can't be this way ♪
♪Oh, I can't see straight
and my hands are tied ♪
♪I could be your type
from your zombie bite ♪
♪No, I can't see straight
but the feeling's right...♪
Yo, Dean, can you do me a favor
and take one of these off my hands?
Who is that?
Whoa.
I don't know her personally,
but I'm pretty sure that's JLo.
That's really helpful. Yeah.
I got an idea.
["On the Floor"
by Jennifer Lopez playing]
Oh, my God! Wait, this is me!
Now!
[squeals]
Who says you're struggling
with your assists, huh?
I can still change the song, dick.
♪To my party people in the club ♪
♪Huh ♪
♪If you go hard
you gotta get on the floor ♪
♪If you're a party freak
then step on the floor ♪
♪If you're an animal
then tear up the floor ♪
♪Break a sweat on the floor
yeah, we work on the floor ♪
♪Don't stop, keep it moving
put your drinks up ♪
♪Pick your body up
and drop it on the floor ♪
♪Let the rhythm change
your world on the floor ♪
♪You know we're running shit
tonight on the floor ♪
♪Brazil, Morocco, London to Ibiza ♪
♪Straight to LA, New York,
Vegas to Africa ♪
♪Dance the night away ♪
♪Live your life and stay young
on the floor ♪
♪Dance the night away ♪
♪Grab somebody, drink a little more ♪
♪Tonight we gonna get on the floor ♪
Should we dance or what?
[percussive music playing]
Oh, my God. Justin's here.
Okay, be cool. You're with me.
Hey, he's just another guy.
All right?
[boisterous chatter continues]
Is he looking?
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
What?
Where are we going?
He needs to see us.
And he has. You've got him interested.
Now we've gotta go.
But he's talking to someone.
Hey, watch the player,
not the puck, Wellsy.
What the hell does that mean?
It means trust me.
This is the part...
where I tell you all the things
I want to do to you
when we're alone.
Now...
you can blush.
["OMG" by Suki Waterhouse playing]
Okay.
♪When I got lost in all these dreams ♪
♪See myself, but it's not me ♪
♪I'm with the crowd, I cannot breathe ♪
♪My baby's no good for me ♪
♪No good for me, no--♪
[music stops]
Oh, thank God. I'm exhausted.
Oh!
You're not letting me take the bed?
[sighs]
Nope.
Sorry for thinking you were a gentleman.
Apology accepted.
I'm not sleeping on the floor.
[chuckles]
Well, that really sounds like a pickle.
You can't just decide.
- That's funny, seems like I just did.
- Oh, my God, you're so stubborn.
[laughs]
You know the bed is big enough for two.
Absolutely not.
Okay, your loss.
Whoa.
You're beat to shit.
Am I?
Yeah, I guess I hadn't noticed.
No, okay, you're right.
You should take the bed.
Wait. No.
- No?
- No.
You're just giving me the bed
because you feel bad for me.
Get back on the bed.
I'm taking the floor.
I don't need your pity. It's all yours.
See you in the morning.
You just collapsed on it two seconds ago.
Take it.
I am perfectly capable
of sleeping on the floor.
So am I.
[laughs]
What?
Nothing.
You can't actually laugh out loud
and not share the goods.
[cell phone vibrates]
[whimpering]
[both laugh]
[notifications chime]
[dog panting]
Impressive.
The Bruins should hire him
to be their mascot.
Do you always get so beat up out there?
Ah, you get used to it.
Hurt more when I was starting out.
How old were you?
- When I started playing?
- Mm.
I don't know. As soon as I could walk,
my dad put skates on me.
That's a lot of pressure on a kid.
Skating was the fun part.
The pressure was...
getting measured once a week to make sure
that I was growing fast enough.
Chugging protein shakes and...
lifting weights.
Missing birthday parties
because my dad wouldn't let me
skip practice.
And his fucking whistle
whenever I made a mistake.
Why do you still do it?
I guess...
I wouldn't know who I am without it.
I spent my whole life
training for a dream,
and I'm so close to it.
If I stopped, I...
I don't know.
That makes sense.
Seems like you never really had a choice.
Yeah. Right.
Fuck that.
Yeah.
Yeah. Fuck that.
You got to practice with the Bruins?
They let me run a drill for fun.
It wasn't that big of a deal, you stalker.
♪Page one...♪
Oh, my God, no. Turn that off.
That's so embarrassing.
[laughs]
♪All that's happened ♪
♪Then on ♪
♪To the first chapter ♪
♪Everyone's happy ♪
♪For shadowing impending disaster ♪
♪Then girl meets boy ♪
♪It's awkward, confusing ♪
♪Can't tell if it's love or it's hate ♪
♪Wet hands graze ♪
- ♪Reaching for something...♪
- Did you write this?
It's incredible.
In high school.
♪Now it's a love story ♪
♪Of epic proportion ♪
♪The likes of which never has been told ♪
You're really good.
♪Two hearts beating as one ♪
♪Run right into the sun ♪
♪Oh, what would I give to go back?♪
♪Back to page one ♪
I gotta tell you something.
The other night, at the Eastwood game...
I was...
struggling.
And then...
I heard someone singing.
Elton John.
Right?
I followed your voice
through the tunnels.
[laughs]
I saw you in the green room.
Saying it out loud,
I realize that sounds creepy, but...
[laughs]
...you were so...
like, genuine, you know?
And free.
You centered me.
[cell phone notification chimes]
[sighs]
Jules posted us.
Wait, what did they say?
Actually, hang on, let me see.
[laughs] We did it.
Yeah, we did it.
Wait, I have just the thing.
Have you heard Miley's cover
of "The Bitch Is Back"?
Yeah, of course.
I'm a man of taste, Wellsy.
Okay, well, what about
Billy Porter's version?
Who's Billy Porter?
Gonna pretend you didn't just say that.
Come up here.
[scoffs]
Will you show me something of yours?
What, like a classical piece?
No, like the one on your Instagram.
Uh, no. I--
I don't write like that anymore.
That's crazy.
Why not?
It's like scary...
telling the world something
I'm not ready for it to know.
Uh, but I am working on something
at the moment
for the pop showcase,
but it's not there yet.
Lyrics are hard for me.
It'll get there.
It has to. I need to win.
You hate losing that badly, huh?
I do, when it means that I can't afford
to go to Briar anymore,
which is what'll happen
if I don't get a scholarship.
And the only way to get the scholarship--
Is to win?
Do you have to write the lyrics yourself?
Can you collaborate?
Yeah, sure. As long as it's still mine.
[typing]
[rock music playing onscreen]
♪We built a bridge and burned it down...♪
I mean, there's your answer.
- [laughs] Justin?
- Yeah.
I mean, just ask him for help.
Pretentious douches love that shit.
He is not a pretentious douche.
Okay, yeah. Whatever you say.
♪Constantly concealing ♪
♪What we'll never be ♪
♪So here is the lie you want ♪
♪It tastes much sweeter than...♪
Wait have you heard of the Beaches?
Mm-mm.
Their Coachella set will change your life.
[both laugh]
[typing]
[gentle romantic music playing]
[crickets chirping]
- Oh, we just made it.
- That was close.
[Garrett] Coach.
Hannah.
Hi. Hey.
Justin.
[laughs] Yeah.
This seat taken?
- No.
- Yeah? Cool.
[gentle romantic music continues]
[inaudible]
[inhales sharply]
♪She's a fire sign ♪
♪And I don't really know
what that means ♪
♪I'm a cold night ♪
♪And I wanna be close to the heat ♪
♪I don't want to get burned ♪
♪I don't want love like that ♪
♪But I can't go any further
Till I start coming back ♪
♪I'm a rock star ♪
♪And I'm never around when you need ♪
♪Like a race car ♪
♪Driving away from the scene ♪
♪Does she want me to stay?♪
♪Does she want me to pack?♪
♪You can't push me any further
till I start coming back ♪
♪Turn me around, right upside down ♪
♪Spin me like a globe
and drop your finger on me ♪
♪I feel so far ♪
♪You're all I want ♪
♪Spin me like a globe
and drop your finger on me ♪
♪You push me in circles ♪
♪To the edge of the Earth ♪
♪Where I can't go any further ♪
♪Till I start coming back to you ♪
♪I'm an addict ♪
♪I'm addicted to her into me ♪
♪She's a magnet ♪
♪Pulling me under the sheets ♪
♪If I hold you too close ♪
♪Will the good things still grow?♪
♪Don't matter what happens ♪
♪Wherever we end up
we'll come right back ♪
♪Turn me around ♪
♪Right upside down ♪
♪Spin me like a globe
and drop your finger on me ♪
♪I feel so far ♪
♪You're all I want ♪
♪Spin me like a globe
and drop your finger on me ♪
♪You push me in circles ♪
♪To the edge of the Earth ♪
♪Where I can't go any further ♪
♪Till I start coming back to you ♪
♪Turn me around ♪
♪Right upside down ♪
♪Spin me like a globe ♪
♪And drop your finger on me ♪
♪I feel so far, you're all I want ♪
♪Spin me like a globe ♪
♪And drop your finger on me ♪
♪Turn me around ♪
♪Right upside down ♪
♪Spin me like a globe ♪
♪And drop your finger on me ♪
♪I feel so far, you're all I want ♪
♪Spin me like a globe ♪
♪And drop your finger on me ♪
♪You push me in circles...♪
[playing "Make Me Feel"]
Janelle Monáe?
Yeah, it's just something I do.
It frees me when I'm stuck.
Keep going.
[continues playing]
You make me nervous.
Why is that?
[orchestral music:
"Make Me Feel" by Janelle Monae]
[piano keys plunk]
[breathing heavily]
[orchestral music: "Make Me Feel"
by Janelle Monae continues]
[buzzing sound]
[panting]
- You can do it.
- Yeah.
I know. I know.
I'm going to.
[panting]
[buzzing sound continues]
Are you almost there?
I'm trying.
Keep going. I can do this.
[sighs] I can do this.
[gasps]
Can you?
[buzzing sound intensifies]
[sighs]
[orchestral music: "Make Me Feel"
by Janelle Monae continues]
[cell phone ringing]
Wellsy!
Hey, I'm on my way to you right now.
Got my flash cards and everything.
Uh, actually, about that.
Uh, I know we're down to the wire,
and I promise I'll have you ready
for Tolbert tomorrow.
- But...
- But?
But I can't meet right now,
because I have my first
songwriting session with Justin.
I asked him for help
with my showcase song, like you said.
And-- And he went for it.
Hello?
Did I-- Did I lose you?
- I'm here.
- Okay, are you keeping up?
I'm calling to say you were right.
That's usually where you hit me
with some arrogant reply.
What can I say?
I know my pretentious douches.
There he is.
Okay, anyway, it's impossible
to get a rehearsal space last minute,
but I got one.
So, I have to push tutoring to later.
- Five-ish?
- Sure.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, why?
Because you're speaking
in two- and three-word sentences.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Wellsy, I am thrilled beyond words
that we have accomplished this key step
in Project Lover Boy,
and you are on the road to getting laid.
Excuse me, that's not what this is about.
[scoffs]
Justin is not just some random guy
I want to hook up with.
He is a talented musician who I respect.
And also want to hook up with.
[laughs] Well, yeah.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I'm so nervous.
[exhales]
You're overthinking.
Get out of your head.
You know your shit. Just do you.
Yeah, right. Me.
And by the way,
he may not know it yet,
but you're the real catch.
So, act like it.
Thanks, coach.
Okay, gotta go.
[up-tempo music]
♪Don't worry 'bout the past...♪
Point. One point. Come on.
Come on!
Bullshit.
[air hockey puck clicking]
- Yes!
- No.
- I win.
Dean Di Laurentis, everyone.
Losing to a girl.
- Sexist.
- How is that sexist?
She is not a girl.
She's a person in a girl's body.
Aw, Dean.
Neanderthals can evolve.
- Sorry.
- You're good.
G, this is Lexi's friend, Zoe.
Zoe? Ahem! Zoe.
Two out of three, okay?
Let's go. Let's go.
Dean. Dean, chill.
Garrett needs to study.
Oh, and I need to live, okay?
This is a living room.
Hey, Dean, Garrett's benched if he doesn't
pass this thing, and then he's fucked.
- Then your whole line is fucked.
- And the season's fucked.
I can't be the number one fan
of a shitty team.
That's so embarrassing.
- Right, guys, I'm trying here.
- Brain fuel flying in, Cap.
We got you.
High in omega-3s,
carb-forward, no keto bullshit.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
- What is that?
- More liquid IV.
I thought you passed on the sponsorship.
Yeah, I did. They DM'ed my dad
some happy family marketing angle.
They want me to do
the whole thing with him.
Wait, sorry, that's it?
- How much money'd you leave on the table?
- Does it matter? It's his business.
Y'all, he's trying to study.
Trust me, no amount of money is worth it.
Yeah, that's why Taco Shack
is the ideal sponsorship.
No strings attached, just carne asada.
[Jules] All I'm saying is cash
is better than tacos.
- Unless you don't need the cash, I guess.
- [Logan] Jules!
What? He knows he's a nepo.
Okay, you know what?
I need to focus. Jeez.
No.
Seriously, dude?
Think he's coming back for that?
I-I mean, it's--
It's just a start, what I have.
It's rough, still.
Might totally suck.
It might suck. It might not.
It's a-- It's a process.
Yeah.
[repeats musical phrase]
Yeah, I like this phrase here.
- You do?
- Yeah.
These, are these lyrics?
No. Uh...
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
They're my attempts.
Um, I haven't written lyrics
since high school.
Okay. Can you sing it for me?
Oh, no, I'm-- I'm not a singer. Sorry.
Well, I, um...
I can't read your handwriting.
You know what? That-- That might be fine.
- [both laugh]
- Okay. Uh...
Um...
Why don't you-- Why don't you tell me
what you think the song's about?
Yeah, yeah, sure. Um...
Uh, well, it's a love song, I think.
Um, kind of wanted to use
the cello here like a guitar.
Kind of like
a George Harrison vibe, right?
Um, like a counterpoint to the vocals.
Like they're having a conversation.
Uh, sorry, but the lyrics could be about,
like, being in love with someone
who doesn't see you.
And the cello's like, "Hey, I see you.
I'm into you," you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, um, I get where you're circling.
Really?
Mm.
Hey, can I-- Can I borrow this?
Mess around with it a bit?
Yes, please. Of course, take it.
- Sweet.
[laughs]
Your life is about to change.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Well, I think my life's about to change,
hence, ergo, therefore.
- You ready for life changing?
- [laughs] Okay.
[sighs] You remember that agent
I told you about?
The one that reps Briar Youth Theater
legend Joanna Maxwell?
Mm-hmm.
Well, he came to see
Our Town a couple weeks ago,
and he wants to sign me.
Oh, wow, that's great.
It is! Like it really, really is.
His agency has offices all over the place,
so this could mean film and TV work in LA,
like stage work in New York.
Like, this is everything.
Everything.
What happened to Vermont?
I thought you'd join me there
after you graduate.
My family, my dad's insurance company?
Vermont was summer.
Vermont was the plan.
Vermont was your plan.
Maybe I have different plans.
It's just...
what are the odds?
What do you mean?
I mean, what are the odds
of you actually making it?
In Vermont,
we can build a life together.
- Yeah.
- A great life that's stable and secure.
Oh, yeah, and that is a great life.
- But I--
- And you can still act.
You can do all
the summer stock you want.
You'll basically always get the lead,
which I know you love.
Okay, and what about fall and winter?
Spring?
I guess I just thought
you'd outgrow all this.
Wow.
I didn't mean it like that, Allie.
I meant...
Look, I'm-- I'm getting cold.
Can we talk about this later?
Are you done?
No, I'm not.
Hey, you don't have to lock it.
You can just leave it on the porch.
Or actually, you know what?
I can leave it on the porch.
Hi. Thanks.
[Logan] All right.
What happened to your Subaru?
Oh, my Bluebaru.
[laughs]
How do you know about that?
I fixed it.
Freshman year, you brought it
to my family's garage just off Route 6.
That was you?
That was me. Yeah.
I-I loved that car.
Tragically, she died.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
No, no, you gave my Bluebaru
six more months of life.
I had her my whole freshman year.
That was huge.
Well, if your bike ever needs a tune-up,
I'm your guy.
[laughs] Okay.
No, I'm-I'm serious.
I kind of made a little business
out of fixing things,
doing handyman work,
whatever I can get around campus.
I'm actually currently on my way
to hang Professor Walden's
new widescreen TV for $25 an hour.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
I'm rolling in it.
Well, I'm holding down three jobs
at the moment for...
wait for it...
minimum wage.
Damn! Where's the Bentley?
I love riding my bike.
Keeps me grounded, you know?
Really? Good for you. I'm proud of you.
You're a hockey player.
I thought all you guys got free rides.
Yeah, well, scholarship money
only goes so far.
Can't all be Garrett Graham, right?
[both chuckle]
Anyway, he is studying in his room.
It's the last door on--
On the left. I know.
Right.
All right. Bye.
[door closes]
["Cherry Pie" by Warrant
plays faintly on stereo]
♪Cool drink of water
Such a sweet surprise ♪
♪Tastes so good
Make a grown man cry ♪
♪Sweet cherry pie...♪
Garrett?
Garrett!
Not sure how "Cherry Pie" is gonna be--
- [moaning]
- Oh, my God!
♪Sweet cherry pie ♪
[Garrett] Hannah, wait.
[Hannah] You know, locking the door
is a thing that people do.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay, you know,
I plan these sessions for you,
and you're always distracted.
You're at the gym curling or pressing
or whatever, or sexting, or...
Fuck! Actually having sex.
Which, by the way,
kind of blows up our entire story.
- No, it doesn't.
- Yeah, it does.
We're supposed to be a couple.
Yeah, but we're not exclusive.
We talked about this.
Well, I know that nobody would believe
that Mr. I Don't Do Girlfriends
would actually have a girlfriend.
That's not the point.
The point is that you're not
taking us, this, seriously.
Yes, I am. I was studying.
Yeah, studying what, exactly?
Okay, no. Actually, don't.
Don't answer that.
Zoe offered to help, you know,
take my mind off of things.
- Loosen up a little bit.
- Oh, my God.
- Please stop.
- You changed the study time.
Yeah, I changed it to now.
And you agreed.
Okay, hold on. Wait.
[sighs]
Okay, I'm sorry.
I want to learn this.
I do. I...
I don't get how there can be
two truths.
Like, shit's either true, or it's not.
Subjective, objective.
I mean, what the fuck, Kierkegaard?
Okay, he believed that people needed
to define truths for themselves.
Like, believing in God.
See, this is why I need you.
That actually makes sense.
Yeah, what can I say?
I know my pretentious philosophers.
[laughs]
Okay, look.
I messed up.
Can you please come back inside?
Tucker made salmon.
We can eat, study...
Okay, you have a naked woman in your room.
Oh.
- Shit, I do.
- [cell phone chimes]
Uh, that's okay.
Just give me five minutes.
- What?
- Uh...
Justin has some thoughts
about the song.
All right, well, what about studying?
I'll send you a video on Kierkegaard
that explains everything, okay?
And I'll meet you tomorrow before class.
With your clothes on!
[plays gentle tune]
♪Silent as the eagle strikes ♪
♪In a cold and lonely world ♪
♪Alone enough for me to ask this ♪
♪Alone enough to fear the hurt ♪
And then the cello part
you wrote for the pre
actually worked great as a vocal melody.
Then, I added another section
before the call and response.
Like, um--
♪What was it all for?♪
♪Hello, hello, pain ♪
♪Sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Yellow, yellow ♪
And then your cello part.
[hums]
♪Yellow, yellow ♪
Something like that.
You-- You just came up with that?
That's your melody.
I just, um...
Just gave it words.
Do-- Do you like it?
Yeah. Yeah, I-I do. I-I really, really do.
I mean, I thought you would. I'm just...
Yeah, I'm really glad you like it.
[both laugh]
Shit, sorry. Damn.
Do you always record yourself?
Well, you never know
when inspiration might strike.
Like, if you see me around campus
with my phone in the air,
it's because I'm recording.
Like, the sound of the wind
or trees rustling.
Or the ceramic clinking at Malone's.
Such a specific sound.
- Such a specific sound, yeah.
- [laughs]
And then, you use it?
Yeah, sometimes.
Usually, like, really deep in the mix
when I'm trying to change things up.
Ben Folds does it, too,
and Sharon Van Etten.
- Like Billie Eilish and Finneas.
- Yeah, yeah, exactly.
[laughing]
Yeah.
Uh...
Let me, um, send you this file,
and we can riff on it.
Are you a Pro Tools or a Logic girl?
Logic. All the way.
[laughs] Okay.
Sick.
Uh...
Uh, let me actually just...
Shit, it's, um, it's 7.30.
I've gotta...
I gotta go.
- Okay, yeah. Yeah, no problem.
- Yeah.
I'll see you later.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Cool.
Ciao.
Fuck.
["Scatterbrain" by Emei playing]
[exhales]
♪Dun, dun-dun, dun, dun-dun ♪
♪All right, got a lot of friends
That I can't escape ♪
♪Sleeping in my head like a Motel 6♪
♪Hold it all together
With a little duct tape ♪
♪It bends, it breaks ♪
♪Got a lot of dreams
But I let them die ♪
♪Ping-pong, drip-drop, oh my, my ♪
♪The TV's on, but the noise is white ♪
♪What am I doing now?♪
♪God, can I catch my breath ♪
♪Not even for a second?♪
♪Chasing Santa Ana winds ♪
♪And I obsess ♪
♪I slow-dance with the tension ♪
♪Can you taste it on my lips?♪
♪I'm so scatterbrained ♪
♪For a second, I don't feel the same ♪
♪Come medicate me ♪
♪I don't sleep at all, yeah ♪
♪I've been counting sheep ♪
♪I look perfect on the surface
But a nightmare underneath ♪
♪I've got anger problems
I say things that I don't mean ♪
♪Some people pay for therapy ♪
♪I find it in the sheets ♪
[sighs]
[exhales]
Here, let me send you this file,
and we can riff on it.
Uh, we could.
Or...
Or?
♪Baby, don't make me
Spell it out for you ♪
♪All of the feelings
That I've got for you ♪
♪Can't be explained
But I can try for you ♪
♪Baby, don't make me
Spell it out for you ♪
♪You keep on asking me
The same questions ♪
♪Why?♪
♪And second-guessing
All my intentions ♪
♪Should know by the way
I use my compression ♪
♪That you got the answers
To my confessions ♪
♪It's like I'm powerful
With a little bit of tender ♪
♪An emotional sexual bender ♪
♪Mess me up, yeah
But no one does it better ♪
♪There's nothing better ♪
♪That's just the way you make me feel ♪
♪Just the way you make me feel ♪
♪The way you make me feel ♪
♪So good, so good, so fucking real ♪
♪Uh-huh ♪
♪That's just the way you make me feel ♪
Please.
♪The way you make me feel ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪That's just the way you make me feel ♪
What do you want, Wellsy?
Wellsy. Wellsy?
S-Sorry, yes? What?
What if she picks Kierkegaard?
I still don't get the two truths thing.
- I'm so screwed if I get him.
- No, you're not.
You know everything on these cards.
I promise.
What if I forget or something, you know?
I mean, Tolbert kind of intimidates
the fuck out of me.
Okay, well, pretend she's a defenseman
from Eastwood coming at you, okay?
What would you do?
Skate away.
Hockey's easy.
Okay, well, if you forget,
just look at me.
Okay? Convince me.
Isn't this fun?
Huh?
Kierkegaard.
- Shit.
Okay, Mr. Graham.
Your topic is ghosting.
Would Kierkegaard argue ghosting
is moral or immoral, and why?
Uh, Kierkegaard would argue
that ghosting someone is immoral,
uh, because it is, like, um...
you know, really wrong
to do to somebody morally.
You've got this.
You know, ghosting
might sound like no big deal,
but Kierkegaard would say,
not only is it harmful to the victim,
it is an absolute abdication of selfhood.
Ahem.
While an objective truth
is supported by facts,
Kierkegaard believed
that, as individuals,
we have a shared moral responsibility
to be honest
based on our own
subjective definition of truth.
To suddenly disappear from someone's life
without an explanation is basically
like discarding their humanity.
Ghosting is choosing comfort over courage,
despair over strength.
It is labeling another human being
as unworthy.
And as Kierkegaard himself said,
"Once you label me,
you fucking negate me."
[laughter]
Uh, I'm paraphrasing.
[chuckles nervously]
- [Garrett] Ah!
- [Hannah laughing]
- We did it! A fucking B!
- Plus!
- Don't forget the plus.
- B-plus?
Yeah, you are officially
a professional bullshitter.
- Thanks to you.
- Oh!
Um...
What do you want, Wellsy?
You can put me down now.
We know how much you can bench.
Shit.
I think Justin saw me.
Uh, yeah, he just waved at you, crazy.
He's walking away now.
What's going on?
So embarrassing.
I think he saw my Justin Kohl playlist.
You have a Justin Kohl playlist?
Okay, don't make it worse.
Are we talking, like,
songs that remind you of him,
or his band stuff?
His band stuff.
And some solo stuff from high school.
Wow, you went down
the fangirl rabbit hole.
- Hard.
- That is the exact opposite
of everything we've been working on.
- Yeah, I know.
- [cell phone chimes]
Oh, my God.
He wants to know if I'm good.
What should I say? Am I good?
- Nope.
- What are you doing?
You're not gonna respond. Say nothing.
What?
Hey, fangirl.
Start thinking like a fuckboy.
- Ghost his ass.
- Wait.
Didn't you just give a whole impassioned
argument about how ghosting is immoral?
That it's an abdication of selfhood?
That was to get me the grade.
This is to get you the guy.
You want that, right?
[heartbeat thumps]
- Yeah, I do.
- All right.
Well, then, you're stuck with me
because we've only finished half the deal.
And, uh, oh, shit.
Haven't I been completely right
about everything so far?
You are intolerable.
So, you are not going to text Justin.
You are going to put your phone away
and come to Malone's
with me and the guys tonight.
- Tonight?
- You're not working, are you?
- No.
- Okay, so you're coming.
- To Malone's?
- Yes.
- With all the guys?
- We've established this.
- Garrett.
- Hannah.
- Do you know what tonight is?
- Hell yeah, I do.
So, you're going to karaoke night
with Garrett Graham?
And the rest of the team. And you.
If you're free.
Maybe.
Oh.
Oh! My slut top.
Take it.
From my boobs to yours.
What do you mean maybe?
I might stay in.
Stay in?
Allie, you didn't even stay in last year
when you sprained your ankle.
- You bedazzled your boot.
- Yeah.
Just feeling a little meh.
What's going on?
I told Sean I got an agent,
and he got all like,
"But what about the real world, babe?"
I'm sorry, you got a what?
Oh, yeah. No, I got an agent.
- Yay.
- Oh, my God!
You let me go on about my shit
when you have news like that?
Allie, this is everything.
Every fucking thing.
Oh, yeah. It, like, is everything, right?
[gasps]
You're the best.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay, screw him.
You're coming out with me,
and we're celebrating you.
I don't know.
It's karaoke night.
You really gonna rob the people
of your talent?
[sighs]
[singing poorly]
♪Take me for what I am ♪
♪Who I was meant to be ♪
♪And if you give a damn ♪
♪Take me, baby ♪
♪Or leave me ♪
Whoo!
- [Garrett] Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
- She's really going at it.
- Yeah, the stage is her happy place.
Hey, who's next?
Someone, please, save us
from Adele Dazeem up there.
[laughs]
♪Lose your head ♪
♪'Cause every night, who's in your bed?♪
Whoo!
Wellsy, what you singing?
- Nothing.
- Come on, it's karaoke.
Yeah, well, sober karaoke's no fun.
I'm sober, too.
Game tomorrow.
- Yeah, and what are you singing?
- I don't know.
The guys will pull me up for something.
I'm good, thanks.
- [laughs]
- All right.
♪What's my sin?
Never quit, I follow through ♪
♪I hate mess but I love you ♪
♪What to do with my impromptu baby ♪
♪So be wise 'cause this girl satisfies...♪
You know, you don't have to be sober
if you don't want to be.
- Yeah, well, I don't--
- [Garrett] Drink in public.
No, I know.
But do you want to?
- Want to what?
- Drink.
- I told Allie...
- I will look after Allie.
She's a no-filter drunk.
Gotta rein her in.
I can handle her.
And I will guard your drinks with my life.
I got you, Wellsy.
Do you trust me?
Yeah. Yeah, I-I do.
Okay, uh, I will have a drink.
A "drink" drink.
And what is your "drink" drink of choice?
I don't know.
Well, that is a fun problem to solve.
[upbeat electronic music playing]
Oh.
[shudders]
I think we found your "drink" drink.
Yummy!
[Hannah giggles]
He thought I would outgrow acting.
[scoffs] Like, dude,
I would love to be
ER nurse number two with half a line.
Jon Hamm had one scene in Gilmore Girls.
I know, he's the Mad Man.
I'm like, I get it.
There's no guarantee that I'll make it.
But isn't that kind of
what's exciting about it?
Like, that's why they call it a dream.
But I do love him.
You know? And...
And I know he loves me.
And...
Like, we're supposed to be together.
Oh, God, we've broken up
and gotten back together so many times.
It's, like, insane.
I mean, that's gotta
mean something, right?
That we keep getting back together.
My mom always used to tell me,
"Never give up on love."
Well, that and, "Love your body,"
which I do.
[woman] My mom said the same thing!
Oh, my God, really?
Wait, hold on,
the love thing or the body thing?
[toilet flushes]
Hang in there, girl.
[tap water runs]
[seductive music playing]
JLo.
Maverick.
I've got a boyfriend, you know.
Yeah, no, I heard.
Along with the rest of the ladies' room.
Doesn't sound like
he's gonna last long, though.
Okay, this is supposed to be,
like, a sacred space.
Who the hell hooks up
in the ladies' bathroom, anyway?
Sorry. Not you.
You're a sweetheart.
And you're disgusting.
♪Well, I walk into the room ♪
♪Passing out hundred-dollar bills ♪
♪And it kills and it thrills
Like the horns on my Silverado grill ♪
♪And I buy the bar
A double round of Crown ♪
♪And everybody's getting down ♪
♪And this town
Ain't never gonna be the same ♪
♪'Cause I saddle up my horse ♪
♪And I ride into the city ♪
♪I make a lot of noise ♪
- ♪'Cause the girls, they are so pretty ♪
- No way.
♪Riding up and down Broadway
On my old stud Leroy ♪
♪And the girls say ♪
[all]
♪"Save a horse, ride a cowboy"...♪
Good, you're here.
I'll put you and Garrett down
for "Summer Nights."
I know that's a joke,
but I would kill Sandy.
[Jules] I wasn't sold on them at first,
but I can see it now.
Yeah. Sure.
- Hey.
- Oh, Logan!
You fixed my car.
He fixed my car.
You have a car?
No.
Had a car. A great car.
I'm buying you a very special
thank-you drink.
[inaudible]
[laughing] Okay, you're gonna love it.
Hannah has discovered
the piña colada tonight.
- Ooh!
- I only had one...
or four.
Is that what I'm getting, too?
Nope.
For my mechanic,
I call this the Bluebaru.
- See?
- Wow.
That looks like wiper fluid.
That might actually be wiper fluid.
It's mostly blue curaçao
with a secret ingredient.
More blue curaçao.
Oh!
I'm so excited. I can't wait.
- Hey, G.
- What's up?
I brought you something.
I thought you were looking
a little parched.
I know. Nepo babies have feelings, too.
Sorry if I was an asshole.
- You're always an asshole.
- Fair.
[Garrett] Here goes.
[Tucker continues singing]
♪Everybody say ♪
[all]
♪"Save a horse, ride a cowboy"♪
They just keep sending you those for free?
- Yeah, they still want him.
- [Garrett] They want my dad.
Wait, you guys should just do it together.
I mean, look at you. Best friends.
All right, maybe we'll slow down
on the piña coladas a little.
[Hannah] No, I mean it. Screw your dad.
Do it with Logan.
You could be teammates
spotting each other at the gym.
Or besties wingmanning
each other at the bar.
- Besties.
Am I drunk, or is she brilliant?
No, I'm drunk, and you're brilliant.
And I'm brilliant, too.
It's not a bad idea.
Thanks, man, but I don't need the charity.
Yeah, you do.
I mean, seriously.
Nobody wants to see
Oldie McOldsfuck has-been, okay?
What's better than
two hot young hockey players?
Three hot young hockey players?
[all] Yeah!
[laughing]
Hannah Wells.
You're up, bitch.
Whoo!
All right, hold on.
Wait, I thought you weren't singing.
That was before I found the perfect song.
[background vocalists]
♪Dirty, rotten, filthy, stinking ♪
Oh, shit, Graham.
You know this one?
♪She's my cherry pie ♪
♪Cool drink of water
Such a sweet surprise ♪
♪Tastes so good, make a grown man cry ♪
♪Sweet cherry pie ♪
Whoo!
[all cheering]
♪Listen ♪
♪Well, swinging on the front porch
Swinging on the lawn ♪
♪Swinging where we want
'Cause there ain't nobody home ♪
♪Swinging to the left
And swinging to the right ♪
♪Think about hockey, I swing all night ♪
♪Yeah ♪
♪Come on ♪
♪Swinging in the living room
Swinging in the kitchen ♪
♪Most folks don't
'Cause they're too busy bitchin'♪
♪Swinging in there
'Cause she wanted me to feed her ♪
♪So I mixed up the batter
And she licked the beater ♪
♪I scream, you scream
We all scream for her ♪
♪But don't even try
'Cause you can't ignore her ♪
[background vocals]
♪She's my cherry pie ♪
♪Such a sweet surprise ♪
♪She make a grown man ♪
Whoo!
♪She's my cherry pie ♪
♪Put a smile on your face
ten miles wide ♪
♪Looks so good, bring a tear to your eye ♪
♪Sweet cherry pie ♪
♪I, I, yeah ♪
♪Swing it ♪
♪All night long...♪
Kind of sweet, isn't it?
Seeing Garrett being serious
about someone.
Do you think he's serious?
Everyone on Fifth Line seems to think so.
They get more likes
than anything else I post.
♪Swinging in the bathroom
Swinging on the floor ♪
♪Swinging so hard
Forgot to lock the door ♪
♪In walked her daddy
Standing six foot four ♪
♪Said, "You ain't gonna swing
With my daughter no more"♪
♪She's my cherry pie ♪
♪Such a sweet surprise ♪
♪She make a grown man ♪
Whoo!
♪She's my cherry pie ♪
♪Put a smile on your face ten miles wide ♪
♪Looks so good, bring a tear to your eye ♪
♪Sweet cherry pie ♪
[cheers and applause]
[Hannah] Swingin'.
[laughs]
[both laugh]
You did good, Wellsy.
Thank you.
[both chuckle]
[turn signal clicks]
[vent air blowing]
[turns vent off]
[inhales deeply]
[clears throat]
You guys, I forgot my purse at the bar.
Your purse with my wallet and keys in it?
- We gotta go back.
- It's closed.
Well, what now?
Next party?
[both laugh]
Night, night.
Wellsy?
["Hope Is a Scary Thing"
by Carol Ades playing]
Wellsy?
♪Back of my mind, back of my mind ♪
♪I'm a little scared, I'm a little wired ♪
♪I don't wanna put my foot down
Right now and stop it all happening ♪
♪Back of my mind, back of my head ♪
♪You look really nice, wanna share a bed?♪
♪I don't wanna put my foot down
Right now, but it's happening ♪
♪Don't kiss me ♪
♪'Cause I might end up on the ceiling ♪
♪Way too high to ever
Come down to reality ♪
♪Back to my sanity ♪
♪Guess it's too late for that now ♪
♪Hope is a scary thing ♪
♪I'm flying on temporary wings ♪
I found something to sleep in.
I can see that.
Whoa, whoa.
But I'm a fuck bunny.
A puck funny.
[laughing] No, no.
A fuck bunny. That's it.
You're a drunk bunny.
Come here.
[laughs] Come here.
A fake relationship means
we can fake sleep together.
I don't think it's a great idea.
I actually think it's my best idea.
Well...
[inhales sharply]
Go to sleep, Wellsy.
Hey, you're not gonna remember
any of this in the morning.
[cell phone chimes and vibrates]
Oh, my God.
[upbeat music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
- Can you?
[upbeat music ends]
[door closes]
[breathing deeply]
[sniffles]
Coffee?
Oh, uh...
Thanks.
Morning.
You were pretty drunk last night.
How much do you remember?
All of it.
You tried to have sex with me.
Yeah, I-I know.
And now, you're bringing me coffee.
Yep.
Okay, are you 100% awake?
Because there's something really important
that I need you to do for me.
Oh.
Okay.
I need you to give me an orgasm.
["Underestimate Me"
by Chloe Lilac playing]
♪Uh-oh ♪
♪Oh, no ♪
♪I think I'm losing all my self-control ♪
♪If you stay, I should go ♪
♪But if you don't
I think I'll risk it all ♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪No, no ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪Don't underestimate me ♪
♪I can change your life ♪
♪ My friends say fixing you ♪
♪Is just a waste of time ♪
♪Waste of time ♪
♪Call me dear sentimental ♪
♪Kiss me at the bar ♪
♪At the bar ♪
♪Think I'm the happiest ♪
♪When I'm within your arms ♪
♪I mean, I don't even know
what to say at this point ♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪Oh, no ♪
♪I think I'm losing all my self-control ♪
- ♪If you stay ♪
- ♪Stay ♪
- ♪I should go ♪
- ♪Go ♪
♪But if you don't
I think I'll risk it all ♪
♪Give you a reason to live ♪
♪Baby, I think it's for the win ♪
♪Cut all ties with the old ♪
♪And I'll give you something to miss ♪
♪When the good gets harder to hold ♪
♪Throw it all to the wind ♪
♪For the win, for the win, for the win ♪
♪Don't underestimate me ♪
♪I'm losing my control ♪
♪Oh-oh, oh, no ♪
♪I think I'm losing all my self-control ♪
- ♪If you say ♪
- ♪Say ♪
- ♪I should go ♪
- ♪Go ♪
♪But if you don't ♪
♪I think I'll risk it all ♪
Uh...
Did you just say...
you want me to give you a...
Orgasm? Yeah, God, why is it so hard
for boys to say "orgasm"?
It's-It's not hard for me to say "orgasm".
I can say "orgasm".
Orgasm.
See?
Just-- are you still drunk?
Okay, yeah, uh, let's-- let's do this.
Uh...
I'm gonna tell you something really heavy,
and you're gonna want to dwell on it,
but you shouldn't.
I'm just telling you the bad stuff
so that you can understand my request.
Okay?
It's just a means to an end.
A means to an end.
Got it.
I was raped.
Wow, okay, there's really no way to make
that seem less heavy than it is.
Uh, it happened in high school.
I was drugged at a party.
That's why I don't like
drinking in public.
- Oh, shit.
- No, no! See?
What you're doing right now is dwelling.
And I need you to just breeze
past this part, okay?
Focus up, Graham. Are you breezing?
- Uh, yeah, I'm breezing, I'm breezing.
- Okay.
I'm fine. Really, I'm okay.
I had a lovely therapist.
Her name was Carol.
She had these mismatched mugs
and a really extensive tea collection.
She helped me understand
that the rape doesn't define me.
Even though I firmly put this behind me,
I still can't seem to...
you know, orgasm with a guy.
I mean, on my own, sure, fine, fireworks.
But, yeah, not-- not with someone else.
And things are going
really well with Justin.
He texted me saying that his roommates
will be gone later,
and we all know what that means.
I-I-I'm just really nervous
about hooking up with him.
I want to be ready, so I was thinking
if I can finish with someone,
you know, lower stakes first.
Lower stakes?
A friend. That I'd feel
more prepared for Justin.
So...
Yeah, wh-what do you think?
Wow, okay, yeah, that was a lot. Sorry.
Um, I'm kind of out of practice
telling people about this.
No one at Briar knows.
Not even Allie?
Just you.
Wow.
Yeah.
Look.
I promise that I have worked so hard
to move past this.
Okay? I'm not fragile.
I don't need your pity.
I don't need you to be my therapist.
I just need you to do
this one last thing for me.
Okay, a thing you have done
for many, many,
many, many women.
- Yeah, it's just...
- A means to an end.
Exactly.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Really?
- You will?
- Of course.
You're my friend and you need me.
- Did you mean now?
- No, no!
Not now. I have class.
[laughs]
Um...
Uh, later?
Tonight?
Tonight it is.
[chuckles]
[upbeat rock music playing]
I don't understand.
Sweet, sweet Tuck.
Can I just be the first to say
how thrilled we are
that you decided to pledge Sig Tau?
We welcome you to our brotherhood,
sweet Tuck.
- Okay.
- And as your future big,
it is my pleasure nay, my honor,
to haze you.
And all I ask is that you take care
of that one little grape.
Until I ask you to stop.
- That's it?
- That's it, bud.
It's so simple.
[Tucker] Yeah, I can do that.
Guys, I gotta be honest.
I was a little worried you were gonna make
me streak across campus or frost my tips.
[both] No!
Hey, I'm gonna be your big brother.
Would your brother
do something like that to you?
- I guess not, man.
- Yeah, okay.
Yeah. Well, uh, thanks, y'all.
- This is gonna be really good.
- Well, just one last thing.
Should anything happen to your fruit baby,
it will be replaced
by a slightly larger piece of fruit.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
- Yup.
- Mm, it's a good one.
Good luck, sweet Tuck.
This is the part where you run.
[Tucker] Okay.
Come on.
[Justin, on recording]
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Yellow, yellow ♪
Intrigue.
This is much stronger
than what you brought to class.
But I'm concerned
I'm not really hearing you in this.
Well, they're Justin's words,
but I'm gonna arrange the crap out of it.
I'm thinking strings, like a shifting
chromatic alteration verse to verse.
I'm gonna just jump back in here before
this conversation gets away from me.
Uh, let's try...
Do you have a favorite song,
something you love to listen to
when you're sad or bored?
Ah, see?
What you just did.
Your whole body relaxed.
Now, were you thinking
of specific chord progressions?
No, I was thinking about listening
to Paramore at my middle school bus stop.
Made me feel so complicated and punk rock.
Exactly. How it made you feel.
You see, people think
that pop music is shallow,
but it lives deep inside us.
It creates memories.
It etches them into our bones.
If you do it right, it lets us feel what
you were feeling when you're writing it.
That's what the judges want.
You gotta let us in.
Wow. That was really good advice.
I know. I should be a teacher.
[Hannah laughs]
And I knew it was a dream
because my childhood dog Rosie was there.
But--But she was like
dark brown instead of tan.
I think we should break up.
[scoffs] Okay.
Wait, sorry, what?
"Okay"?
I just ended a two-year relationship.
I mean, maybe you did.
Also, maybe not.
No, I definitely did because I was there
and it was three seconds ago.
- How many times are you gonna do this?
- Do what? What are you talking about?
Your whole
"Allie's breakup in five acts" cycle.
You go through the same stages every time.
First, "Surprise Fight Allie",
which I can safely say we're in right now.
Then, "Eats Her Feelings Allie",
destroys three bags of hot Cheetos,
followed by "Raging Diva Allie".
Stop titling things like they happen.
These are not things that happen.
Then "Complete and Total Breakdown Allie"
has a...
Well, that one's self-explanatory.
And the grand finale,
"Late Night Phone Call Allie",
where you beg me to take you back.
- That is not what I do!
- That is exactly what you do.
I know you better than anyone else
in the world, Al.
I know you're secretly scared of cats.
I know that you're out of ChapStick.
Speaking of which...
I stopped by CVS on the way over.
And I know that you love me.
And I love you.
So, that is why I need to protect myself
by opting out of the next 36 hours.
No, our breakup is not
an extended warranty, Sean.
You can't just opt out.
Well, the alternative
is that I get angry or sad
or beg you not to make this mistake again.
But you will because you always do.
And I disappear into some sad hole
of video games and depression
and ultimately take you back because
I can't imagine my life without you.
It's not fair to me, Al.
Sean, I need you to hear me.
I'm sorry if I've hurt you before.
But this is it.
We're just going in different directions.
And I don't even know
what direction I'm going in,
but I'm going there by myself.
I'm not going to call you.
Okay. [scoffs]
And I'm not out of ChapStick!
Yes, you are.
See you in 36 hours.
[heavy rock song playing]
[Garrett groans]
Shit.
What's wrong, G?
Can't rock a measly 205 anymore?
No, yeah, I'm...
Oh, thanks.
I'm fucking with you, Graham.
I know.
Right.
Okay, what's going on?
Look, Dean, you're, uh...
You're kind of, well...
[chuckles]
You've been with a good amount of women.
I always knew this day would come.
Well, Garrett, when a man and a woman
love each other very much--
- All right, fuck it. Forget it.
- Okay, hold up, hold up. I'm listening.
Is there something going on with Hannah?
No.
Uh...
not Hannah, someone else.
She wants me to do this, uh...
This thing.
Do all the things, bro.
Do them all.
It's just...
It's kind of a big... thing.
It's really important to her.
- She's, like, trusting me.
- G, is Hannah a virgin?
What? No.
Dude, don't...
Don't-- Don't make this weird.
[chuckles]
This doesn't leave the weight room.
We're not having this conversation.
It's just that I really want it
to be good for her.
If it's her first time,
she might not come.
- Not an option. She has to come.
- Respect.
Well, there is one thing
that helps make a girl come.
The single, most effective,
highly recommended,
enjoyed-by-all tool at your disposal.
Trust.
That's it.
She's just got to feel completely safe.
Like, completely relaxed.
But consent is key.
And she can't consent
if she doesn't feel safe.
So you just-- you just gotta figure out
whatever makes this...
specific girl who is not Hannah feel safe.
Yeah, I'm just...
not sure I'm the kind of guy
she should be trusting with this.
Well, if she asked you,
she thinks you are.
Which is fucking hot.
Just don't skimp on the foreplay.
Yeah.
Talking five-play, six-play...
- Yeah, got it.
- You know? Right?
- Thanks.
- Good talk, man. Great talk.
Sorry. I was, uh...
- Justin. Hi.
- Hi. Yeah.
There's easier ways to get my attention.
Sorry, yeah, I was just on my phone.
I'm taking the piss, don't worry about it.
- [laughs] Yeah.
- Yeah.
My advisor really likes the song, mostly.
- Okay, yeah. Mostly?
- Yeah.
He has some notes, but it's getting there.
Cool.
You never replied to my text.
Do you want to come over later
and work on the song?
Uh...
definitely yes.
But, uh, there's just one last thing
I need to iron out before we dive into it.
Rain check?
Rain check, yeah.
Yeah, I'm really looking forward to it.
- Cool.
- [both laugh]
Yeah.
Yeah, bye, I guess.
Bye. Bye.
[laughing]
♪You're scared of heights, that's vertigo ♪
♪You wanted lights, go see a show ♪
♪You ran away, that's touch and go ♪
♪You're scared of love
well, aren't we all?♪
♪Well, aren't we all?♪
♪I know that you started to feel
what I feel...♪
Hey.
♪...my hand by the wheel ♪
♪But you couldn't dare to make it real ♪
♪Oh, it's such a shame...♪
- Is that dress...?
- Allie's.
Yeah.
Um...
We did say 7:00, right?
Yeah.
Uh, come on up.
♪You wanted lights, go see a show ♪
♪You ran away, that's touch and go ♪
♪You're scared of love
well, aren't we all?♪
♪Well, aren't we all?♪
Would you be, um,
more comfortable wearing...
literally anything else?
Maybe. [chuckles]
Think fast.
[laughs]
Uh, you don't need to turn around.
You're about to see me naked.
Yeah, but not until you want me to.
Uh, all clear.
[chuckling] Are nightgowns my thing now?
Definitely.
Uh...
so are we gonna...
do it now?
Well, uh...
I mean, as romantic as that is.
Um, here.
Why don't you pick a song to play?
Just to set the mood a little.
Set the mood?
Ew, that's awful. I can't believe those
words actually came out of your mouth.
[both laugh]
People say that.
Okay, let me see.
Wait, this is one of your
most played songs?
- Which one?
- Shh.
["Baby Now That I've Found You"
by the Foundations playing]
I'm setting the mood.
♪Baby, now that I've...♪
You're actually proving my point.
- The mood is set.
- Is that right?
Please. This song is so sexy.
Makes me want to do a sexy little dance.
[laughing] What is happening?
The groove.
It's taking over.
Look.
You're feeling it too.
Oh.
♪Baby, even though you don't need me ♪
Okay. [chuckles]
♪You don't need me ♪
Oh yeah, that's terrible. I love it.
♪Baby, baby, since first we met ♪
♪I knew in this heart of mine ♪
♪I wanna tell you ♪
♪The love we had could not be bad ♪
♪Play it right and bide my time ♪
[laughs]
♪Spent a lifetime looking for somebody ♪
♪To give me love like you ♪
♪Now you've told me
that you wanna leave me ♪
♪Darling, I just can't let you...♪
[romantic music with pulsing beat]
[panting softly]
[pulsing beat quickens]
[breathing heavily]
- [music stops]
- What's wrong?
Nothing, nothing.
I think we should stop.
I don't-- I don't want to stop.
I-I can do this.
No, you don't have to.
But I...
I want to.
Okay?
Fuck.
[panting]
I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
This-- This-- This is what happens.
I'm-- I'm in it. I-I'm having fun.
I feel good.
And then I just, like, zoom out.
Like, leave my body.
It's like I'm sitting there watching
myself from across the room going, like,
"What is wrong with you?"
Nothing.
Nothing is wrong with you.
What if, like...
Like, what if I'm broken?
You're not broken, Wellsy.
You just don't trust me enough
to fully let go, and that's okay.
No, but I do trust you.
I wouldn't--
I wouldn't be here if I didn't.
But nothing is more vulnerable than sex.
So...
if you're not there yet...
that sounds completely normal.
Wow, that-- that was surprisingly deep.
I do have another idea.
I mean, if you're willing to hear it.
Yeah, okay, sure.
Instead of me giving you an orgasm...
why don't you give yourself one?
Uh, that's not going to prove anything.
I do that all the time.
- Oh, do you?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Then...
show me.
["Back In My Body"
by Maggie Rogers playing]
[sighs]
Show me.
And I'll show you.
["Back In My Body" continues]
[song intensifies]
[Hannah gasps]
[Garrett] Stay here.
[Hannah breathing heavily]
Stay with me.
[Hannah gasping]
[panting]
♪Oh, this time ♪
♪This time, I know I'm fighting ♪
♪This time, I know I'm back in my body ♪
[sighs]
[laughs] Oh, my God. I did it.
[breathing heavily]
Thanks.
No, no.
Thank you. That was...
Thanks.
[both laugh]
[sighs]
So what now?
Drunk Shakespeare? Who's drunk?
- Like the actors or the audience?
- [Hannah] Everyone.
Last year's Hamlet got so drunk that he
made out with the ghost of his own father.
- Yikes.
- Yeah.
Okay, well, wish Allie luck for me.
[laughing] Yeah.
Jackpot.
Always count on Tucker
to make too much pasta salad.
Why does he always put
Brussels sprouts in it?
Yum.
- All right, give me.
- Yeah, you want one?
- This one's got a little bacon on it.
- All right.
[both laugh]
[humming "Baby Now That I've Found You"]
I told you that was a sexy song.
Got to say, I'm surprised
it's one of your most played.
Kind of doesn't fit in with your whole,
"I'm a cool hockey man
that listens to classic rock" image.
Hey, I'm a cool hockey man
that contains multitudes, so...
[both laugh]
But actually, my mom used to play me
all kinds of music.
- Yeah, she sounds cool.
- Yeah, she was cool.
She had a huge record collection.
She used to let me pick one out to play
whenever my dad...
got too...
intense.
How do you feel
when you listen to that song?
Why do you ask?
Is it just something my advisor said.
Uh, I guess...
I don't know, it makes me feel bold.
Bold?
Yeah, like to just say,
"I like you, deal with it."
- That's badass.
- Yeah, it is badass.
- You know, I was thinking...
- [cell phone chimes]
Sorry.
Uh, where were we?
Uh, I actually probably should go.
- Oh, are-- are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
I have a lot to do for the showcase
and classes and...
Yeah.
But thank you for your service.
It's much appreciated.
See you soon?
Yeah, okay.
I'll text you?
- So Garrett made you come.
- Yep.
- And you're not freaking out.
- No.
Uh, and you broke up with Sean.
- Yeah.
- And you're not freaking out.
- No.
- Because if you were freaking out,
I could break out
the emergency stash of hot Cheetos.
No, I can't let myself become
"Eats Her Feelings Allie".
'Cause if I do that
I'll just keep backsliding
through "Raging Diva Allie",
and then "Complete and Total
Breakdown Allie",
and then next thing you know,
I'll be "Insurance Queen
of Dorset, Vermont, Allie".
God help us all.
I promised myself.
This has to be the last time.
It has to stick.
I'm actually doing pretty well so far.
Like, I don't even really miss Sean.
I believe you.
Uh...
even if you are wearing his sweatshirt.
This isn't his sweatshirt.
Um...
Oh, my God!
I am a woman possessed!
Hannah, you got to help me.
I lied. I already ate the Cheetos.
- I licked the bag clean.
- [cell phone chimes]
Who is that? Is it Garrett? Is it Justin?
Please distract me with the sordid
details of the intricate web
that is your love life.
Uh, it's-- it's Justin.
So you're still into him?
Of course I am.
I worked out this whole orgasm problem
so that I could be with him, didn't I?
Yeah, but I don't know, I thought
you might be "dicknotized" by Garrett.
- You wouldn't be the first.
- Yeah.
Okay, I'll admit it.
The night was kind of perfect.
Garrett made me feel really safe
and a lot of really,
really good other things,
but that doesn't magically turn him
into someone else, you know?
No, you got to take him at face value.
Right, exactly.
[laughs] And the guy can't get
through a single conversation
without someone trying to sext him,
which is fine because I got the orgasm,
which is what I wanted.
It's just an arrangement between friends.
Yeah, and this won't make
your friendship weird at all?
We had a plan.
The plan worked.
There will be absolutely
no weirdness whatsoever.
It was so weird.
Yeah, well, girls don't usually love it
when other girls snap you during a hookup.
- [coach] Tucker, in.
- Logan, this is Bernardo.
Protect him with your life. Your life.
Why do you care
how the night ended anyway?
Because he didn't want it to end.
What? You guys have been
talking about this all practice
and the answer seems pretty obvious.
[coach] Logan, in.
Hey, does Logan
seem off to you guys today?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
Bunch of missed passes,
flubbed a goal, stuff like that.
What? No, not you.
Birdie, what do you mean? What's obvious?
You're into her, dude.
Fuck. I think you're right.
- He's all over the place.
- [all] Shut up, Joe.
- I should tell her.
- Yup.
Like today?
- Yep.
- [whistle blows]
- [coach] Birdie, in.
- [Garrett] Shit.
- She's going to Drunk Shakespeare later.
- Sounds like you're going.
- Hey, Joe, watch Bernardo.
- Who?
Who's going to Drunk Shakespeare?
- Hannah.
- Bernardo.
- Amazing, I'm there.
- [coach] Rogers, in.
Hold this for Birdie.
- So why are we going to Drunk Shakespeare?
- We are not going anywhere.
Birdie thinks I should tell Hannah
how I feel about her.
- How do you feel about her?
- [coach] Stuebs, in.
Finally.
Telling her is the right move, G.
We all fuck with Wellsy,
and I think she's good for you.
No! Bernardo! How?
Okay. We're going to Drunk Shakespeare.
[whistle blowing]
Okay, dramatic entrance.
Whatever.
Seriously, what's your damage, Heather?
Nothing, just a shitty practice.
Really?
- [sighs]
- That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Mm.
Garrett, he was so busy talking about
Hannah that we missed a bunch of passes
and it just made me look bad.
Oh, I see what's happening.
This is about your dumb crush on Hannah.
What? That's...
I... I don't...
[laughs] Convincing.
Don't bother. I saw the way
you were staring at her at karaoke.
This is so like you.
You want things you can't have.
- No, I don't.
- You need a fucking wake-up call.
Maybe Garrett can afford to get distracted
chasing a little crush, but you can't.
You don't have a guaranteed deal
with the Bruins.
Jules, I get it.
You've been passed over
twice in the draft.
Your chances of making it to the NHL
are slimmer than Timmy Chalamet.
And if you don't make it,
it's you and Mom at the garage.
Forever.
Is that what you want?
No, it's not what I fucking want.
I'm just saying, if you're going to chase
an impossible dream,
chase one that actually matters.
[indistinct chatter]
["Sex, Drugs & Existential Dread"
by Chloe Qisha playing]
♪Well come on inside ♪
♪And we can watch the news
and get naked...♪
This "mingle with the audience
before the show" shtick
is such hacky student director bullshit.
"Ooh, it's immersive.
We're breaking the aesthetic distance."
- Give me a fucking break.
- Hey, whoa, babe.
Maybe we've turned the corner
onto "Raging Diva Allie".
Maybe you've turned the corner
into Cuntsville.
[Hannah scoffs]
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean that.
No, it's okay. It's your first show
at Briar without Sean.
Yeah, he just really used to help
calm me down, you know?
I'm kind of nervous.
Yeah, maybe it is making me
a little bit of a...
Catherine! Don't touch a prop
that's not yours!
♪There's people everywhere you go ♪
♪There's people in the bars ♪
♪There's people on the motorways ♪
♪Driving little people cars ♪
♪There's people walking animals... ♪
- Hey.
- Hey. Hey.
[Hannah] You're here!
♪Kissing other people
what the hell is that for?♪
♪Ew...♪
What-- What are you doing here?
I'm glad you're here, but...
Well, Beau recruited me.
I have to steal this from Tucker.
Fuck! Oh my...
Sorry.
Are you kidding me?
- Hey, Wellsy.
- Hey.
Jordan.
- Justin.
- Oh, right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sorry, man. My bad.
- It's all good, man.
- Beau and Dean drag you here?
Yeah, man. Well, you know Dean.
He's persuasive.
What about you, bro?
You a big Shakespeare guy or what?
Not really, but Hannah told me
she was coming, so here I am.
[laughs] Oh, she did?
She did.
Looks like the show's starting.
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna get a seat?
Couch is free.
- Yeah, yeah. We should probably sit.
- Yeah.
- See you around, man.
- Yeah, brother.
[soft, melancholic music playing]
- [inaudible dialogue]
- [applause]
Come on, bitches.
Let me hear you all scream
for our gay show.
A Midsummer Night's...
Scream!
[all cheer]
Now, virgins oft find
Drunk Shakespeare scary.
If it's your first time,
I'll pop your cherry.
Now, there's only one rule,
my sweet, gentle twinks.
When an actor calls "line,"
everyone drinks.
- I like that.
- Okay, let's drink to that.
Yeah.
What? What?
[whispering]
No. I'm so sorry, everyone.
It seems that the actors that were going
to play our four young lovers
have all been struck
by a terrible affliction.
- True love?
- No.
Gonorrhea.
- [all] Oh!
- [laughter]
[snickers]
We'll be needing some brave volunteers
from the audience.
You.
- You go.
- Mm-mm.
Oh, would you look at this couple?
[cheering]
Give it up for our Hermia and Lysander!
[cheers and applause]
Whoo!
Bitch, I love this for you.
Okay, next I need a big,
strong man to play Demetrius.
Me, Garrett Graham.
I want to be in the show.
- What the hell? Shut the fuck up.
- What?
You can't tell her how you feel
sitting here on your ass, come on.
- Come here, pookie.
- That's okay.
- No, I'm all right.
- You're ours now.
Come on, G! Yeah!
All right, all right.
[Tucker] Yeah!
Thank you.
[Dexter] Okay, now we just need Helena.
She's a real messy bitch
who wants to get in Demetrius' pants.
- Can anyone relate?
- [excited chatter]
Allow me.
Not even going to wait to be picked.
That is messy.
Let's hear it for our four young lovers.
- [applause]
- From the game, right?
Hannah.
Please. Everyone knows the girl
who locked down Garrett Graham.
Uh, no. No, I didn't lock him.
I mean, we're not locked.
He is free to unlock anyone he wants.
[Dexter] ...we love to stir up some drama.
All right, Hermia.
Let's get you all caught up.
All right, you're in love with Lysander.
[all] Oh!
But your big, bad daddy
is forcing you to marry Demetrius.
[audience boos]
What say you, Hermia?
But Daddy, I love him!
[audience] But Daddy, she loves him!
[The Cardigans' "Lovefool" plays]
Oh!
Now, after this, we've got like
ten minutes of rude mechanicals BS.
So, feel free
to help yourselves to our wet bar.
Okay.
So your life is practice, class, repeat,
and now also the theater.
- Can we seriously not do this right now?
- Do what?
You're broadening your horizons.
I think it's fun.
Looks like Hannah's
broadening her horizons, too.
Didn't have to mess with her like that.
She's not my girlfriend.
[scoffs] But you clearly want her to be.
No, I don't.
Please, you can deny it all you want,
but I looked at you
the same way for months.
Kendall, about the way
that I ended things,
I was kind of a dick.
Don't.
Don't apologize to me
just to make yourself feel better.
I was just gonna say, you know,
it sucks when you like someone
and they don't like you back.
It does.
If I knew just how much it sucked,
I probably would have
done some things differently.
So, I'm sorry.
And really...
will you accept my apology
if I promise to keep feeling bad about it?
[laughs]
I was having so much fun being a bitch.
Fine. Yeah, okay, I accept.
[chuckles]
Herbal. It's foul, but it's effective.
[Jeremy] I see their knavery.
This is to make an ass of me.
[Allie] What angel wakes me
from my flowery bed?
I pray thee, gentle mortal, sing again.
Mine ear is much enamored of thy note.
And so is mine eye enthralled to thy...
to thy...
smile.
And thy sweatshirt.
And how surprisingly ripped thou art.
And how thou always made me chocolate chip
and blueberry pancakes
because thou knowest I want both,
even though thou aren't
eating carbs right now.
And so what if thou favors missionary?
Methinks I could get on board
with missionary.
Oh, sweet Bottom,
out to Vermont do not desire to go.
Please, do not desire to go.
[applause]
- Holy shit, she's incredible.
- Yeah, man. She really is.
[laughs] Line?
["Whiplash" by Aespa playing]
♪One look, give 'em whiplash ♪
Line?
[all] Line!
- Line.
- He said it!
- He said it.
- That's the word.
[rowdy chatter]
Okay, I understand your confusion.
This is what's happening here.
I am... I'm fucked up, man.
Line?
It's not even your line!
Sue me, I'm thirsty.
Okay, are these drama kids
better at drinking?
- No, I get it, I get it.
- What's going on?
I totally get it.
Ooh!
Pyramus and Thisbe are us all.
- Okay.
- Hmm? Right?
- Well done.
- You see, Tuck?
[laughing] Tucker.
[both laughing]
Welcome back!
My lovers.
Oh!
Looks like you two had a good time.
And it's about to get even better.
I made this love potion
special for the boys.
It's a real knockout.
And wouldn't you know it?
When they came to,
they only had eyes for Helena.
[audience] Ooh!
Okay, loving this.
But, fools and mortals,
who will win fair Helena's hand?
How is a buxom maiden ever to decide?
Oh.
I know.
How about a good old-fashion dance-off?
Which one of you
wants to take the pole first?
[Dean] Garrett...
[all, chanting] Garrett! Garrett! Garrett!
Garrett! Garrett! Garrett!
Garrett! Garrett!
Garrett! Get your pole on!
Fuck. Fuck you guys.
[cheers and applause]
[The Kid LAROI "Girls" plays]
Fuck it.
Oh!
[playful shouting]
♪Fuck your ex-man, I'm the man now ♪
♪Think I feel bad, he was fanned out ♪
♪Do what you like, you've been too nice ♪
♪He didn't do right, that's too bad now ♪
♪I see that you worked all night
you're trying to cash out ♪
♪You and your friends
are trying to lash out ♪
♪And I'm not the one
to tell them, "Stand down"♪
♪It's their world and they just wanna...♪
You know, I was thinking
about asking you out.
The reason I didn't is because I thought
you and Garrett were serious, but...
I guess you're not?
Nope. Uh, definitely not serious.
Cool.
Look, I'm not normally
into theater, but...
you know, I'm really glad I came.
- Yeah, me too.
- [both laugh]
♪I'm for real ♪
♪You worked all night
you're trying to cash out ♪
♪You and your friends
are trying to lash out ♪
♪And I'm not the one
to tell 'em, "Stand down"♪
♪It's their world and they just wanna ♪
♪Girls just wanna dance ♪
[Dexter] If we shadows have offended,
think but this, and all is mended.
That you have but slumbered here
while these visions did appear.
And this weak and idle...
[Hannah] Hey.
Hey.
That was some show you put on out there.
Very Boys Gone Wild.
Thanks.
I, uh, bet you're happy
about the second love potion.
You and Justin back together?
Yeah, well, all's well that ends well.
That's-- That's Shakespeare.
- Yeah. I know.
- Sorry.
Um, uh, actually...
Justin said he wants to ask me out.
Uh, congratulations. That's, uh...
Yeah, you did it.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh...
So I-- I guess this means
our deal is officially over?
Right?
Uh, yeah. Right.
Yeah, I mean, I got you the grade.
And I got you the guy.
[Justin] Hey.
They want us over there for curtain call.
Ready?
- Sure.
- Sweet.
[applause]
[melancholic music playing]
[hockey stick slapping]
[sighs]
You're getting some good power
behind the shot.
Still going wide.
Well, as long as you keep
hitting the rink.
- Remember Eastwood? Freshman year?
- Yeah.
That wasn't on me, all right?
Birdie took the shot.
It just deflected off my stick.
And Bragg's teeth.
I bought him a beer. He's fine.
[both laugh]
Hey, sorry I couldn't make
the Shakespeare thing.
Yeah, it's okay.
You didn't miss much.
So...
you and Hannah?
[sighs]
I don't know what I was thinking.
I don't have time for a girlfriend.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
I know you were really into her.
It's fine.
There's a plan in place for me.
Team captain, Frozen Four, Bruins.
- All I gotta do is follow through.
- That's a good plan.
People would kill to have that plan.
Right, exactly.
Hannah was just a distraction.
Yeah, I mean...
sometimes you don't get
everything you want.
But you're Garrett Graham.
All right?
Things are gonna work out for you, okay?
They always do.
[laughs]
Yeah, well, for you too, man.
It's me and you on the Bruins.
That's the dream, right?
Yeah, that's the dream.
Anyway, I was gonna hit up Malone's
if you wanted to join.
You look like you could use it.
That's all right. I'm gonna stay.
You sure?
- Yeah.
- All right, man.
- I'll see you later.
- All right, bud.
["Bluest Flame (DJ Sliink Remix)" by
Selena Gomez and benny blanco playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[inaudible]
[phone line rings]
I know. I said I wouldn't call.
And that's how I learned the difference
between Billie Joe Armstrong
and Haley Joel Osment.
[laughs]
Yeah, that's-- that's funny.
I'm-- I'm really glad
we got to spend some time together.
You know, outside of rehearsals.
Yeah, same.
["Sofa King" by Royel Otis playing]
Oh, I fucking love this song.
Why do you love it so much?
Well, I mean, for starters,
the bass line and the way it interacts
with the lead guitars--
No, uh, sorry.
I actually mean...
what does it make you feel?
I mean, jealous I didn't write it first.
Why? What does it make you feel?
Uh, nothing.
I mean, they're not for everyone.
Yeah.
Hey, this...
This party's kind of dead, right?
- Do you want to come back to mine, and--?
- Justin...
Let me guess. Rain check?
Not quite.
♪You're so fucking gorgeous ♪
[jiggles doorknob]
[phone line rings]
[Garrett's voice] This is Garrett.
No phones allowed on the ice,
so leave a message.
[voicemail beeps]
[Hannah, over PA]
♪Baby ♪
♪Now that I've found you
I can't let you go ♪
♪I'll build my world around you ♪
♪I need you so ♪
♪Baby, even though you don't need me ♪
♪You don't need me ♪
♪Baby ♪
♪Now that I've found you
I can't let you go ♪
♪I'll build my world around you
I need you so ♪
♪Baby, even though you don't need me ♪
♪You don't need me ♪
♪Baby, baby, since first we met ♪
♪I knew in this heart of mine ♪
♪The love we had could not be bad ♪
♪I played it right and I bide my time ♪
♪Spent a lifetime looking for somebody ♪
♪To give me love like you ♪
♪Now you've told me
that you wanna leave me ♪
♪Darling, I just can't let you ♪
♪Baby ♪
♪Now that I've found you
I can't let you go ♪
♪I'll build my world around you
I need you so ♪
♪Baby, even though you don't need me ♪
♪You don't need me ♪
["Baby Now That I've Found You"
piano instrumental plays]
- Wait.
- Wait?
Are we on the same page here?
Didn't you hear?
I just did a whole thing. It was romantic.
I'm just... I don't want
to be your friend, Wellsy.
This isn't how you kiss your friends.
No more Justin.
Music collaboration only.
No more sexy Snapchats.
The unsexiest only.
Deal.
And no more deals.
I can live with that.
[Hannah chuckles]
[sighs]
["Bed on Fire" by G Flip playing]
♪Hey ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪Preacher said I couldn't get no higher ♪
♪Playing Jesus like a backseat driver ♪
[all cheering]
♪If that's what I get for my desire ♪
♪Then watch me set the bed on fire ♪
♪She held my hand ♪
♪And led me back to the river ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪We drowned our sins all night ♪
♪And howled at the moon ♪
♪Hey ♪
♪I'm running around
I'm running around, it's heaven ♪
♪Well, if I'm going down
I'll light a fire for you ♪
♪Hey ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪Preacher said I couldn't get no higher ♪
♪Playing Jesus like a backseat driver ♪
♪If that's what I get for my desire ♪
♪Then watch me set the bed on fire ♪
[camera shutters click]
♪I tried it, I liked it ♪
♪No one found that surprising ♪
♪I'll fall asleep
with a match in my hand ♪
[both laugh]
♪I tried it, I liked it ♪
♪No one found that surprising ♪
♪I'll fall asleep
with a match in my hand ♪
♪I'll set the bed on fire ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪Preacher said I couldn't get no higher ♪
♪Playing Jesus like a backseat driver ♪
♪If that's what I get for my desire...♪
[gasping]
[Garrett moans]
[gasps]
♪Watch me set the bed on fire...♪
[moaning]
♪Watch me set the bed on fire ♪
[both laugh]
[woman on phone]
Hann?
Did you hear that?
I think the whole campus heard that.
Okay, rude. But that's not--
- Hann?
- Mom?
Are you there? I can't see you.
Fuck! Oh!
♪I'll set the bed on fire ♪
♪Oh, oh, oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
I mean, those kids are a blessing,
but they're a lot.
You say that every year, and every year
you get sad when Aunt Nicole
and everybody leave
and the house is empty again.
I know. What are you doing this year?
Gonna go to Brooklyn with Allie again?
No, Garrett's housemates
are doing Friendsgiving,
- so I'm going to stay for that.
- [text alert]
Friendsgiving?
That sounds so fun.
What are you going to bring?
You said they liked Nana's
lasagna recipe, right?
Yeah, yeah, but...
- Well, you can't show up empty-handed.
- We won't.
Text Garrett.
Ask him how many people are going.
Uh, I, um...
Garrett?
Wait, he's there?
Uh...
Introduce me.
No, Mom.
Garrett, honey, how many people
will be at Friendsgiving?
Hi, Mrs. Wells.
Uh, please, call me Carrie.
Look at you.
You weren't exaggerating, Hannah.
He's so handsome.
- [both laugh]
- Okay, hanging up now.
Garrett, Hannah's dad is going to be
so jealous I met you first.
He's been bragging about you
to all of our friends.
He posted about your game last night.
He wanted to tag you, but don't worry.
I didn't let him.
Just know that you have
a super fan over here.
Mom, they lost last night.
[laughs]
It doesn't matter. He's proud.
Okay, we gotta go. We have class.
Okay, well,
it's nice to meet you, Garrett.
Nice meeting you, too, Mrs...
Carrie.
[both chuckle]
Miss and love you, sweet pea.
- [Hannah] Miss and love you, too, Mama.
- Bye.
[Hannah chuckles]
Sorry, she's enthusiastic.
She's sweet. She loves you.
Okay, are you driving or shall I?
I'm not sitting
on your handlebars, Wellsy.
One day, Graham.
One day.
[both laugh]
[sticks slapping on ice]
[bag thuds]
I didn't know how else
to get you to talk to me.
I want you to come home for Thanksgiving.
Are you serious?
Cindy still really wants to meet you
before the wedding,
and I would appreciate it, as well.
Look, I don't know what kind of bullshit
game you're playing, but I don't--
It's not a game, Garrett.
I'm really trying here.
I'm a different man now,
and I don't expect you to understand this,
but Cindy...
she's chosen to trust me.
And I want to be someone
worthy of that trust.
Garrett, please.
Just think about it.
It's almost there,
but it's like my advisor said.
I'm just-- I'm not feeling it.
Not yet.
Okay. Uh, fine.
I'll take another crack
at the lyrics over the break.
- Great, yeah, thank you.
- No worries.
See you, Garrett.
Yeah, bud.
Did Julian wipe out again?
Uh, Justin has some cool ideas
for a new verse,
which means that I can take a break
over Thanksgiving.
- Hey, Wellsy.
- Yeah?
Why don't you go home
for the long weekend?
Seems like your parents
would love to see you.
Uh, that-- that place
isn't really my home anymore.
Because of what happened to you?
Yeah, yeah, and what happened after.
Uh, when the guy you accuse
of assault is the mayor's kid,
people don't tend to believe you.
Yeah, it didn't help that his whole team
rallied around him,
testified against me in court.
Some real Hester Prynne bullshit.
He was an athlete?
Yeah.
A hockey player?
Ah, fuck.
Look, that's all in the past now.
He's in the past.
Indiana's just not
my favorite place to go back to.
My parents get it.
Uh, why do you ask?
Uh, my dad wants me to go home
for Thanksgiving and meet his fiancée.
Would you want to?
Maybe.
I don't know.
Uh, yeah, things with my dad
are kind of...
It's complicated.
Yeah, well, he's still your dad, right?
Even if he is a hard-ass.
When I saw him before practice,
he seemed, like, different?
Good different?
Well, I don't know
if he's capable of that, but...
But you hope so.
Look, I think people
can change if they want to.
So you're saying you think
I should give him another chance?
If that's what you want.
If I go...
will you come with me?
Of course.
Are you-- Are you sure?
That's what girlfriends do.
Real ones, anyway.
[both laugh]
Thank you.
[sighs]
Am I getting faster?
Oh, I lost interest in that.
You look good.
Mean.
- Like "tough" mean or "you" mean?
- Hmm.
- Zdeno Chara mean.
- Oh.
You can never pull off "me" mean.
[chuckles] I'll take it.
By these pictures, I'd almost assume
you weren't into Garrett's girlfriend.
- Because I'm not!
- Uh-huh.
[scoffs]
[cell phone ringer vibrating]
Ah. Looks like you drew the short straw.
Want me to put it on speaker?
I'd rather keep skating suicides.
She's probably having
a hard time right now.
Because she'll be alone on Thanksgiving?
She did that to herself.
She's trying, dude.
She's always trying.
[vibrating continues]
Better get that.
Hi, Mom.
This, gentlemen, is 25 pounds
of pure poultry perfection.
[loud thud]
- [Logan] That's a big-ass turkey.
- Damn straight.
We're gonna kill Thanksgiving.
Unlike last year
when everyone "brought" something
and all we had to eat was a turkey
and 300 Miller High Life's.
Champagne of beers.
I actually want to remember
my Thanksgiving this year.
Which is why I've put it upon myself
to handle all food preparations.
Because this year
is going to be the best Thanksgiving.
The perfect Thanksgiving.
- Holy shit.
- Fucking hell.
Since I can't go home,
I've decided to make
all my mama's greatest hits from scratch.
We got three kinds of pie,
two kinds of cranberry sauces,
and more sweet potatoes
than you can shake a stick at.
And the pièce de résistance.
The Tucker family deep-fried turkey.
All rights reserved, 1985.
- Can I go work out now?
- I don't think he's done.
No. No, no, no. I'm very much not done.
A general is only as good
as his troops, okay?
Where is Garrett?
[laughing] Are we supposed
to be your troops?
I'm not leaving anything up to chance.
This, my friends,
will be a military operation.
You all have jobs to do, okay?
Where the fuck is Garrett?
- What's up?
- Garrett.
Thank you for finally joining us.
You and Wellsy will handle
the pie crust from Della's backstock.
For?
Thanksgiving.
Oh, right. Sorry, Tuck.
Hannah and I are going to my dad's
place in Boston. Can't make it.
What? No.
Okay.
No problem. No problem.
Dean, you can handle all his stuff, okay?
No, I would be all over that,
but I am road-tripping
- down to New York tomorrow with Bella.
- Oh, no, dude.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Blackout Wednesday, dude.
Drinksgiving? Why would I be drunk here
when I could be drunk there?
Sorry, bro. See you next year.
So, the friends
are abandoning Friendsgiving.
Who needs them?
Jules and I are here, it's gonna be
the perfect fucking Thanksgiving.
What do you need?
I'll send you my to-do list.
[phone chimes]
- [Logan] Damn.
- [Tucker] I know.
It's glorious.
I'm so depressed you're not coming
to Brooklyn with me this year.
Me, too.
But I want to be there for Garrett.
As much as I love
watching Aunt Kathy get drunk
and busting out her old cheer routine.
- God, old gal's still got the splits.
- [laughs]
It's your first Thanksgiving without Sean.
How are you doing?
Honestly, I am loving my single life.
I'm Yasmina in season two
of Al Nisa Alashba.
Doesn't she fall into a coma
for most of that season?
Yes, but before that,
she is single and thriving.
As am I.
Just not getting tied down,
focusing on myself and my acting.
- That's it.
- Well, I am proud of you.
Well, you, too.
Meeting Garrett's dad,
being a good girlfriend and shit.
- [both laugh]
- You nervous?
Uh, no.
I mean, he's famous, right?
Yeah, yeah, okay, I'm a little nervous,
but not because he's famous.
Just... I don't know.
The way Garrett talks about him,
he seems like really intense.
Yeah, I've seen him at games.
Does the man ever smile?
I don't think so.
Well, don't stress.
It's not about him liking you.
It's about Garrett.
And he already likes you.
Yeah, I just think it's really important
to Garrett that this goes well.
That's what relationships are for,
honey bun.
Supporting each other.
Helping each other grow as people.
It can't all be about sex and fun.
[cell phone vibrates]
Oh, shit. The bus is almost here.
Gotta go.
Well, no, Garrett can just drive you.
No, it's fine. I love a bus.
You hate a bus.
It's fine.
I love you. Happy Thanksgiving.
Love you. [laughs]
- [Tucker] 425 for how long?
- [Gail on phone] Thirty minutes.
Use that time to prep the turkey
before it has to go in.
- And don't forget to--
- Pat-dry the bird.
I know. I know. Can't be wet.
Unless you want a crispy turkey
and no eyebrows like Uncle Pete.
And don't skimp on the marshmallows
for the sweet potato casserole.
Ooh, slivers, dude.
Dude, slivers.
Just... easy.
- Yes, chef.
- There you go.
Just remember to drop the turkey in
exactly one hour
before your sides are ready.
One hour. Got it.
First Thanksgiving
you're cooking all on your own.
It's weird doing all this without you.
Miss you, too, JT.
But I'm right there with you.
I can practically smell
the sweat and testosterone.
- [laughs]
- Fair.
Just don't want to screw anything up.
- It has to be perfect.
- No such thing.
It's not the food.
It's the comfort and love
that make the food.
Did you just quote the Barefoot Contessa?
Or did she quote me?
No way of knowing, is there?
[laughs]
Gravy, gotta go.
Love you, baby.
Perfect. Yes. Yes.
Where were the marshmallows?
I just saw them five seconds ago.
Where could they possibly go?
One, two, three.
They were just here.
What are you doing?
Keeping our family tradition alive.
I'm trying to have a normal
Thanksgiving right now, okay?
What's normal? Turkey, pumpkin pie?
Boo, boring.
Say what you will about Mom,
we always had fun.
Okay, you have a very interesting,
selective memory.
Can't we just enjoy this, please?
You are ruining Tuck's Thanksgiving.
[Tucker] They were just here.
The marshmallows were just here.
Party people!
- Happy Thanksgiving!
- Oh! Birdie!
Nats! Thank God!
- I thought we'd have too much food.
- Not a chance. We brought friends.
And we brought wine.
Oh, six. Six more people.
Hi, Kendall. Great.
That's perfect, I can do that. Yeah.
Hi, how you doing?
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi, Tucker. Thanks for having us.
- [indistinct chatter]
- Good to see you.
Is it possible to double a sweet potato
casserole in one dish?
You're asking me?
I got this.
This is a bad idea.
[Hannah] Yeah, you're right.
Who brings a key lime pie to Thanksgiving?
Why didn't you stop me? Pumpkin?
Pumpkin is the thing.
Or maybe I should have brought wine.
I meant my dad, Wellsy.
- Oh, right.
- [both laugh]
And we can go at any point.
Just give me the signal,
and we'll get the fuck out.
- The signal?
- Yeah.
Like, I don't know,
squeeze my hand or something.
Once means you're good.
Two squeezes, and we're gone.
[laughs]
[sighs]
Or we go?
Or... Or we stay?
You gotta give me something here.
[laughs]
All right, we stay.
Okay.
First step, getting out the car.
- [laughs]
- Yeah.
[doorbell rings]
Garrett, you made it.
Dad.
And you must be Hannah.
- Glad to finally meet you.
- Hi.
Sorry, I'd shake your hand, but--
Oh, I'll take that.
Pie!
Oh, it's key lime.
You love key lime.
- He loves key lime.
- I do, it's the superior pie, thank you.
Well, don't let the poor kids
freeze out there.
Come in.
I'm gonna put this in the fridge.
I'll take your coats.
Thank you.
Thanks.
[Hannah sighs]
It's a nice house.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Aw! Look at you.
Oh.
They look alike, don't they?
It's uncanny.
I'm so glad you're here, Garrett.
I can't wait to hear
all about how the season's going.
[laughs]
Come on, I'll put the game on.
It's you versus me, kid.
Rangers, Bruins.
Actually, is it cool
if I show Hannah around first?
Yeah, of course.
You don't have to ask permission.
This is your house, too.
Here, I'll give you the tour.
Cool.
[knock on door]
Thank you so much.
Thank you for coming.
Who is that now?
We come bearing alcohol.
And we got tiny little boxes of cereal
stolen from the dining hall.
Hey, look, Tuck. More people.
Hannah said orphans were welcome.
They are. They are, yes.
Uh, just grab a seat.
Jules will grab you a drink.
Yeah. Just make yourselves at home
here in the living room.
Okay, thank you, guys. Happy Thanksgiving.
[all] Happy Thanksgiving.
[stove beeps]
Why is the stuffing not in the oven yet?
Because the corn pudding and the green
bean casserole are already in there.
Here, please consult the oven schedule.
I did all the math.
The stuffing needs to hang out
in the neutral zone.
- It only takes 30 minutes.
- [stove beeps]
If you guys were half as good at hockey...
Jules, I can't right now.
Please.
- Go.
- Gravy. Guys, please.
- Somebody taste it. Thank you.
- Logan, try it.
And for the end of the tour, this is me.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's just weird
being back here.
After my mom died,
I went off to boarding school,
and I never really lived here again.
Yeah, I can tell. [laughs]
Is your dad running
a storage business on the side?
[both chuckle]
This is just all the stuff he signs
when he goes to mall appearances
or conventions or whatever.
Right.
Trying to keep the legend alive.
His best years are behind him.
Are you afraid that'll happen to you?
This is what success
looks like, eventually.
Or I could tear my ACL tomorrow
and get stuck bagging groceries
at the Stop 'N' Shop.
Not that--
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
Hey, my mom works at Bob's Market, so...
Yeah, not-- Yeah, that wasn't really
a dream, either, so...
What was?
I don't know. She-- She was a singer.
Her high school choir
won a bunch of competitions,
but I don't know,
she never really went for it.
She must be proud of you, then.
Yeah, I just think
she wants me to be happy.
My dad, he's not really like that.
Or, I don't know about now, but he wasn't.
Not just with hockey, with everything.
He was always...
so...
Intense?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, seriously intense.
Yeah, I don't know,
it just seems kind of sad.
Like you wake up one morning
and can't play hockey anymore.
Would you miss it?
It's the only thing I'm good at.
That's not true. And that's not an answer.
[laughs]
I think I would be...
like, relieved.
[cell phone vibrates]
Sorry.
Uh, Allie said that they wanted
to wish me a Happy Thanksgiving.
Take it.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I've got this.
Okay.
Hey.
[laughing] Oh, my gosh!
Hi, everyone.
Okay, we have more people here
than a Walmart on a Black Friday.
We are going to loaves and fishes
this whole thing.
I'mma go get potatoes
from the extra fridge, and then, um...
- Pat-dry?
- ...pat-dry the bird, yes.
- Yes.
- Go get 'em, buddy.
Wait, wait, wait.
No marshmallows on the sweet potatoes?
[man] They're already sweet.
Okay, that's fucking blasphemy.
You're a blasphemer.
I will die on this hill.
We never had marshmallows
on our sweet potatoes.
- We never had sweet potatoes.
- I had a sweet potato taco one year.
Tacos? On Thanksgiving?
It's actually the best time
for tacos, honestly.
Especially when your big bro has a sweet
sponsorship deal with Taco Shack.
Ah. They're open on Thanksgiving?
Yeah, they're the only place
open on Thanksgiving.
And we learned that the hard way
when our mom got drunk one year
and forgot she was grilling chicken.
The propane tank almost leveled the block.
- Whoa.
- It was a blessing, actually.
Mama Logan was never known
for her cooking.
I know.
We should bring Mom Taco Shack.
Absolutely not.
Well, she's probably surrounded
by strangers
eating gross rehab food right now.
So?
So, she needs our support.
Should we be here for this?
I supported her the last time she went in,
and the time before that,
and the time before that.
It's Thanksgiving,
and she's fucking family, John.
She's in fucking rehab, Jules.
Exactly.
She's...
She's trying.
Okay, new plan.
I'm gonna whip up some spinach casserole.
What?
You know what? Forget it.
I'll go myself.
Tucker! My friend.
We are here.
Yes. Yes, you are.
I'm so sorry to be late.
Uh-huh.
- So, Yanis from Latvia.
- Hi.
- Uh, Cheryl from Philippines.
- You know Arjun?
- Mm-mm. Hi.
- And Karl Heinz.
- Hello! Karl Heinz.
[all laugh]
- [glass shatters]
- [Lexi] Sorry.
You know what, boys and girls?
I need space to work.
Everybody, we are going
to take this shindig outside.
Let's go. Outside. Outside, guys.
- Outside, guys.
- [man] Outside.
Thank you, guys.
- [indistinct chatter]
- Thank you, guys.
[exhales]
[TV announcer] The Bruins started the day
three points clear
of fifth-place Philadelphia,
and fourth in the East.
The game is on.
It looked like the Bruins
are gonna get that puck out.
I heard you stopped by
and saw a Bruins practice.
Yeah.
You get a chance to show off?
Yeah, a little bit.
Attaboy.
Cindy seems... nice.
She is.
Knows hockey, too.
Penguins fan, but we're working on that.
All right. Good.
- [cheering on TV]
- Mm!
- There you go.
- Fuckin' A.
There you go.
Bonneville is giving the Bruins trouble.
He's too fast for the D.
Yeah, but he's slow on the backtrack.
They've just got to get
the puck off him first.
Mm. I bet the Bruins would love having you
on the ice a year early, huh?
They don't need me yet.
Fontano's got a few seasons left in him.
Plus, I'm not ready yet.
I want to graduate.
[announcer] We'll be right back
after this commercial break.
That's a smart choice, Garrett.
Probably good to be a little bit older
before you go pro.
Eighteen was really young for me
to be thrown in the deep end.
You'll be better equipped
to handle the pressure.
[announcer]
And we're back.
Face off won by Levy
and the Bruins set it up.
The Rangers' penalty killing
has been outstanding.
A huge factor in the game
against the Bruins today.
Okay, are you alone now?
Can we talk about Aunt Kathy's
new British accent?
And she goes by Kiara now.
It's like a whole thing.
Wasn't she in London for, like, a week?
- [boisterous chatter]
- [cell phone vibrating]
- Al?
- Huh?
Um, no, yeah, totally.
Uh, okay, what-- What's going on?
Nothing, it's just like everyone's over.
Hey, if you're busy, I...
Hey, Allie Hayes, I can hear your nails.
Who are you texting?
What? Nobody.
It's Sean.
- You're backsliding.
- Am not.
Hey, it's okay.
[laughs]
It's my dad. He, uh...
He can't find the remote again. He--
I swear he has ADHD,
but his generation's undiagnosable.
Oh, okay.
Hey, I should probably go help.
Um, love you, miss you. Gobble, gobble.
- [call disconnects]
- Oh...
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Happy Thanksgiving.
- You have an appointment?
- Hi.
No, I'm-- I'm here for Jean Logan.
And when did she check in?
Last week.
I'm sorry, new intakes
don't have visitation privileges yet.
No, I, uh... I have a delivery.
Can you just tell her it's from Jules?
[Logan] And John.
Excuse me?
I paid for this with my hard-earned cash.
Well, I'll Venmo you.
Jules and John, thank you.
[receptionist] Any particular message?
"Happy Thanksgiving," or...
Actually, uh, contraband, please.
It's a family tradition.
She'll get it.
Thank you.
It'll mean a lot to her.
Well, I'm here
because it means a lot to you.
And you're right.
She is trying.
So, what do you say we hit
the hardware store on the way back?
For real?
I mean, we gotta shore up our supplies
if we're gonna spread
the Logan love this holiday season.
In that case, we'd better hit
the Stop 'N' Shop, too.
One bag of marshmallows
ain't gonna cut it.
- [snaps fingers]
- Let's go. Come on.
[timers beeping]
♪I'm your leader, I'm your teacher
I'm your Michelin Man...♪
- Status check.
- All sides in the oven. Chef.
T-minus one hour. Chef.
- I've always wanted to say that.
- We crushed it.
Which means, mis amigos,
it is time to deep-fry the turkey!
[all cheer]
- Simms, you ready?
- Let's fucking do this.
[all] Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two,
one!
Wait, I forgot to pat-dry the bird!
Oh!
["National Treasure"
by Barns Courtney playing]
- [man] Bonfire party!
- [cheering]
[mellow dinner music playing]
You guys are in for quite a treat.
Cindy's mashed potatoes
are really something.
And dairy-free.
It's a happy accident, Hannah.
I asked Cindy to, uh,
make the mac and cheese...
- With the breadcrumbs, uh-huh.
- With the breadcrumbs.
- Like Mom used to make.
- [Phil] Mm-hmm.
I didn't want to overstep.
[Garrett] No.
No, that's-- that's very kind. Thank you.
[Phil] Thanks for coming.
It means a lot to me.
Phil, would you?
Yes, of course.
We should say a little grace
before we dig in.
Oh.
Yeah.
Lord, thank you for this wonderful bounty
you have bestowed upon us.
Thank you for bringing us all together
to enjoy this delicious meal.
And for the hands that prepared it.
We ask you to guide us
towards love and understanding.
[voice becoming muffled] To experience
what it means to be family.
In this life and the next.
[angry shouting]
Thank you, Lord.
[muffled thuds]
[normal audio resumes] Amen.
Amen.
Everything okay?
[Cindy] Yeah.
I just got a chill.
She's thin-skinned, this one.
Not built for Boston winter.
Why don't you go upstairs
and get a different sweater, darling?
No! Don't!
- Whoa!
- Just sit.
Is there a problem?
Sorry, I just...
I need a...
Um...
I'm so sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
Can we go?
Let's go.
- [breathing heavily]
- Slow down.
- Garrett, give me the keys. I'm driving.
- Hannah.
Garrett.
Please.
Wait! Your coats!
Thank you.
I'm gonna go warm up the car.
Your wrist.
It was an accident.
No, it wasn't.
I'm sorry I ruined Thanksgiving.
Your father really wanted us all to...
No, you-you-you didn't ruin...
You can't stay with him.
Look, he felt awful after.
And it's just...
- It's not who he is.
- It's exactly who he is.
He says it's not
gonna happen again, right?
He makes promises. He says he'll change.
It's a lie. It's all a fucking lie.
He doesn't care about you.
He doesn't care about me.
All he cares about is Phil fucking Graham.
That's it.
Listen to me.
My mom didn't have the chance to get out.
But you do.
Please leave.
Please.
It's complicated.
[sighs]
["Over and Over Again"
by Matthew Perryman Jones playing]
- [door closes]
- [sighs]
♪I can see you in myself ♪
♪And it's scaring me to death ♪
♪You're running from what was ♪
♪And what hasn't happened yet ♪
♪I can't be someone else ♪
♪But I can't be like this ♪
♪Any longer ♪
♪Guess you give ♪
♪What you're given...♪
Garrett.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm-- I'm fine.
No, you're not.
♪And my heart ♪
♪Just gets broken ♪
♪Over and over again...♪
Garrett, talk to me.
[breathing heavily]
[Garrett grunts]
I couldn't.
It's okay. You're okay.
I couldn't protect her.
My mom, she...
I tried, but...
I couldn't fight back.
Garrett.
Did he hit you?
[breathing shakily]
♪Guess you give ♪
♪What you're given...♪
What if, uh...
What if I'm just like him?
Hey, you're not.
You...
You would never hurt someone like that.
She was scared of me.
- Cindy?
- The way she looked at me.
That was-- That wasn't about you.
She doesn't know you.
Hey.
[sobbing]
♪Guess you give ♪
♪What you're given ♪
♪You're a world ♪
♪I would live in ♪
- I'm sorry.
- No, no.
Garrett, come on.
I should've told you everything.
- I should've told you the truth.
- You did.
You did.
♪Over and over again...♪
Garrett...
What do you need?
Let's just go home.
Yeah. Let's go home.
Okay.
[Tucker] I know this isn't exactly
what we had planned for today,
but I want to thank you all for coming
together to enjoy this once proud bird.
So, without further ado,
let's play!
["Take Me Home, Country Roads" by
Me First and the Gimme Gimmes playing]
♪Almost heaven, West Virginia ♪
♪Blue Ridge Mountains, Shenandoah River ♪
♪Life is old there, older than the trees ♪
♪Younger than the mountains
Growin' like a breeze ♪
♪Country roads, take me home ♪
[all cheer]
[in Czech] The bird broke into pieces.
- [in English] That doesn't count.
- What?!
Yes, it does.
♪Take me home, country roads ♪
♪I hear her voice in the mornin' hour
She calls me ♪
♪The radio reminds me
of my home far away ♪
♪Drivin' down the road I get a feelin'♪
[loud thump]
[all cheer]
♪Country roads, take me home ♪
♪To the place where I belong ♪
♪West Virginia, mountain mama ♪
♪Take me home...♪
- [grunts]
- It's a Logan Thanksgiving, motherfuckers!
Whoo!
["Take Me Home, Country Roads" continues]
♪Country roads, take me home ♪
♪To the place I belong ♪
♪West Virginia, mountain mama ♪
♪Take me home, country roads ♪
♪Take me home, down country roads ♪
- Mm.
This might be the best sandwich
I've ever had.
There's something about cold turkey
that just tastes better.
I think it's the fact
that you don't have to stress about it.
It's cold turkey.
Not going anywhere. It's reliable.
Wellsy...
Yeah?
Thank you.
It's just a sandwich.
Still.
Thank you.
Oh, wait.
I forgot, um...
It's, uh, it's not mac and cheese
with breadcrumbs, but...
My therapist used to say that you can't
let the bad memories erase the good ones.
[Garrett] Hmm.
It seemed like a good one.
It was.
[chuckles]
The cake was still so frozen
that we couldn't cut into it.
[cell phone rings]
Here we go.
Hey, lovebirds. Glad we got you.
Happy Thanksgiving.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
Hey, wait, let me add Dean.
We gotta get the whole fam here.
- [phone chimes]
- Hello?
Hey! What?
Are you already asleep?
It's called tryptophan, motherfuckers.
- Where are you?
- [Tucker] He's in fucking New York.
On Thanksgiving.
Yankees suck!
[all chanting]
Yankees suck! Yankees suck!
- Yankees suck!
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
Well, at least I'm not freezing
my ass off at the rink.
I don't know.
Last time I checked,
my ass was perfectly intact.
- [Tucker] Ooh, can confirm.
- You guys are so dumb.
Dean, do you never have a shirt on?
Wellsy, don't stoop to their level.
- Happy Thanksgiving!
- Good night.
Yes, Happy Thanksgiving, dorks.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
They didn't see you.
["Sue Me" by Audrey Hobert playing]
♪I knew you'd be at the party ♪
♪Drinking a Coke and Bacardi ♪
♪Not that it matters
but I'm breaking patterns ♪
♪And getting so good at Pilates ♪
♪Broke up with you in November ♪
♪Sorry, I know you remember ♪
♪Are you depressed
or are you feeling better?♪
♪'Cause you're looking like
it's the latter ♪
♪I've been so careful with you, babe ♪
♪But I'm out late ♪
♪And being a saint is exhausting ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be wanted ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be ♪
♪Just me, or does he look amazing?
♪When he's all in his Amazon Basics?♪
♪Let's rip 'em off, top to bot ♪
♪Let's rock ♪
♪Suddenly, all the lights are on ♪
♪Taking it as a sign from God ♪
♪Sign from God ♪
♪And I'm saying it over and over again ♪
♪I've been so careful with you, babe ♪
♪But your line's bait ♪
♪So I'm thinking that I'm gonna cross it
Cross it ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be wanted
Sue me, I wanna be wanted ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be
Sue me, I wanna be ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be wanted ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be toxic ♪
♪Gonna blow up your life like atomic ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be sued
Yeah, I wanna be ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be wanted ♪
♪Your face, my face ♪
♪It's kismet, babe ♪
♪And I won't make you wait
'cause I know that you want it ♪
♪Your face, my place ♪
♪It's business, babe ♪
♪And my roommate is here ♪
♪So let's ménage à trois it ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be, uh ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be, yeah ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be
Sue me, I wanna be ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be wanted ♪
[hockey team, on phone]
Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiving, dorks.
- [chuckles]
- [call disconnects]
["Sue Me" by Audrey Hobert playing]
[sighs]
They didn't see you.
♪In my bones, yeah, I know it's platonic ♪
♪Fucking your ex is iconic ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be,
sue me, I gotta be ♪
♪Sue me, I wanna be ♪
♪Wanted ♪
[Allie sighs] Night-night.
Wellsy?
["Sex Party" by Sugar Pit playing]
♪Super hot, big fun ♪
♪Lights off...♪
[laughing]
♪I wanna know
what's your fantasy ♪
♪We can make it happen
at my sex party ♪
What the fuck?
You again.
No, not me again. You again.
Are you seriously hooking up on top of me?
- Well, this is my house.
- Yeah, where you presumably have a room.
It's you from the bathroom.
Yes, we've established it's me.
Did you follow me?
I was here first.
Well, it's not my fault
you won't leave me alone.
you can't survive two seconds
- without sticking your dick in someone.
- Oh.
No offense.
- All good.
- None taken.
- I take offense.
- No one asked you.
You know, we don't really need him.
- You wanna go back to mine?
- Mm-hmm.
- [both giggling]
- Wait, no, no, wait, wait, wait!
She's leaving in a second.
- Jesus.
- [laughs]
[door closes]
[groans]
[sighs]
- Happy now?
- A little bit.
Whatever.
I'm going outside.
["Nowhere" by Mod Kiddo playing]
[exhales]
So, you're breaking up
with your boyfriend?
What? I'm not breaking up with him.
You want to, though.
You guys have been together
since your freshman year, on and off.
But now you're not sure about your future
because the dude's gonna move to Vermont
and be a boring insurance salesman
and you, you wanna act.
How?
You told pretty much everyone
tonight at karaoke.
Oh, my God.
[Dean laughs]
Okay, so what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
This whole thing.
I just...
My dad gave up so much
to be there for my mom when she...
And I know that meant everything to her.
And their relationship was beautiful.
And I want that.
But you don't want to move to Vermont.
No.
Okay, so what do you want, Allie?
I guess... I want to be in love.
But I don't want that to make it
impossible for me to, like, move to LA
or take a show to Edinburgh,
work my ass off on Broadway, you know?
I want to be able to do it all.
Even though I know it's more likely
I'll succeed at none of it.
- So...
- Hell no.
That's not dumb.
If that's what you want, go after it.
People who care about you will understand.
And if they don't,
they're not your people.
Okay, which one of your exes
taught you to be so insightful?
I don't have any exes. It's...
- the weed.
- Wait.
Dean Di Laurentis
has never had a girlfriend?
I like being the casual sex guy.
It's easy.
I have heard you're easy.
I'm Six Flags, baby.
Everybody wants a ride.
They come for a good time,
not a long time, and that's fine by me.
Is it?
[cell phone vibrates]
Looking at it won't make him text.
[laughs] No. No, you're so right.
Here, save me from myself.
[laughs]
[Allie] What?
- What are you--
- When you break up with this guy,
which you will,
you're gonna want a fun ride
to distract you.
Call me.
Sorry, dude. I don't do roller coasters.
♪I was too scared to let myself sing ♪
♪All these pieces left behind ♪
♪Making it easier to find ♪
["Bluest Flame (DJ Sliink Remix)
by Selena Gomez and Benny Blanco playing]
[inaudible]
[line ringing]
- [laughing]
- [cell phone ringing]
One sec.
Well, hello.
Yeah, I know.
I said I wouldn't call.
And yet?
[sighs] And yet.
You're calling.
I broke up with Sean.
[exhales]
I'm sorry.
Hmm. No, you're not.
No. I'm not.
I really want to call him.
But you called me instead.
I did.
You lied.
About what?
You like roller coasters.
No.
[call ends]
I fucking love roller coasters.
["Touch Me" by DivineDevine,
Shai Nowell, and 2oo7 playing]
[both moaning]
♪I just wanna know
if maybe it would be okay ♪
♪If we could get together after hours
maybe at my place...♪
[panting] Okay.
I just broke up with Sean,
and I can't hurt his feelings.
- This is a one-time thing.
- Uh-huh.
[Allie laughs]
Tell no one.
- I got it.
- Good.
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe ♪
♪Treat me like you need me...♪
[moaning]
♪Oh please baby don't be dense...♪
[panting and moaning continues]
♪Careful with my body-ody
like a brand new Benz...♪
Okay, this is the last time.
[Dean laughs]
♪...make it go just like the rest ♪
♪It gets better if you let me ♪
♪Dive into this ocean
make it ride just like a jet ski ♪
♪I can take you up
like falcon doors all on a teslie...♪
Okay, this is the last time.
♪...if you ready ♪
♪If you ready ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me...♪
[gasps]
♪Baby give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe...♪
[both laughing]
- [loud thud]
- [song fades]
[indistinct voices]
- I thought you said no one was home.
- They weren't supposed to be.
Okay, but...
[Tucker] Yeah, give me a second.
I forgot something in the bathroom.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Dude, dude, take it.
[Tucker] One second, all right.
[water splashing]
[vibrating sound]
I'm sorry. I just needed my--
Yeah, no. It's fine, man. Just...
[vibrating sound continues]
- Just go.
- Okay, I'll go.
[gasping for breath]
[song resumes]
That was absolutely the last time.
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me ♪
I just think this is really important
to Garrett that this goes well.
That's what relationships are for, honeybun.
Supporting each other.
Helping each other grow as people.
Can't all be about sex and fun.
- [cell phone vibrates]
- Mm.
Shit, the bus is almost here. Gotta go.
What? No, Garrett can just drive you.
No, it's fine. I love a bus.
You hate a bus.
It's fine.
Love you. Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving.
["Can't Get Enough" by Winifred playing]
♪I can't get enough of your love ♪
♪I can't get enough of your love...♪
All roads lead back to Dean.
This is just a ride.
Allie, this is...
- Beau Maxwell.
- Yeah.
- Joanna Maxwell's little brother.
- Oh, yeah. You know Jo?
Well, I don't "know her" know her,
but I know her in the way
that she's like a god who walks among us.
She booked a Lynn Nottage play,
like, a week after graduating,
and now she's Zendaya’s understudy
in Oleanna on Broadway.
Joanna Maxwell's, like, iconic.
You're allowed to just call her Joanna.
You know that.
Okay, sorry.
I bet you're so sick of theater talk.
You kidding? You're looking at the guy
who skipped his midterm
to go see J-Groff in Merrily.
No way. Did he spit on you?
- Oh, don't get him started.
- So much.
- I was in, like, the sixth row.
- Shut up!
Okay, favorite musical of all time.
Three, two, one.
- [both] In the Heights.
- Fuck off.
- [Allie] Stop!
- You guys just met.
Okay, okay, second favorite.
Three, two, one.
- [both] Little Shop.
- [gasps]
[laughs] Oh, my God, you guys!
What'd you say?
What?
["Omigod You Guys" playing]
♪Oh, my God ♪
♪Oh, my God, you guys...♪
What is this, hell?
You're receiving an education.
♪Elle saw right through
that salesgirl's lies...♪
What is this? What...
♪...but I'm not that blonde ♪
♪I may be in love, but I'm not stupid ♪
♪Lady, I've got eyes ♪
- Oh, my God!
- Oh!
♪Sorry, our mistake ♪
♪Courtney, take your break ♪
No, no, no.
- [turns music off]
- I can't--
Don't listen to him, Allie, all right?
Dean was indoctrinated by Joanna
just like the rest of us.
- What? I don't know what you mean by that.
- Yeah, you do.
Dean, do you sing?
- Absolutely not.
- No, Dean was more of a dancer.
- Stop. Stop.
- [laughing]
- Please tell me there's a video.
- Oh, there's a video.
I will kill you.
["Good Girls Go Bad"
by Cobra Starship plays]
[laughs]
Okay, the sunglasses are too good.
Why were there sunglasses, you ask?
No reason. No reason at all.
Okay, well, you are sending this to me.
- No, you're not.
- Obviously.
Need a ride back Friday?
Do I get to DJ?
Hell, yeah, you get to DJ.
As long as you exclusively play songs
that'll make Dean miserable.
On second thought,
I think you should take the bus.
Oh, no, no, don't listen to him, Allie.
He can hitchhike to New York.
[cell phone vibrating]
See you Friday.
[Hannah on phone] Are you alone now?
Can we talk about Aunt Kathy's
new British accent?
[Allie] And she goes by Kiara now.
It's, like, a whole thing.
Wasn't she in London for like a week?
- Al?
- Huh? Um, no, yeah, totally.
Uh, okay, what's going on?
No, nothing.
It's just like, everyone's over.
Hey, Allie Hayes, I can hear your nails.
Who are you texting?
[Allie] What? Nobody.
It's Sean. You're backsliding.
Am not.
Hey, it's okay.
It's my dad. He, um...
He can't find the remote again. He...
I swear he has ADHD,
but his generation's undiagnosable.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I should probably go help.
Love you, miss you. Gobble, gobble.
[phone beeps off]
[slow, tender music]
[Allie sighs]
[traffic ambiance]
Hey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Cute.
Yeah, my dad gets me one every year.
Holy shit.
I mean, I kind of hate you, but...
holy fucking shit.
Thanks?
No, I mean, seriously,
it's like Gwyneth Paltrow's AD tour
and the Guggenheim had a baby.
- You said this wasn't a date.
- It's not.
- Feels like a date.
It's a good bottle of wine
my parents won't miss.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Okay.
Do you want the tour?
Is it gonna make me hate you more?
Probably.
Your sister's closet
is the size of my bedroom.
I could literally live in it.
I don't know why one person
needs so many vintage bags.
Usually, we have a Basquiat there,
but it's on loan to the Whitney.
Okay, let's see it.
What?
Your big move.
Grand finale.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Fine.
There's a piano in the den,
and I usually end the tour there.
And I talk about the piano,
and then they ask if I play,
and then I say, "Kind of."
- Kind of?
- Exactly.
Then I sit down and I play "Mad World."
"Mad World?"
It's the only song I know, and it works.
It works, okay?
Can you be normal?
It's just me.
- I am being normal.
- No, you're not.
What would you be doing if I wasn't here?
You play chess by yourself?
I had to get better than Summer.
She's a chaos monster.
My dad taught us when we were little.
It was a family tradition.
That's sweet.
It's cutthroat.
Where is your family now?
St. Barts.
We have a-- We have a place there.
Sounds terrible.
Mm, doesn't it?
I'm so glad Jensen's
making us practice on Friday
because otherwise I'd be--
you know, I'd be laying on a beach
day drinking with Nick and destroying
Summer in beach volleyball.
God, you live a tough life, Di Laurentis.
The worst.
I'm sorry you can't be
with your family, though.
It seems like you miss them.
I get to be here with you.
Also...
Check.
- Come on!
- Never...
ever let the enemy distract you.
[both laugh]
Okay.
[sighs]
["girl in new york" by ROLE MODEL playing]
- Never let the enemy distract you.
- [laughs]
♪Feel me ♪
♪Ah ooh ♪
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel?♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪Your momma warned you
about the boys like me ♪
♪We're said to break your heart ♪
♪Ain't that true?♪
♪I wish you listened to your friends ♪
♪When they had told you, "Break apart"♪
♪Yeah ♪
♪Hey, it's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪It's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪It's never too late to make love ♪
♪But I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪No, I don't want to have to make up ♪
♪Ooh ♪
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel ♪
♪Feel me ♪
[chess pieces clatter]
♪Do you think about the way
we used to feel?♪
[Allie laughing]
[song ends]
Be honest, how many of your neighbors
have seen you butt naked?
Literally all of them.
[both laugh]
[cell phone rings]
Sorry, it's the guys.
Take it.
Seriously?
Hello?
[Logan on phone] Hey! What?
Are you already asleep?
It’s called tryptophan, motherfuckers.
[Hannah] Where are you?
[Tucker]
He's in fucking New York on Thanksgiving.
Yankees suck!
[all chanting] Yankees suck!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Well, at least I'm not
freezing my ass off at the rink.
[Logan] Last time I checked,
my ass was pretty intact.
- [Tucker] Can confirm.
- [Garrett] You guys are so dumb.
[Hannah] Dean, do you never
have a shirt on?
[Dean]
Wellsy, don't stoop to their level.
[all] Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiving!
Happy Thanksgiving, dorks.
[sighs]
They didn't see you.
This was supposed to be a one-time thing.
I mean, Hannah's stupid happy
and Garrett's your friend.
- Like, I can't mess that up.
- How is this messing it up?
By making her thing about me.
She deserves this.
And the second people find out we're...
- They're gonna ask what this is.
- No, no. No one's gonna ask that.
They're not gonna ask you that.
People are gonna talk
and Sean will find out,
and I can't hurt him.
Like, I called you, what,
36 hours after I broke up with him?
That's less than 48. Oh, my God.
I-I-I fucked you less than 48 hours
after breaking up with Sean.
We had fun. We were safe.
We didn't hurt anyone.
Yeah, so let's keep it that way.
Allie, come on.
[Hannah playing guitar]
I'm sorry. I have to go.
- Allie.
- [Hannah] ♪There you stood ♪
♪Behind your glasses ♪
[sighs]
♪There you stood ♪
♪There you stood, regret the past ♪
♪But regretting all the things
that past, but...♪
[laughing] Hey.
- How was practice?
- It was fine.
- Hey.
- How are you?
Good.
- I can practice this downstairs if you...
- No, stay.
I'm just gonna close my eyes.
♪There you stood behind your glasses ♪
♪In a hazy yellow world ♪
♪Alone enough for me to ask ♪
♪Just alone enough ♪
♪To feel the hurt ♪
♪The glow ♪
♪The glow of star-born eyes ♪
♪Reflect the sky ♪
♪Until I find ♪
♪I'm sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Lingering as you pour ♪
Why did you stop?
You're exhausted.
No, I like listening to you sing.
I like playing for you.
What do you think?
You sound beautiful.
About the song, the lyrics.
- You hate it.
- No.
No, I don't. At all.
I... I really like the melody.
I just... I don't get it.
I mean, well, maybe I'm just tired, but...
No, no, it's okay. I don't get it either.
[laughs] What exactly is a yellow haze?
Justin said something
about the aura of falling in love.
Oh.
Is it getting worse?
- Well, have you talked to him about it?
- Yeah.
I thought I could fix it, but, I mean,
the showcase is in two weeks.
And my gut is telling me
you should just start over.
I just can't figure out how to tell Justin
his lyrics aren't working.
Well, have you tried,
"Hey, asshole, this isn't working"?
- Right?
- No.
- [both laugh]
- No!
- You never had a problem giving me shit.
- Well, this is different. This is his art.
This is your art, too.
- And your showcase piece.
- [strums]
- Ah!
- [both chuckle]
You've got this. I believe in you.
Hmm.
♪Justin, our song fucking sucks
and we're gonna lose the showcase ♪
Oh, we got a winner here.
♪It sounds so bad, so bad ♪
Actually, you know what, usually,
I like hearing you sing, but...
♪Oh, Garrett hates my singing ♪
♪But it's okay, 'cause he loves me ♪
Yeah, I do.
I...
I love you, Wellsy.
[soft chuckle]
I love you, too.
[soft, romantic music playing]
You guys said "I love you"?
If you would have told me six months ago
that I'd be hot and single
and you'd be abandoning me to go spend
the night with Garrett Graham, I'd...
Okay, I'm the worst.
Being this happy when you're in a crisis?
I'm unpacking.
What? No, no, no, no.
You're in love. Go be in love.
Okay, you were texting Sean
over Thanksgiving.
You miss him.
Actually, I was not.
He's been giving me space.
And that's freaking you out?
Surprisingly, no.
I'm enjoying the space.
- Well, that's great.
- Totally.
Totally.
Except, if I'm enjoying the space,
then that means
I'm a terrible, shitty person
who hurts someone she supposedly loved
and then just moves on.
This is about your mom.
She said never give up on love.
And when she got sick,
my dad was there for her, you know?
Like, every step of the way.
Even when it got so hard.
So then do I just call it quits with Sean
because I'm not willing
to put in the work?
Like, did I give up on love?
Of course not.
If Sean's not the great love of your life,
that's okay.
You'll find another great love.
Or, I mean, hear me out.
Like, a fling?
Okay, uh...
flings have just not been super successful
for you, historically speaking.
What are you talking about?
I can fling.
- [laughing] Uh...
- I can!
Remember after the second Sean breakup?
All those dates with frat boys
who didn't believe in soap?
[both laugh]
Yeah, okay, well,
maybe that was my mistake.
I don't need to date someone.
I just need a distraction.
A fuck buddy.
Okay, you know I love you.
And I think you're perfect.
And I will support you no matter what.
But you, Allie Hayes,
are a card-carrying member.
I know, I'm Team Boyfriend.
Team Boyfriend.
You like snuggling and inside jokes.
You want to tell a guy about your day
and meet his mom
and watch him run a 5K
and then complain
about having to watch him run a 5K.
It's a really stupid length for a race.
Hey, look, this stuff with Sean is hard.
But whether you move on
or you get back together with him,
bottom line is, I'm here for you.
I'm Team Allie.
So just know that and believe that.
And totally ignore this giant duffle
I am packing to abandon you yet again.
You're not abandoning me.
You're going to have super hot sex
all night with a guy who loves you.
But you're not taking that.
It's mine.
Maybe "all you can eat"
was not my most romantic idea?
[laughs]
Wellsy.
Saw you guys on Fifth Line.
Is Jules--
- They're everywhere.
- Like God.
We're supposed to be on a date.
Oh, wow, you really splurged, G.
- This one was my treat.
- Oh, then, rescinded.
So, how was y'all's break?
First time meeting Papa Graham, right?
Yeah, it was... it was fine.
Yeah. Family. Sucks.
Did you at least get that signed jersey
for the Hurricanes fundraiser?
That Phil Graham merch room is legit.
Uh, not this year.
What's the Hurricanes?
It's a local youth hockey program.
We do a fundraiser for them every year.
Logan was a Lil 'Cane.
[all laugh]
Oh, is that still happening?
I thought the venue fell through.
Yeah, well, they double booked.
I'm trying to figure it out.
Hey, we were really
counting on that Phil donation.
I... I can reach out.
I'll sign a jersey,
and you can auction that.
Okay, big shot.
You're not in the pros yet.
I didn't mean...
I'm trying to help.
Uh, what if you did it at Malone's?
That's...
- Really?
- Yeah, I can run it by Della.
I'm sure she'll be happy to help.
What kind of vibe were you thinking?
[band playing "Dirty Little Secret"]
[crowd cheering]
♪I'll keep you, my dirty little secret ♪
♪Dirty little secret ♪
♪Don't tell anyone ♪
♪Or you'll be just another regret ♪
♪Just another regret ♪
♪Hope that you can keep it ♪
♪My dirty little secret ♪
♪Dirty little secret,
dirty little secret ♪
- ♪Who has to know?♪
♪Who has to know?♪
[crowd cheers and whoops]
Give it up for After Hours, everybody.
[all cheer]
And a big round of applause
to my buddy John Logan
for putting on this killer event!
[all cheer]
Look at him.
Doesn't get any better-looking than that.
And he's single, ladies.
And we've already raised 2,000 bucks
for those Lil 'Canes,
but we want to raise a hell of a lot more
for those guys.
So get drunk, hit up our silent auction,
and get some cool shit.
Sadly, the photo booth is out of order,
but there's still a lot of fun to be had.
The band is taking requests.
So scan those QR codes and let them know
what songs you want to hear.
- All right, you guys ready?
- [all cheer]
Let's have some fun.
♪Let me know what I've done wrong ♪
♪When I've known this all along...♪
So, what'd you think?
"Dirty Little Secret"?
That was mine.
Subtle.
Just reminding you in case you forgot,
I can keep a secret.
I get that you're worried,
but there's no reason
we can't just keep doing
what we've been doing.
- Hooking up all over campus?
- Having fun.
Just meet me in the bathroom
in, let's say, five minutes.
You're delusional.
Everyone we know is here.
And I'm not that kind of girl.
But you want to be.
Take these to your boys.
For the record, I am not delusional.
I just know what I want.
Go.
[Justin] ♪Go around a time or two ♪
♪Just to waste my time with you...♪
You see how quick they are?
They're going to capitalize on mistakes.
Control is key. Tucker, you cannot
let them get a step on you.
- Not a single one.
- No, Graham, I'm not having this.
Put that thing away.
We have St. A's tomorrow.
We don't go to bars
to gripe and moan about hockey.
We go to bars to score, okay?
What the fuck is wrong with you people?
- Fellas.
- Thank the Lord.
Beau, tell them to stop
talking hockey shit.
Oh, no, no. Keep talking hockey shit.
That's why I came over here.
- [Tucker] Why?
- Puck bunnies, 11 o'clock.
- Hey guys.
- Oh, hello.
Hi, I'm Beau. Nice to meet you.
- ♪These sleeping dogs won't lie...♪
- Here you go.
♪And all I've tried to hide ♪
♪It's eating me apart...♪
We need more pigs in a blanket,
napkins, and--
That really doesn't bother you?
No, I trust Garrett.
And the puck bunnies
are actually kind of cool.
Yeah.
They know what they want.
God, it's so hot when someone
knows what they want.
If you really want a fling,
I think you should go for it.
- You think?
- Yeah, you're single.
Embrace that.
Just pick someone
who will never catch feelings for you.
Someone down for anything.
Like the anti-Sean.
Yeah, you make a good point.
Yeah, someone with zero expectations
who just wants sex.
Just sex.
[crowd cheering]
All right, we've got another request.
[whoops and cheers]
This one goes out to Maverick.
[band playing "U + Ur Hand"]
♪Check it out
going out on the late night ♪
♪Looking tight, feeling nice
it's a cock fight ♪
♪I can tell, I just know
that it's going down ♪
♪Tonight...♪
I love a throwback.
Right?
♪You don't really want
to mess with me tonight ♪
♪Just stop and take a second ♪
♪I was fine
before you walked into my life ♪
♪'Cause you know it's over ♪
♪Before it began ♪
♪Keep your drink, just give me the money ♪
♪It's just you and your hand tonight ♪
♪Midnight, I'm drunk ♪
♪I don't give a fuck ♪
♪Wanna dance by myself
guess you're outta luck ♪
[cell phone vibrating]
♪Back up, I'm not the one ♪
♪Buh-bye...♪
Okay, back to work.
♪Listen up, it's just not happening ♪
♪You can say what you want
to your boyfriends ♪
♪Just let me have my fun tonight ♪
♪All right...♪
Is that your answer?
Take a look around.
Any girl would be happy
to stick her tongue down your throat.
I don't want any girl.
Well, guess you're stuck with your hand.
♪'Cause you know it's over ♪
♪Before it began ♪
♪Keep your drink, just give me the money ♪
♪It's just you and your hand ♪
- [all cheer]
- Thanks.
This next one is for fans
of One Direction.
Hey, Wellsy.
[band playing "Kiss You"]
I need those freshmen
selling raffle tickets
and not listening to GHA over there
talking strategy.
GHA?
Uh, General Hard Ass.
[laughs]
[Hannah] What's so important
about this game tomorrow?
St. Anthony's?
Ever since they beat Eastwood,
they've been gunning
for our top spot in the conference.
- Are they close?
- They're on a ten-game streak.
So they're close.
If we lose, they'll be number one
in the conference.
Shit.
That's what's in his head right now.
But there's nothing we
can do about that tonight.
We need people drunk and happy
and spending money.
[laughs]
Can you help?
Aye, aye, captain.
Thanks.
And, uh...
For all this.
What are friends for?
[Justin] ♪Oh, I just wanna take you
anywhere that you'd like ♪
♪We could go out any day, any night ♪
♪Baby, I'll take you there...♪
They've scored at least three goals
by end of the first.
I mean, their zone is suffocating--
A little bird told me that you freshmen
need to get off your asses
and go sell some raffle tickets.
It's Logan.
Was it Logan?
- It was Logan.
- [laughs]
Okay, this is a party.
And?
And parties are supposed to be fun.
Well, so is winning.
Jensen wants me to step up more
as captain, so I'm stepping up.
Well, others have suggested
you might be boring everyone to death.
I'm guessing that was also Logan.
This fundraiser means a lot to him.
It's sweet.
Sweet doesn't win games.
Okay, I heard carbs are good, though.
Thank you.
♪And you just wanna take me home...♪
Have you talked to him yet?
Uh, yeah, no, sound check
didn't really seem like the time to be...
like, "Justin, I don't like
your lyrics or our song,
which, by the way, used to be about you,
but I don't have a crush on you anymore,
so I really don't know
what it should be about,
but it should not be about yellow haze."
Hmm.
Well, maybe we work on the wording
of that a little.
- [laughs]
- [crowd cheers]
- [cymbal crashes]
- Okay, party people.
A few of our silent auction items
are currently going for way undervalue,
so if you act fast,
you could get them for a steal.
A steal. Now, um, I know there are
mostly Boston fans in the house.
- That's right!
- [boisterous cheering]
And as a born and bred New Yorker,
I happen to think those people
are living a sad, desperate existence--
Ow! New York!
- Get out of here!
- [Dean] Hey, Della.
We love you, but this one...
This one.
This one's part of the family.
I have box seats
to a New York Rangers game
and a meet-and-greet
with the legend himself,
Phil Graham!
[all cheer]
[Dean] Yeah, so don't be cheap!
- Did you...?
- Nope.
[Dean] ...for all the beautiful,
intelligent supporters...
And that's right, Rangers fans,
I'm looking at you.
Garrett.
Did you call my fucking dad?
Hey, I hope your son enjoys the camp.
Thanks.
What the hell, dude? He just donated.
Did you call my dad?
Look, Phil gives something every year.
All right? You obviously
just didn't ask him right.
That's not...
- He's...
- A self-centered pompous asshole?
Yeah, my mom's in rehab
for the fifth time.
I get it, okay?
But who cares, all right?
It's for a good cause.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You never once considered
why I didn't want you to call.
Are you kidding?
All we ever do
is think about what you want.
Do you know how much hockey costs?
Genuine question.
Because these kids need the money.
I needed the money.
This fundraiser
is the only fucking reason I'm here.
It's not all about money.
Spoken like a person
with a shit ton of it.
[Dean] Back for a second set.
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for After Hours!
[crowd cheers]
All right, we're gonna take a break
from requests.
We're gonna play something
brand-new for you, it's an original.
Written with one and only Hannah Wells.
[band plays rock music]
You didn't tell me
he was going to sing your song.
Oh, you didn't know. Shit.
Hey, well, on the bright side,
you're about to find out if it's any good.
Maybe people will love it.
♪There you stood behind your glasses ♪
♪In a hazy yellow world...♪
Oh, God.
♪Alone enough for me to ask just ♪
♪Alone enough to feel the hurt ♪
♪Echoes weaving through the walls ♪
♪They're keeping secrets in the night ♪
♪We are indivisible ♪
♪Together we're a number prime ♪
♪The glow ♪
♪The glow of star-born eyes
reflect the sky ♪
♪Until I find I'm sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze ♪
♪Lingering as it pours ♪
♪Yellow, yellow rain ♪
♪What was it all for?♪
Yellow rain?
Like pee?
♪Sinking into your ♪
♪Yellow, yellow haze...♪
No, it-it's catchy. It's catchy.
♪Yellow, yellow ♪
[door opens]
There you are.
What'd you think?
What did-- [laughs]
The song is not ready.
Well, I mean, I thought--
I thought it went well.
No, it's supposed to grab people.
Like, make them feel things.
Yeah, they seemed really into it.
The lyrics don't even make sense.
They're poetic.
No, we need to start again.
From the beginning.
No.
What?
Hannah, stop fucking with my head.
I made something I'm proud of.
I performed it.
I put my heart on the line.
And you go on and on
about how you don't feel it.
How you don't connect.
How the song doesn't sound like you.
Of course it doesn't.
Because you refuse
to put yourself in this.
You...
You want to feel something, Hannah?
Try writing your own lyrics.
I'm done.
[somber music playing]
And in first place...
- [crowd cheering]
- [rhythmic pounding on table]
Grace Ivers.
[cheers and applause]
Please collect your prizes
from Della at the bar.
Congratulations to all
of our lucky winners tonight.
A lot of people got what they wanted,
but not all of us.
So if there's any last-minute requests,
changes of heart,
remember that the photo booth
is out of order.
["Touch Me" by DivineDevine,
Shai Nowell, and 2oo7 playing]
Um, okay, yeah. Good night.
Good night.
[all cheer]
He's been weird tonight, right?
So weird.
♪I cannot wait to get around you
see that look upon your face ♪
♪Touch me ♪
♪Squeeze me
treat me like you need me ♪
♪Baby make it easy ♪
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby give it all ♪
♪I want to believe...♪
Change your mind?
No. Maybe.
- Just every time we do this, I feel so--
- Amazing.
Bad. I feel bad.
- Guilty.
- Wait, are you Catholic?
No. I'm just a girl.
I have to think about
what everyone else feels
before I can figure out what I'm feeling.
And I can't even do that right now
because this fucking breakup
is totally messing with my head.
- I don't even know what to think.
- Then don't. Don't think.
Tell me what you want.
Allie Cat.
This is not a relationship, okay?
No strings, no feelings, just sex.
Just fucking kiss me.
♪Baby, make it easy ♪
♪Backs against the wall ♪
♪Baby, give it all ♪
♪I wanna believe it ♪
♪Treat me like you need me...♪
Meet at mine in an hour.
♪How I crystallize ♪
♪Everything I see ♪
♪Through my rose tint eyes ♪
This is a party.
♪It's just the way I feel...♪
Parties are supposed to be fun.
Are you having fun?
Not really. You?
Yeah, not really.
Justin and I broke up.
Oh, not words I was expecting to hear
from my girlfriend about another guy.
I have two weeks to write another song.
There's plenty of time.
You and Logan gonna be okay?
We'll be fine.
Yesterday when he asked about your dad,
it could have been an opening
to tell him.
Tell him what?
About Thanksgiving?
What you told me.
Phil's a dick.
Logan knows that. Everybody does.
That's all they have to know.
Yeah, well, what happens
when Phil shows up to a game?
When I win, he nods.
And when I lose, he says nothing.
He won't be that hard to ignore.
I think you should tell someone.
Jensen, Logan.
- [sighs]
- They care about you.
I don't need them to know.
I mean, that's why I have you.
I trust you.
- You wanna go home?
- I wish.
I told Della I'd oversee cleanup,
and I really should get started
on the song.
Okay, you go.
I'll stay at my place tonight.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You get some sleep for the game tomorrow.
Big scary game against big scary St. A's.
[both laugh]
You scare the shit out of them, you know.
Look how hard
they're trying to please you.
[Garrett] They're not trying to please me.
They're trying to win.
Which you will.
See you tomorrow, okay?
I'll be in the stands with the sign
that says, "I heart Garrett Graham."
Might be kind of hard to spot you.
There are a lot of those signs.
[laughs]
- I hate you.
- I love you, too.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
♪Twist it up, make it art ♪
♪Oh, you twist it up, twist it up ♪
♪Looking for something real ♪
♪Twist it up, make it art ♪
♪Oh, you twist it up, twist it up ♪
♪Looking for something real ♪
["Cinderella" by Remi Wolf playing]
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
[knock on door]
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby...♪
Fuck me.
[both laugh]
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
♪Low tide, moon's so bright ♪
♪Moving my hips from left to right ♪
♪My, my, check my phone ♪
♪Feel it in my belly
when you're driving home like ♪
♪Low tide, moon's so bright ♪
♪Moving my hips from left to right ♪
♪My, my, check my phone ♪
♪Feel it in my belly
when you're driving home like ♪
♪Like Cinderella making babies
on the company's dime...♪
Hannah, I got a bar to close.
Sorry. I'm going.
♪We're making pennies out of paper ♪
♪Better find a new slime ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby ♪
♪Me and the boys in the hotel lobby...♪
[vibrating]
- Where you going?
- [both laughing]
- Oh, shit.
- What?
Okay, wait, you gotta go. Like, right now.
Hannah's coming home.
- I don't--
- It doesn't matter. You can't be here.
- Okay.
- Hustle!
- You look so good.
Shut up.
[laughs]
- Go.
- Okay, bye.
[sighs]
[knock on door]
[Allie] Oh, shit.
You forgot your jacket...
Wow.
Sean, I...
We just broke up, Al.
- I wasn't...
- Yeah, you were.
You really can't be alone, can you?
No, Sean. It wasn't like that, I swear.
Oh, come on. Sean!
- Night, guys. Good luck tomorrow.
- Thanks.
Yeah, if you're on the ice with Delaney,
you just gotta do what G says.
He can't hold up against all the pressure.
Who?
St. A's new center, Aaron Delaney.
Dude's a beast.
[heartbeat thumping]
[Hannah gasps]
[breathing heavily]
♪I've been numb, I'm dying to feel ♪
♪Touching a grave that isn't real ♪
♪Touching a ghost that I can't see ♪
♪But the ghost is me ♪
[echo of crowd cheering]
♪A melting candle on a piece of cake ♪
♪I can't tell if I'm awake ♪
♪There is a ghost that stares at me ♪
♪But the ghost is me ♪
♪The ghost is me ♪
♪Fall through the floor ♪
♪Walk through walls ♪
♪Looking at pictures in the hall ♪
♪Staring in mirrors so I can see ♪
♪That the ghost is me ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪Showing up when you least expect ♪
♪A little girl that died in a wreck ♪
♪Alive again and finally free ♪
♪The ghost is me ♪
[exhales]
[song instrumentals continue]
[song fades out]
[crowd cheering]
[announcer] Delaney with the puck!
He's trying to fend them off!
Delaney shoots!
He scores!
Ransom wins!
[cheers and applause]
Hannah. Hannah.
We won.
[band playing percussive music]
["This Too Shall Pass" by OK Go playing]
♪When the morning comes...♪
Uh, excuse me, gentlemen.
The UN has declared
an international band emergency,
and they say that my dad
is the only man for the job.
An international band emergency?
Have they called Prince?
They tried, but he is famously dead.
Good God, this is worse than I thought.
- Sorry, guys.
- [Hannah laughs]
You're so weird.
Also, can we hit Dairy Queen
on the way home?
What? Are you saying the international
band emergency was a ruse?
Is Prince even dead?
Han! Honey, you were phenomenal.
Uh, how was I?
Mm, you were okay, too.
Ah, yes!
[laughs]
Okay, can I help you?
[Greg] I just want to know
how your new song is coming along.
[breathing heavily]
It must be going well,
because you missed three cues tonight.
The muse waits for no one.
[Greg]
Oh, does the muse play clarinet?
Because we're looking
for a new alternate first chair.
[panting]
[woman] Just write, Hannah.
[breathing heavily]
["This Too Shall Pass" playing
over headphones]
- [knock on door]
- [Allie] Han?
I'm gonna skip the game today.
Got an extra monster cookie
if you want one.
[knocking]
Hannah?
Babe, you okay?
[music stops]
Yeah, yeah, sorry, I'm...
I'm not super hungry.
Uh, don't worry about me, I'm-- I'm good.
[Allie] Okay, love you.
[dramatic music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
- [heart pounding]
[breathes sharply]
[Dean]
Look at those smug motherfuckers.
Their ten-game streak ends now.
[exhales] Not if their new center
has anything to say about it.
[Dean] Please, he's been skating
in fucking cornfields.
- Iowa, or whatever.
- [Birdie] Indiana.
Kid's fast as fuck. Physical, too.
Doesn't matter. Nothing's getting past us.
[speaking Czech]
[Dean] Yeah, see? Simms gets it.
Yeah, come on, boys.
Let's get it.
Fuck, yeah. Let's go.
[door closes]
He also doesn't back down from anything.
Same as Garrett.
Oh, shit. Papa Graham's mad early.
No pressure, man.
Garrett, good to see you.
[sighs]
Looks like you got
a tough one out there today.
- Feeling good?
- [door opens]
Yeah, you know what?
Don't worry about me. I'm ready.
Sorry, I left my phone in the car.
It's okay.
Hi, Garrett.
[gasps]
Cindy.
Good luck out there today.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[dramatic music playing]
[cell phone vibrates]
[vibrating continues]
[breathes sharply]
[Allie] Sean, I am so sorry
that you had to find out like that.
I never meant to hurt your feelings.
But also, literally, how dare you suggest
that I am incapable of being alone?
Like, that's so fucked of you,
Sean. So fucked.
Again, could not be more sorry.
- Please just call me back or text me or--
- [voicemail beeps]
[computerized voice]
Please hang up or press one to re-record.
- Oh.
- Allie, what are you doing here?
Uh, this is the drama building.
I'm in the correct place.
What are you doing here?
This is perfect. You're not busy, right?
I need a huge favor.
No, Beau, sorry, I can't
take on anyone else's stress today.
I am emotionally raw.
I'm the shell of a woman.
Okay. Okay. Thank you, Ira.
You, too, Ira.
Bye, Ira.
Sorry about that.
Ira is not great at ending conversations.
Jo, this is Allie. Allie--
You're Joanna Maxwell.
Yeah, Allie's a fan.
Nice to meet you.
Wait, are you Allie Hayes?
Don't we have the same agent?
You know who I am.
Joanna Maxwell knows who I am.
Well, you can just call me Jo.
Yo, respectfully, there is literally
no way I can make that happen.
- [chuckles]
- Joanna's back here doing a master class
with the seniors,
because she's so famous.
Definitely not famous.
And because she's so famous,
she has this big self-tape.
- It's a same-day audition.
- Last time I read with Jo,
I got in trouble
for my voice
- being "stiff and distracting."
- Well...
So, I thought that maybe
you could read with her, Allie,
so I could go do literally anything else.
- [scoffs]
- What?
- Beau...
- Uh-huh?
You don't just ask someone
to be your reader.
- There's an etiquette, fool.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry about him.
I couldn't ask you to do that.
It would derail your entire day.
No, no, no, derail it, please.
Seriously, it is not a problem.
I would be honored
to read with the Joanna Maxwell.
- [whistle blows]
- This is it, folks.
The start of our
long-awaited game with St. A's
and their new center, Aaron Delaney.
[rock music playing]
[Jules]
And we're underway here in the first.
Hawks take possession.
[grunts]
- [crowd groans]
- [Jules] Oh, shit.
Brutal hit from Aaron Delaney.
Seems the new guy's fitting right in with
St. A's legendary trash-talking bullies.
- [grunts]
- [crowd groans]
- [groans]
- Whoa! How is that not a penalty?
Hawks regain possession.
Graham starts out
from behind his own net and...
- Oh! Delaney says, nope.
- [crowd groans]
[Jules]
He shoots... and beats
Simms's blocker side
for the goal.
[crowd jeering]
Come on, Graham.
It's not fun if you don't fight back.
Fuck you.
[laughs]
Take it easy, princess.
Whoo!
Hey, come on, bro.
- Shake it off. You got this.
- [crowd audio fades and distorts]
[Garrett]
Wellsy, where are you?
- [breathing heavily]
- [woman] Just write, Hannah.
[vibrating]
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
- [sniffling, gasping]
- [vibrating continues]
- [stick hit echoes]
- [Jules] Nasty cross-check by Delaney.
Vipers are absolutely dominating
the Hawks right now.
Hawks can't play the zone.
Vipers collect the puck
in the Hawks' zone.
Are you kidding?
The Vipers are relentless.
There's is a slashing penalty
on St. A's 29.
- [woman] Just write, Hannah.
- There's Delaney again.
What the actual fuck?
Delaney shoots.
[breathing heavily]
[Jensen] Well, that wasn't
the first period I was looking for.
Graham, Delaney's shadowing you.
Move the puck. Look at Birdie and Dean.
We got two periods left.
Your turnovers are killing us.
- Don't worry about us. We're good.
- [imitates buzzer]
Fuck that. I'm not good.
[Jensen] Let's just work as a team
and try not to do it all ourselves.
- No more one-on-one sloppiness.
- I got it, okay? Fine.
Hey, cut the attitude, Graham.
I mean it.
Hey, Delaney's trying
to take you out of the game,
so take their defenders out, too.
As soon as the puck comes in,
- you just get rid of it.
- Who died and made you coach?
I'm out there, too, man.
Okay, then worry about yourself,
all right?
Okay, fine.
I don't know what your problem is,
but I suggest you do
whatever it takes to work it out.
Fucking quick.
[exhales heavily]
[exhales]
[phone line rings]
[cell phone vibrating]
[soft piano playing]
[piano volume increases]
[gasps]
Sorry. Sorry. Uh...
I-I couldn't be in my room, so I came.
And I-I heard.
Who was that you were playing?
It's actually an original.
Part of a series I wrote
when my son first went off to day care.
[chuckles]
Kind of exploring the emptiness of time.
Wow. Y--
- You're incredible.
- Ah.
I would hope so.
- [plays notes]
- That's why I'm here, right?
You okay?
Yeah, I finally get it.
When you said,
"Write music that lets people in."
Like, just now, I-I didn't know
it was about your son, but I felt it.
That's a sweet compliment.
Just having a hard time taking it,
because of the general melancholy.
Uh, it's...
It's just that I don't think
I could ever write anything
that comes close to doing that.
- Come on, that's not true.
- No, it is.
I-I can't do what you do.
Letting people in.
- Hannah--
- No, it's okay.
Um, I made a mistake trying to do this.
Anyway, uh, it's been an honor
to be a part of your class.
I really hope we can keep in touch.
Not on my student email,
because if I don't do the showcase,
then I-- I won't be here
next semester, but, um...
I'll send you my old one.
It's a Yahoo, for some reason.
[Daveed]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold up.
Hannah, Hannah, Hannah,
Hannah, Hannah.
Just, if you don't come back here
right now, okay?
I'm still your advisor for as long
as you're here, so, talk to me.
Get your money's worth.
[exhales]
I have been doing this a while.
I mean...
Like, doesn't it hurt?
Doesn't what hurt?
Ripping yourself open over and over again.
Letting people see all the weird,
jagged pieces of you.
Is that what it feels like?
Yeah, well, it doesn't feel good.
I don't subscribe to the notion
that art has to be painful.
In fact, if done right,
allowing people into our truth,
that can even be healing.
Yeah, I don't-- I don't know about that.
In-- In my experience,
whenever I tell someone my truth, it...
it ends badly.
Well, that doesn't mean we have
to close ourselves off for good.
It doesn't?
No, that just means we have to cling
to the people who see us and smile.
There has to be someone like that
in your life, right?
[soft, tender music playing]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there is.
Then, with love, what the hell
are you doing here talking to me?
- [laughs]
- Taking up my rehearsal time.
[laughs] Yeah, you're--
You're right.
Sorry. Um, I'm gonna...
Thank you. Thank you, Daveed.
Anytime.
- [voicemail beeps]
- [Garrett] Hey, hey, it's me.
Um, are-- are you okay?
Or did I-- did I do something wrong?
Just, you said you were coming,
and you're not here.
And I-I really wish you were here.
You always help me
get out of my head, and...
I could just really use a Coach Wellsy
pep talk right now, so...
Yeah, just...
Uh, if you could just
let me know you're okay.
I'm here.
Okay.
[crowd cheering]
Heavy into the second.
Briar's trailing 3-1.
You can tell Graham is frustrated
with this incessant coverage.
- Move it!
- Fuck you!
Up, G.
- You got Logan!
- Come on, man! Get rid of it!
- You got Logan! Move it!
- Heads up, G!
- Can't keep up, Daddy's boy?
- Fuck!
- [Delaney] Come on, then!
- [Jules] Woof.
Someone hold Garrett's hair back,
because he is getting sloppy.
[Logan] Go! Go! Go!
[Jules] Delaney banks the puck to himself
past Graham and breaks up the ice.
No! Fuck!
[Jules] Delaney sends the puck
behind the Hawks' net.
The Hawks are on their heels again.
The pass comes out front
to Delaney, and...
- [groans]
- [crowd jeering]
[whistle blows]
[player] Hey, we need the trainer!
[Jules]
What an absolutely brutal hit from Delaney
and a brutal end
to the second period for the Hawks.
Birdie sure got his bell rung.
Let's hope he's okay.
[Logan] How you doing, Birdie?
[Birdie] Everything's so fucking bright.
Okay. You're not going back in.
Rogers, you're up.
I'm gonna put you on D for the third.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Just keep your feet moving. Di Laurentis.
Yeah, I'll look out for him, Coach.
- Fuck Aaron Delaney, man.
- There's no way that was an accident.
He knew exactly what he was doing.
Okay, guys, anything can happen
in 20 minutes.
[Tucker] Maybe we switch to a one-two-two
trap to really cut off their outlets,
amp up the pressure?
[Logan] That won't work.
It doesn't matter what we do.
We were getting our asses kicked
before Birdie got domed.
- We know what the problem is.
- You got something to say?
You know you're locked off.
I told you to get rid of it.
- Logan, come on.
- No, everyone is thinking it.
Garrett Graham's got to do it all himself,
and now, we're down by two.
Stay in your lane, Josh.
Guys, come on. It's not that deep.
No, it fucking is for some of us, Dean.
It is that deep.
I'm not gonna let us lose this game,
because Phil Graham's son
gets to do whatever he fucking wants.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
- Come on.
- You gonna fight me now?
Hey! Calm down.
[Logan] We're on the same team, G.
Don't you get that?
You're not the only one
who can play hockey.
who's been busting their ass,
and you're not the only one who wants
to beat these motherfuckers!
We are on the same team!
Logan, just give him a second
to calm down.
I don't need your fucking help, Tucker.
[breathes deeply]
[tense music playing]
Fuck.
[sighs]
- Hey.
- [door closes]
[sighs]
Need a pep talk?
What's going on?
Are you okay? Where were you?
I'm fine.
- I called, but you didn't--
- No, I know. I'm...
I'm sorry. I should have texted.
I w-- I was dealing with something
that kind of took over for a minute there,
um, but I'm-- I'm here now.
You're dealing with what?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Okay?
Just, you know, it didn't matter
as much as being here for you.
[sighs]
Please just text me next time.
I was worried about you.
I know. I know.
Okay, focus up.
Graham, what's going on out there?
Everything.
I'm playing like shit,
getting pressured like crazy,
making stupid mistakes.
Everybody's counting on me
to be in control,
but I just got in a stupid fight
with Logan, because...
Your dad's here.
[sighs]
With Cindy.
We can't let him win.
It gives him power.
This is how we win. We just--
We show up, and we live our lives.
- Okay? We can do that.
- [sighs]
Right?
Yeah.
And as for everything else,
we can just start with the small stuff
and work your way up.
Small stuff?
Yeah, whatever that means for hockey.
I guess the small stuff
could be stop playing like shit.
[both laugh]
- Okay, yeah. I can do that.
- [chuckles]
Delaney's kicking my ass, though.
Guy's a fucking monster.
[inhales sharply and sighs]
Wellsy.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I'm...
- [soft, tender music playing]
I'm good.
I promise.
Okay.
[crowd cheering]
Hey, Graham.
I love you.
I love you, too.
[tender music continues]
[tense music plays]
[buzzer]
Graham and Delaney meet center ice,
ready to start the final period.
[whistle blows]
What? Nothing to say this time?
[crowd cheering]
[man] Delaney, you suck!
Hey, that hit was bullshit, man.
You all right?
- Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
- I got you.
[upbeat percussive music]
[Jules] Hawks in their own zone.
Vipers forecheck, recover the puck,
and get it back to the point.
Clutch deflection by Tucker
gets the puck back to Graham.
But can he get past Delaney?
Graham puts on the brakes,
spins and drops to Tucker.
- Tucker shoots.
- [Tucker] Yes!
- Scores! Hawks score!
- [crowd cheering]
Whoo!
[rock music playing]
Let's go! Yes!
Good pass, G!
Let's go!
[players cheering]
Whoo!
I like that! I like that, Tuck!
Okay, Briar, looks like we've decided
to get off our knees and stop sucking.
[whistle blows]
And... cut.
Wow. Okay.
Holding back tears?
I mean, such a smart choice.
Beau wasn't kidding.
You really are
a much better reader than he is.
And you have cuter clothes.
Thank you for this, by the way.
You got it. Of course.
God, it is just so fun to be hanging out
with someone who's, like,
actually doing the thing, you know?
You're auditioning for a TV show
on your day off from Broadway.
It's so chic.
Oh, I think you'd feel differently
if you saw me hiding my pin curls
under an old baseball hat
with my falsies barely hanging on.
Ah, you've got to know
how cool that sounds.
Broadway's hard, dude.
It's... Like, I know I'm super lucky.
But, oh, my God, I'm also so exhausted.
[laughs]
I don't have time for anyone.
My dating life is in shambles.
That, I can relate to.
Ooh.
I smell token straight boy drama
in the theater department.
No, it's, like...
Okay, well, can we still
be peers in the industry
even if I tell you all my messy bullshit?
Oh, that's literally the only way
we'll be peers in the industry.
[both laugh]
My ex, like, found out
I hooked up with someone
and just got, like,
all scrunch-faced and, like,
just basically accused me
of not being able to be alone.
Ugh.
Boys are so silly.
So, you fucked a little.
It's not like
you're in a new relationship.
Thank you. I've hooked up
with this new guy a couple of times.
But this isn't about him. It's about me.
- I am capable of being single.
- Yeah.
I mean, you're sleeping
with other people, too, right?
[panting and laughing]
Totally.
- Except...
- Except, you're not.
It's okay.
It'd be different if you and this new guy
were texting all the time or had, like,
cute, gross nicknames
or something like that.
[vibrating]
Oh, no, you do.
So, how long have you been
hooking up with new guy?
Like, a month... ish.
Bitch, I hate to break it to you.
You're in another relationship.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Hey, I can see
I've caused some turmoil here.
We need to get off campus.
Somewhere with alcohol.
[chuckles]
["A-Game" by Chloe Qisha playing]
- [bartender] ID?
- Hey, can I do an old fashioned?
Thank you.
Nice fake.
Excuse me?
Just saying,
it's not the worst one I've seen.
Oh, no. No, this... This is real.
Please. I work at a bar.
I can spot one, like, five booths away.
Maybe you need any glasses,
because it's definitely not fake.
Your name is Carter St. James.
The Fifth.
Mm. Yeah.
Nobody's named that.
That's a name from Glee.
Well, I guess I'm lucky they don't ask
too many questions here.
[bartender] There you go.
I guess I am, too.
What are you doing?
That guy was hitting on you.
- So?
- [laughs]
Look, you want to prove
you're not in a relationship?
The best way to do that is
to sleep with someone new
who you'll never see again.
I don't think hopping to yet another man
is the answer.
You're a relationship girlie, right?
The best way to get over that
is to have no-strings-attached fun.
But there legit has to be no strings.
And that guy has "no fucking strings"
written all over him.
I don't know, having sex with someone
and not getting to know them at all, like,
doesn't it feel a little...
Slutty?
- Yeah, that's part of it.
- I was gonna say "meaningless."
Allie, you're in college.
You have the rest of your life
to have meaningful sex.
Don't you want to know what being single
and slutty has to offer you?
Hey, you with the cheekbones.
Hey! Hey, hey, what are you doing?
♪Tonight, tonight,
tonight, tonight...♪
What's up?
If my friend wanted to have really hot,
meaningless sex with you,
but the only caveat was that you couldn't
learn anything about each other,
and you had to promise
not to call her after,
would you be cool with that?
Oh, yeah, most definitely.
[Joanna] Great. Buy her a drink.
This one's mine now.
♪And maybe I'll be your number one girl ♪
What do you say?
♪Tonight, tonight,
tonight tonight ♪
[crowd cheering]
Coming out of the last time-out
with two minutes left,
it's looking real good for the Hawks.
Graham and Logan
have been having a blast out there.
We love that for them.
And more importantly, we love it for me.
[disquieting, tense music playing]
[whistle blows]
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Let's fucking go, baby.
- Any final words of wisdom, Cap?
- Let's win this fucking thing.
- Let's go!
- Whoo!
- [Jules] This is it, folks.
It's looking like the last face-off
of the game.
[Delaney] Hey, man.
Everything they say is true.
Playing against you has been really fun.
Yeah, all right.
Graham, you know what's gonna
be even better than me beating you?
What's that?
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Beating you in front of that lying slut.
[music distorts, intensifies]
[distorted clatter]
- [gasps]
- [music cuts out]
[players shouting]
[whistle blowing]
[players] Garrett! Garrett!
[whistle blows]
[music intensifies]
[gasps]
[coach sighs]
[grunts softly]
[groans lightly]
What are they going to do?
The NCAA?
Guess we'll find out.
Aren't you gonna
yell at me or something?
Why would I yell at you
if I need you to actually hear me?
- Coach...
- Garrett,
you're on the brink of greatness.
But I can't help you get there
if you're not in it for the right reasons.
And after that hot-headed bullshit?
I'm not sure that you are.
[Jensen sighs]
Either way, I won't condone
that kind of behavior on my ice.
As of now,
you're suspended for four games.
- [door opens, closes]
- [exhales sharply]
[intense music plays]
[door slams shut]
[Garrett sighs]
Garrett.
No, we have an agreement.
I don't win, you don't talk to me.
Clearly, this is an exception.
- Move.
- No, hang on. Just listen.
[sighs]
I'm proud of you.
- What?
- That was some tough old-school hockey.
[chuckles]
I just got suspended.
Four games.
Yeah, that is not ideal.
But hey, it happens, right?
You get worked up. You lose your cool.
Part of the game.
But shit will rain down, though.
NCAA will be on your ass, but don't worry.
I'll call the Bruins.
I'll take care of this.
No one will keep
Phil Graham's son off the ice.
So, that's it, huh?
Excuse me?
As long as I have "Graham" on my back,
I can just beat people up
with no consequences
for the rest of my life?
Like you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
You know, I don't remember you
complaining about being a Graham
when you landed the best coaches,
when you got on the best teams
with the best equipment.
With the best bruises.
Right? Easy to write it off when your kid
plays such a violent sport.
I did what I had to.
That's fucking bullshit. And you know it.
I don't want to hear what a terrible dad
I was for making you tough.
For wanting you to have the best.
Oh, fuck you!
You don't want the best for me.
- It was never about me.
- Of course it was!
You're about to play for the Bruins.
I made that happen.
You can hate the name
on the back of your jersey all you want,
but it doesn't make you better than me.
It just makes you ungrateful.
I will never be like you.
You already are.
Stay the fuck away from me.
Stop calling. Stop coming to my games.
We're fucking done.
[slow, somber music playing]
What the hell, Garrett?
I really can't do this right now.
Can you just please get in the car?
- No. What was that?
- Are you serious?
You're mad at me?
You lied to me, Hannah.
I didn't lie to you.
You did. You looked me in the eye
and told me you were okay.
You promised me you were okay.
You just had to make it through one game.
- Oh, my God.
- One hour. That's it.
I had to go back out there
and play against that piece of shit.
- Do you not trust me, or what?
- Garrett, you lost your shit on him!
- You didn't hear what he said.
- I know what he fucking said.
What? Did he call me a whore?
A liar? That I wanted it?
Who cares?
I heard it every day in high school.
I wasn't just gonna stand
there and listen...
- I was fucking defending you!
- Well, I didn't ask you to do that.
I didn't want you to.
I didn't want anyone to.
People in Ransom
didn't just turn on me, Garrett.
They turned on my family.
My parents lost friends.
My dad got fired.
You want to know why I didn't tell you?
It's because every time I tell someone
the truth, it fucks everything up.
It ruins people's lives.
And it happened again.
No, my life isn't--
No, tell me you didn't
just put your season at risk.
Your future with the Bruins.
How do you think that makes me feel?
You blow this all up for me.
What do you want me to say?
You want me to apologize?
Say I'm sorry? I'm not.
I could face that asshole a hundred times,
and one hundred fucking times,
I'd beat the shit out of him again.
Yeah, well that scares me, Garrett.
It scares me that you would risk
everything for me
when I'm telling you it's not what I want.
I worked so fucking hard
to put it all behind me.
I scare you?
What? No, what? Of course not.
- That's what you said.
- Garrett, you're not listening to me.
Fuck.
[breathing heavily]
My dad was right.
Your what?
This is who I am, Hannah.
This is just how I'm programmed.
No, you're not. You're not Phil.
I am. I fucking am.
Do you think I like being like this?
[sighs] You know, maybe
not right now, but someday...
you're gonna look at me the same way
Cindy looked at me.
And that would kill me, Hannah.
Garrett.
- Garrett!
- No, no.
I'm not good for you.
You shouldn't be...
This is over.
This needs to be over.
[score intensifying]
[woman] Just write, Hannah.
[breathing heavily]
I just want you to write down
what happened...
in your own words.
Okay?
[Hannah breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[panting]
[phone line ringing]
- [all laughing]
- [cell phone ringing]
Han, honey, I'll tell you what.
I am missing my euchre partner
right about now.
Hanny, save me. I bet the house.
Dad says hi.
What's up?
Mom.
Han?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, my-my-my bike.
My-My bike is wrong.
Okay. We can fix the bike.
No, I don't think we can, Mom.
Is she okay?
[Carrie] Okay. Tell me.
Why can't we fix your bike?
Because...
Because, um...
Because I lost my scholarship.
I'm gonna need you
to connect some dots, honey.
No, I wasn't gonna tell you, because
I wanted to figure it out on my own.
Um, so I was--
I was gonna win the pop showcase
and get another scholarship.
But Garrett and I broke up,
because he played St. A's,
and he got into a fight,
and it's all my fault.
And now I have to walk home.
Okay. Okay. Breathe.
[crying]
Breathe.
So...
a lot to unpack there.
Let's start with the small stuff
and work our way up.
Okay?
First off, let us figure out the money.
We always do.
Don't worry about the grant.
We will find a way for you
to be at Briar next semester.
How can I not worry about it
when it's my fault?
[sobbing over phone]
I'm the reason that you can't afford it
in the first place.
Like, I'm the reason
for the therapy bills and the lawyer.
I ruined your lives, and I-I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm so sorry.
[sobbing] I'm sorry.
What did you do wrong?
What?
Well, if you're feeling guilty,
then it must mean
that you did something wrong.
So, what is it, exactly?
Uh...
I should have...
You went to a party, sweet pea.
You were a high school kid
who had a drink, that's all.
You didn't do anything wrong, Hannah.
That night and everything that happened
after that is not on you.
There's nothing that you could've
or should've done.
And as far as ruining our lives...
I am fine, and so is your dad...
despite being terrible at euchre.
[laughs]
Yeah, he really-- He really is so bad.
He's the worst.
[Hannah laughing]
But I love him.
And we love you.
So, will you let us do our jobs
and take care of you?
Are you nodding?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm nodding.
[laughs]
Good.
[rock music playing indistinctly]
[Carter] So, how's your ice?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, it's good.
- Right.
- Good ice.
Okay, did you change your mind?
It feels like you changed your mind.
- No, no, no. I'm super into this.
- It's... that's...
- Okay.
- Promise.
Right.
You're kind of a shit liar.
[both laugh]
Look, the benefit of being strangers
is you don't owe me anything, right?
You know...
It's really not you.
I-- You are very charming
and have the kind of body that suggests
you work out on federal holidays.
Well, I take Memorial Day off.
Only human.
Okay.
It's just...
It has recently come to my attention
that I'm a serial monogamist,
um, which I don't want to be.
You know, I love love,
but I also love sex.
And-And I don't want to not have one
just because I'm waiting for the other.
Sure.
Which is why
I became involved with someone.
- You have a boyfriend?
- Oh! Oh, my God, no, no. Can you imagine?
But we are at the very least something.
Like, some weird baffling thing.
More weird or baffling
than this conversation?
Okay, well, I am trying to explain
myself to you, Carter St. James.
Right. Sorry, sorry. Continue.
I want to have hot, meaningless sex.
- I do.
- Mm.
But the last time I tried,
I just ended up hurting someone
that I really care about.
So...
I just, like, I want to do it
the right way this time.
Yeah, I get that.
You do?
God, now I'm gonna have to go back
and tell the living theater legend
that I'm not fun,
and I can't be slutty.
Okay.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna kiss you.
You're gonna kiss me back.
- Pull my hair. Just really sell it.
- Mm.
And then you can go back
to your clearly very invested friend.
And you can brag
about how hot and meaningless it was.
Okay?
One kiss, and I'm bragging?
Oh, it's gonna be
a really good fucking kiss.
Bullshit.
Only one way to find out.
["we never dated" by sombr playing]
♪How come we never even dated ♪
♪But I still find myself
thinking of you daily?♪
♪Why do you always leave me aching ♪
♪When you were never mine
for the taking?♪
♪How come we never even dated ♪
♪But I still find myself
thinking of you daily?♪
♪Why do you always leave me aching ♪
♪When you were never mine
for the taking?♪
♪I can't make you love me ♪
♪No, I can't make you love me, babe ♪
♪No, I can't make you love me ♪
- Go the fuck off.
- [giggling]
Making out with a hot stranger at the bar?
Who is she?
I am she. She is me.
I'm actually so proud I could cry.
You have to admit you had fun.
[both laugh]
[dog barking]
[door opens]
[Garrett sighs]
So?
I'm out four games.
[sighs]
Yo, what's going on with you, bro?
Where'd that come from?
I don't want to talk about it.
You never do.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I just thought that,
you know, maybe...
You know, for a second there, I...
thought we were
on the same team again.
["Massachusetts" by Jensen McRae playing]
[door opens, closes]
[indistinct chatter]
♪When someone tells me
they're from Massachusetts ♪
♪Now I always ask, "What part?"♪
♪I wonder if you kept
the pilgrim ashtray ♪
♪If it's still propped up
on your bar cart ♪
[door opens]
♪Could make a grand
off of the chain you bought me ♪
♪But goddamn, it's not for sale ♪
♪When someone asks me
who's my favorite Batman ♪
♪I'll think of you and say
"Christian Bale"♪
♪As long as I live ♪
♪I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The look on your face ♪
♪When you turned 26♪
♪And your dad got too stoned ♪
♪Yeah, that one's gonna stick ♪
♪You broke me to pieces
but I root for you ♪
♪Even though everything
went up in flames ♪
♪I'll never forget
how I bloomed for your gaze ♪
♪Or your wall of guitars
or your video games ♪
♪Or your video games ♪
♪Pick up your phrases ♪
♪Now I say, "It's aces"♪
♪But it always sounds so fake ♪
♪I wonder if your tongue is turning over ♪
♪Anything I used to say ♪
♪It's getting darker, so I turn you down ♪
♪But I can't turn you off ♪
♪Oh, oh ♪
♪As long as I live
I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The look on your face
when you turned 26♪
♪And your dad got too stoned ♪
♪Yeah, that one's gonna stick ♪
♪You broke me to pieces
but I root for you ♪
♪Even though everything went up in flames ♪
♪I'll never forget
how I bloomed for your gaze ♪
♪Or your wall of guitars
or your video games ♪
♪Or your video games ♪
♪At least I'm treading water
and not about to drown ♪
♪I'm not trying to find you, babe ♪
♪You're just around ♪
♪Everything reminds me of you ♪
♪Even now, even now, even now ♪
♪As long as I live ♪
♪I'll remember the names ♪
♪Of your favorite beers
and your video games ♪
♪The fire in my gut
that I've chased ever since ♪
♪You set the bar ♪
♪You're gonna stick ♪
["Fade into You"
by Mazzy Star playing]
- ♪I want to hold the hand ♪
- [alarm beeping]
♪Inside you ♪
♪I want to take the breath that's true ♪
♪I look to you and I see nothing ♪
♪I look to you to see the truth ♪
♪Some kind of night into your darkness ♪
♪Fade into you ♪
♪Strange you never knew ♪
♪I think it's strange you never knew ♪
♪Fade into you ♪
- [song stops]
- [bell dings]
[sighs]
Here you go.
Hi, welcome to Malone's. I'm Hannah.
What can I get started for you guys today?
Hannah Wells?
Yeah. Yeah, that's me.
Have we met?
Actually, could we maybe
sit in another section?
Uh, we're pretty slammed at the moment,
but I promise I'll take good care of you.
Maybe even throw in
a slice of pie on the house.
I-I-I have a girlfriend, so...
You know, actually, we all do.
Oh, okay. Um...
Look, I was just trying to get your order,
if you need a minute.
Yeah, give us a minute. Thanks.
[door chimes jingle]
Sean.
Oh, shit. Uh, hi.
She's not working today, is she?
I mean, I know she has
Movement for Actors on Tuesday.
She's-- She's not working today.
Good. I just really miss
Della's fries, you know?
Yeah, I-I do.
I miss Tucker's salmon.
- Uh, Garrett and I...
- Broke up.
Yeah, I heard.
It's all over Fifth Line.
Plus the...
The what?
Uh, I'm not sure it's real.
It's not real.
Just a thing a guy said to me in class.
- I'm sure Garrett wouldn't...
- Sean.
Hannah.
What are you talking about?
[laughs nervously]
[Sean] Uh...
- Is Garrett in there?
- Uh, yeah.
But I don't think you should go in there--
Hannah!
Hannah, wait!
[chatter in locker room]
Oh, my God!
[upbeat music playing]
Well, well, Wellsy.
Have you made a wrong turn, or...?
Um...
Have you seen Garrett?
No, not since this morning.
Uh, Simms says that he's, um...
- Fuck, in here.
- Wellsy?
Okay, you have officially
stepped over the line.
Well, this is gonna be good.
You're so far over the line,
I can't even see this stupid line.
A campus-wide hands-off law?
You broke up with me.
And why are you in a suit?
- Hannah...
- No, sorry.
You cannot go around campus
telling guys you'll beat them up
for speaking to me.
Are you insane?
With that masochist--
Sorry, misogynist...
Sorry, I can't even think straight.
There are too many penises in this room.
- It is a men's locker room.
- [Hannah] Okay.
Garrett, I really can't have my customers
be afraid of speaking to me.
I work for tips.
I never said any of that.
For fuck's sake, someone obviously
knows what's going on here.
Stuebs said Garrett was gonna
beat anyone up if they hit on Hannah.
I didn't say that, Dean said it.
[Tucker] You gotta be fucking kidding.
I said he'd lose his shit, numb nuts.
Losing your shit is different
than beating somebody up.
He kinda did, though, right?
Just fix it, okay?
Sure, yeah.
Sorry, Wellsy.
Look, I would never tell anyone
to stay away from you.
You should be with
whoever you want to be with.
Yeah, thank you.
[soft, melancholic music playing]
Bye.
[sighs]
[door closes]
It's our understanding that Coach Jensen
has already suspended you for four games
following last week's altercation?
Yes, ma'am.
We support that,
and we appreciate you
taking responsibility for your actions.
However, in light
of your past indiscretions,
we simply can't let this slide.
What past indis...?
[players cheer]
Like tha--?
Are you familiar with the NCAA bylaw
that requires student athletes to maintain
their amateur player status?
[heart pounding]
- Excuse me, that wasn't a--
- Just answer the question.
Yes, I'm aware.
According to this video posted on your own
social media account,
it appears you participated
in a professional Bruins practice.
That video was taken after a practice.
Perhaps, but that is not at all clear
in what we see here.
How would it look if we were to bend
the rules for you, Mr. Graham?
The video was posted
prior to the start of your season,
which means Briar University
rostered an ineligible player.
It is therefore our ruling that Briar
forfeits all games played thus far.
- What? You-You-You can't do that.
- Garrett.
- Which takes your current standing
from 13 wins, 3 losses, and 1 tie,
to 0 wins, 17 losses, and 0 ties.
They're gonna fucking hate me.
They're gonna be upset. Yeah.
Why'd you do it, Garrett?
The Bruins invited me.
That's not what this is about.
Not really.
Why did you attack him like that?
[sighs]
It's not my story to tell, Coach.
Okay.
What kind of hockey player
do you want to be?
The hothead who hit Delaney?
I have no interest in coaching that guy.
I want to coach players
who love the game the way I do.
Who go out on the ice because every
fiber of their being wants to be there.
You gotta love it, Garrett.
Do you love it?
[Jensen sighs]
Then do me a favor.
Figure that out.
[Tucker] Dead last?
Oh, we can't be dead last.
- Dead last.
- That's it.
That's my senior year down the drain.
Not necessarily.
You explain to me how we make
the Frozen Four from last place.
- Yeah, you're right. No Garrett.
- No Birdie.
Fucking concussion.
- Joe Rogers.
- He's not ready.
- But if he--
- Nope.
Yeah, he's not ready.
How many games do we have to win?
- [Dean] Every fucking game.
- Or tie.
- [Dean] We can't win every fucking game.
- With three-fifths of a starting line?
- Garrett will be back.
- Garrett's the reason we're in this.
All right? This is on us.
We have to fix it.
The only way to get a shot
at the Frozen Four
is if we are first in the conference,
and to do that, we need new blood.
Tuck, you and I can hold it down
without a strong center,
but we need a solid D-line.
Dean, you can't do it alone.
We need a new Birdie.
There was this kid
at open tryouts last year.
Remember? Tore up the ice.
Crazy fast defenseman.
Yeah, um... Hunter something, right?
Yeah. Davenport. Hunter Davenport.
Fuck no.
- What?
- No.
Fuck that guy.
Why, because he out-skated you?
- He didn't out-skate me.
- No, he kind of did, bro.
Jensen offered him a spot on the team,
and he turned it down.
Maybe he had a good reason.
Yeah, the reason is
that he's a selfish dick
with a piss-poor attitude,
- and I'm not fucking playing with him.
- [Tucker] But...
Just drop it.
I'm serious.
I'll talk to Rogers.
I'll get him ready.
[quiet, melancholic music playing]
[typing]
[sighs]
- [door closes]
- [Hannah] It's over.
Work, study, finals,
the semester, all of it.
I'm free.
Okay, is that...
Good? Bad?
Sorry, your line read is so confusing.
It...
I-I don't know.
Ah.
You can't distract yourself anymore.
I can't distract myself anymore.
Yeah, you gotta be sad, babe.
That's part of it.
No. Garrett's not sad.
He's totally fine not invoking
a campus-wide hands-off policy.
Okay, well, gentle reminder,
we didn't want him to have done that.
- It's like wildly problematic.
- I know. I know.
But, yeah, if he had,
it would mean he misses me,
and he's miserable, too.
And I really want him
to be miserable, too.
- Is that shitty?
- No, it's like Breakup 101.
How'd you get over Sean so fast?
You were sad for, like, a day,
and then, you were fine.
Teach me your ways.
I...
started having fun.
- Wait, you had a fling?
- No.
You had a fling, and you didn't tell me?
No, okay?
A fling is like a mini relationship.
It's like a gateway drug.
I... am through with all that.
- [both chuckle]
- It's too much pressure.
I am just being single and hooking up.
Both of the things, none of the stress,
and that's what you should be doing.
You've been so focused on school and work
and the showcase and Garrett.
Like, just lower the stakes.
Have fun?
Have fun.
Do stuff just 'cause you want to.
Well, can sleep be fun?
Sleep is self-care. We'll allow it.
Yeah, if I go to bed now,
I could sleep for a full eight hours.
Dream big, Hannah.
You could sleep for nine hours.
[Hannah] Ugh, that sounds glorious.
[laughs]
- [door opens and closes]
- [cell phone vibrates]
- Oh, shit. Al.
- [grunting] Hey.
Okay.
[Allie] Oh! Oh, my God.
[both laugh]
- Hi.
[laughs]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I, um...
I'm fine.
Just... need you to sit.
I came to say...
Okay, what's-- what's going on?
You may have noticed
that it's been a second
since we slept together.
I have noticed, and let me be
the first to say I'm not crazy about it.
Yeah, it's because I had a revelation.
Uh...
We need to sleep with other people.
We've always said that
we can sleep with other people.
Right, of course. You're Six Flags.
But when's the last time
someone other than me
actually got on this particular
roller coaster?
- Shit.
- Exactly, yeah.
So, um...
Like, this thing between us...
- It's fun.
- Agreed.
But it can't be a relationship.
Sure.
Just need to lower the stakes
a little on us.
Sleep with other people, so we can
sleep with each other, as well.
- I'm not tracking the logic here.
- Just have sex with someone.
Are you in or are you out, Di Laurentis?
A sexy homework assignment.
I'm in, Allie Cat.
I am so in.
Good.
Okay, bye.
["Too Busy Missing You"
by Asha Banks playing]
- So, we're not...?
- Just text me when it's done.
♪To fall in love with someone else
it's such a bitter taste ♪
♪Too cold to stand I need a hand
in crawling out your grave ♪
♪So I can get up and start living ♪
♪Too busy missing you ♪
♪Too busy missing ♪
[playing "Baby, Now That
I've Found You" slowly]
[quiet, melancholic music playing]
[sighs]
♪Page one ♪
♪It's just the prologue ♪
♪Setting the stage
for all that's to happen ♪
♪Then on to the first chapter ♪
♪Everyone's happy ♪
♪For shadowing impending disaster ♪
♪Then girl meets boy ♪
♪It's awkward, confusing ♪
♪Can't tell if it's love or it's hate ♪
♪When hands graze ♪
♪Reaching for something ♪
♪Forgettably dull and mundane ♪
♪Now it's a love story ♪
♪Of epic proportion ♪
♪The likes of which never's been told ♪
♪Two hearts beating as one ♪
♪Ran right into the sun ♪
♪Oh, what would I give to go back ♪
♪Back to page one ♪
[car engine starts]
Hey, which light came on first?
[Jules] The squiggly one? I don't know.
The s--
What? Hey, could you show me?
I would, but I can't get oil
on my new favorite outfit.
No.
No way. No, absolutely not.
They sent you so much cool shit.
- I told you to stop opening my mail.
- That box has been in the truck for days.
Days. It's practically
begging to be opened.
And it's a good thing I did.
Because look what I found.
Who says print media's dead?
- Toss it.
- Absolutely not.
Okay, I finally found them.
Ian's little's best friend's girlfriend
is in American Studies with him.
And?
And I really don't think
it's a good idea, bro.
What's not a good idea?
- Don't worry about it.
- Hunter Davenport.
Oh. To take Birdie's spot?
- See what you did?
- [Jules] That'll be messy.
- I love it.
- Wait, why messy?
Well, doesn't he hate Dean?
Okay, I'll bite.
What do you know?
Well, they're both bougie bitches
who vacation in the Hamptons,
so it could be any number of things.
All I know for sure is Hunter
went to high school with Dean's sister.
Fuck. Summer?
[Jules] The one and only.
- That's not good, man.
- Look, okay, I don't care.
If we're gonna have a shot at fixing
Garrett's mess, we need him.
- You tracked him down, yeah?
- Yeah.
Good.
Let's reach out.
[guitar being played]
♪Spare myself of this ache ♪
♪How could anyone dare
to love again?♪
♪I'm raising my walls ♪
♪So I never fall ♪
♪Into another love story ♪
[laughs] Hi.
What is that? It's beautiful.
Uh, it's just a song I wrote
in high school.
- Okay, Taylor Swift.
- [Hannah chuckles]
Those lyrics are insane.
Uh, yeah, well, they used to be easier.
I felt things.
I wrote them.
Well, some of the best songs ever
were written after a breakup.
Maybe this is what you need
to bust through your writer's block.
Yeah, I...
I-I think it's about more
than that, actually.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[clears throat]
[Hannah sighs]
Um...
Um, you know when you meet someone,
and you don't quite
get their name at first,
then you start seeing them all the time,
and you've got inside jokes,
and it just becomes really awkward
to ask what their name is?
- My literal nightmare, yes. Go on.
- Um...
Uh...
What if it's your best friend?
And she doesn't know
this huge fundamental thing about you?
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you something.
But I really don't want you
to look at me differently.
Or treat me differently.
Or hate me for not telling you sooner.
Hey, I would never.
You say that, but a lot of people did.
[sighs]
Remember my friend from high school?
The one who was roofied,
and all the stuff that happened after?
You're the friend.
Oh, Hannah, I always knew.
I just...
I thought you'd tell me
when you were ready.
[gasps]
[laughs]
You're my favorite person ever.
Right back at you, babe.
So, what does this have to do
with writer's block?
I... I just haven't been able
to write lyrics since.
Oh.
I didn't want to be the girl
who was raped.
I want to be this girl.
The girl who wrote this song.
The Hannah that I love is that girl.
And this girl.
And all the girls in between.
Because you're not just one thing, babe.
You're everything.
Never forget that.
Okay, you are everything.
[cries]
And the words will come when they come.
[laughs, sniffles]
And maybe I might have the beginnings
of an inkling of an idea for a new song.
But I need someone's help for it.
Thank you, again, for all the help.
Yeah, of course.
- Can't wait to hear the finished product.
- Yeah, if it ever turns into anything.
Well, hey, if it does,
I've got some friends
who work at the radio station.
I could call in a favor.
Yeah, I-I-I think this one's just for me.
These hockey sounds
will be so cool in the mix.
All right, totally, we got some good ones.
[somber music playing]
[exhales]
He's been sneaking in after practice.
Skates these pensive
little circles around the ice.
It's hard to watch.
Almost as bad
as his divorced Tom Brady stories.
- Yeah, those were bad.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I make Allie show me on her phone,
so he doesn't see.
My brother makes me do the same thing.
They aren't speaking?
No. They got in this big fight.
Apparently.
Anyway, send me the song
once it maybe turns into something.
Yeah.
Hey.
Uh, why are you...
Uh, Jules was helping me with a song.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You kind of helped me come up
with the idea, so...
thanks, I guess.
[laughs]
Are you dropping a diss track or...?
[laughing] No.
No, uh, you just...
reminded me of who I used to be.
Right.
Well...
good luck at the showcase.
Actually, I dropped out.
Oh.
That's too bad.
Uh, you would have been really great.
- Well, I should--
- Hey, can I--
Sorry, what?
- No, it's fine.
- Garrett, I know we're...
You know.
But it's me.
I'm thinking about quitting.
Hockey?
Yeah.
Oh.
I don't know if I'm in it
for the right reasons.
I don't know if I'm playing because
I want to prove that I'm not like my dad
or I want to prove
that I am like my dad or...
[inhales deeply and sighs]
...because I'm not good at anything else.
But...
Jensen said I should be skating
because I love it, and...
I don't know.
You once told me
that you'd be relieved
if you couldn't play anymore.
And now, you can't.
And that means you could be anywhere,
doing anything.
But you're not.
You're here.
On the ice.
Skating.
And for what it's worth,
you do have a good reason to play.
It's not your dad.
It's the guy on your right.
Who's always had your back.
Even when you're being an asshole.
[sniffles]
[crowd cheering]
[Garrett] Come! Come here!
- [Logan] Right here!
- [puck clangs off goalpost]
- [buzzer]
- [Garrett] Yes, yes!
[sniffles]
[crowd shouting]
[Jules] Graham and Logan
have been having a blast out there.
We love that for them.
And more importantly, we love it for me.
[laughs]
[indistinct shouting and cheers]
[Jules] Two minutes left, it's looking--
...Graham and Delaney meet center ice,
ready to start the--
[skate blades on ice]
[yells]
[Logan] Hey, get off!
- [whistle blows]
- Get off of him!
[Logan] Hey! Graham!
- Hey! Hey!
- [Garret grunts]
- Bring him to me! Come here!
- Hey! Hey!
Garrett, look at me!
- [panting]
- Hey, I got you.
I got you.
Okay?
[tap water running]
Oh, you know Tucker hates
when you do that in the kitchen.
[scoffs] He'll live.
What do you want, Garrett?
The, uh...
St. A's game.
You pulled me off Delaney.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I blacked out.
If you hadn't stopped me...
Listen, Delaney's a piece of shit.
But I don't want to be that guy.
I don't want to be the guy
who loses himself in a violent rage.
I don't want to be...
[sighs]
I don't want to be my dad.
Look, um...
I'm gonna say some things.
I haven't said
any of this out loud before.
Except, well, except to Hannah.
But I think I need to.
Okay.
Yeah.
[Beau]
What's up with the cryptic text, dude?
I'm having a crisis.
Can you keep a secret on your life?
Where's the body?
- This is serious.
- [laughs] Okay.
Right.
Sorry.
I've been hooking up with Allie.
- I know.
- You know?
I was in the car with you for eight hours,
and I have eyes.
Oh. Fuck, you're not as dumb as you look.
I appreciate that.
So, what's your crisis?
I've lost my game.
What?
I tried hitting on, like,
three different girls.
Gorgeous girls.
All of them totally into me.
But I just...
I don't care.
Heart's not in it.
- Dick's not in it.
- Whoa.
I know.
Dude, you like Allie.
Like, "like" like her.
- Just tell her how you feel.
- No.
No, that's...
[laughs] No.
She wants Six Flags.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
She doesn't want anything heavy or real.
Yesterday, she told me
that we had to sleep with other people.
And, uh, evidently I cannot.
"We"? Like, she's supposed to hook up
with other people, too.
- Yeah.
- And...
you're cool with that?
Totally, I mean...
- We aren't...
- No, you aren't.
We aren't at all, like...
But...
Yeah.
You're fucking awesome, D.
I know that. She knows that.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
be hooking up with you.
So, stop being chicken shit
and tell her how you feel.
And you gotta do it fast before she goes
and hooks up with some other guy.
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Love you, bye.
- Love you.
[cell phone vibrating]
[panting and fast footsteps]
["I Want You" by Debbii Dawson playing]
Carter St. James.
♪Sick ♪
♪Oh, dear ♪
♪You're ringing in my ear...♪
[panting]
You checking me out?
No.
You sure?
[upbeat music playing]
[Jensen]
Okay, we got Braun on center, Rogers on D.
Logan, Dean, you look
after those two out there, okay?
We gotta get the puck
to the net tonight.
- Okay?
- [door opens]
That goes for all of you.
I want shots all fucking game.
Do not let up.
You hear me?
Sorry, Coach. Um, can I...
Go ahead, captain.
Uh, you know I'm not a big speech guy.
Uh, but I figured since I can't, uh...
I thought that being captain
meant I had to do it all.
So...
I was selfish
and angry, and I shut you all out.
I acted like I was bigger than the team.
Yeah, you were a bit of an asshole.
[laughs]
I was.
But even when I abandoned you,
even when I lost my shit
when you didn't deserve it,
when I forgot about the game and the team
and how much fucking fun we have
when we're out there together,
you were there.
You guys backed me up.
That's why I love this sport.
Is that it's about showing up
and leaving it all out on the ice.
Not for yourself,
but for the guy on your right.
For your brothers.
I know I let you guys down.
I haven't been the captain
that you deserve, but...
[players whispering]
But until then...
You guys already have a captain
skating with you out there.
That okay, Coach?
I'm good with it.
Gentlemen?
[players cheering]
- Yeah, Logan!
- [sticks knocking]
[Dean] Let's go!
[players whoop]
[Tucker] Let's go, Logan.
[player] Captain Logan!
- [player 1] Yes, sir.
- [player 2] Yeah!
Yeah, let's go, all right!
[cheering continues indistinctly]
- Let's fucking go!
- Yes sir!
Let's go!
Hit it!
[quiet, hopeful music playing]
[no audio]
[crowd cheering]
- [grunting]
- Way to lay the body, D.D.!
[Jules] Tough hit by Di Laurentis.
Wherever he is,
I bet Garrett Graham's proud.
[hopeful music playing]
[fan shouts]
- [buzzer]
- Let's go!
Ha-ha! Yeah! Tucker!
[cheers and applause]
Daveed!
Hi.
I wrote something, and I don't know why,
I feel like it's really good.
And anyway,
I don't even care about winning.
I just feel like I need to share this
and let people into my truth to heal,
like you said.
And I know what time it is,
and I know it's too late,
and I know I said I was dropping out,
but can I maybe drop back in?
Now, girl,
you know they didn't have the budget
to reprint all these programs.
So, you're saying...
I'm saying you better start warming up.
You are on after Bethany.
Thank you!
[both laugh]
Yes! Okay!
["MESSY." by REDD. playing]
We can come back from a tie,
but we can't come back from a loss.
- Let's be smart.
- They’re not getting that puck back.
- Let's fucking go.
- All right, get it done! Change! Change!
♪Talking what I′m doing next week ♪
Stall, stall.
♪You really don′t wanna test me...♪
[Dean] Fuck yeah!
Nice.
- Hey, shouldn't you be back on D?
- They're not getting the puck back, baby.
Fucking right. Let's go!
Don't play it safe, get back to him.
Hey, Tuck! A tie's not a win!
Aye-aye, cap!
Come on, Logan. Go to work.
Take it!
- Yes!
- Yeah!
- [crowd cheering]
- Yes!
Whoo! Go, John!
Attaboy, Logan! Attaboy!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go!
Whoo!
♪Who cares what you're doing next week ♪
♪You're saying please don't test me ♪
♪Just pass the drinks, I feel sexy ♪
♪Ooh, get messy ♪
♪Baby, get messy ♪
♪Get messy ♪
[vibrates]
Oh, my God. She's doing it.
Okay, this has been fun, but I gotta go.
You don't want my number?
[rock music plays]
No. Actually, I don't.
I could stay, and we could keep up
this cute little banter thing we're doing,
but, I mean, like you said,
the benefit of being complete strangers
is we don't owe each other
anything, right?
I mean, that works for me.
Okay.
I have a best friend to go support.
- [laughter]
- [cell phone ringing]
Hey, we won. You should come to Malone's.
I want to talk to you.
No time. Hannah's doing the showcase.
You have to get Garrett there.
- Why?
- Because they're right for each other,
and Hannah deserves a romantic gesture.
So you want me to...
Yes, now.
[players chatting indistinctly]
[Dean] G.
We gotta go now.
What's up?
Wellsy's doing the showcase.
You gotta be there.
How do you know that?
I overheard it in the stands.
Wait, Hannah's doing the showcase?
Well, we're going. When does it start?
- Like, now.
- [Tucker] Then we gotta hustle.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Come on, come on.
What's going on?
What if she doesn't want me there?
Fuck are you talking about?
Of course, she wants you there.
- No, she's moving on. I have to let her.
- Jesus Christ.
Look, you guys are perfect for each other.
So, whatever you did to fuck it up,
just undo it.
It's not that easy.
She deserves better than me.
No, don't fucking do that.
You are not your dad, okay?
So, are you gonna fight for her?
Come on.
[emcee] Please welcome to the stage,
Hannah Wells.
[applause]
[vocalizing melody]
[melody electronically looping]
[hockey sounds]
♪Ooh ♪
♪Ooh, ooh ♪
♪I heard the talk ♪
♪I wish I never listened ♪
♪It's so hard letting go of it ♪
♪The sharpest knives ♪
♪Are whispered harsh opinions ♪
♪And what did I have to show for it ♪
♪Like a glass hits the floor ♪
♪My world was shattered and broken ♪
♪Couple years
I was coping and holding in ♪
♪I had no words ♪
♪Couldn't make a sound ♪
♪I took my time ♪
♪But I'm here right now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪And all at once it all makes sense ♪
♪I had to break, I had to bend ♪
♪ I had to lose myself to finally see ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
[prerecorded vocalizations]
♪Ohh ♪
♪I bared my truth ♪
♪Not knowing what would follow ♪
♪And I would do it all again ♪
♪Time heals all wounds ♪
♪But leaves a pretty scar, though ♪
♪Stronger than I've ever been ♪
♪'Cause I found my words ♪
♪So I'll sing 'em loud ♪
♪Guess all the hurt ♪
♪Got me here now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪And all at once it all makes sense ♪
♪I had to trust to feel again ♪
♪I had to let you in to finally see ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
♪It all makes sense
It all-- It all makes ♪
♪It all makes sense ♪
♪'Cause I found my words ♪
♪So I'll sing 'em loud ♪
[buzzer sound]
♪I had to let you in, to let you in ♪
♪To let you see ♪
♪Guess all the hurt ♪
♪Got me here now ♪
♪I spent so long inside my head ♪
♪The pain, the tears, secrets I kept ♪
♪In fear one day they'd be the end of me ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of what I went through ♪
♪Partly because of you ♪
♪I am the girl that I am ♪
♪Because of the girl I used ♪
♪To be ♪
- [cheers and applause]
- Yes!
Yes!
[calming music playing]
You came.
I couldn't miss your big moment,
could I?
You are, um...
fucking incredible.
The way you just opened up
in front of all those people.
I want to be more like you, Wellsy.
Like the girl from the green room.
The girl up on that stage.
[sighs] Fuck.
Everything you are.
Garrett--
Just hear me out.
Please.
You make me want to be better.
To do better, and...
I'm going to.
Just...
give me another chance.
I meant what I said before.
You should be with whoever you want to be.
But...
I really want that guy to be me.
["Shapeshifting on a Saturday Night"
by Avery Cochrane playing]
You know, girls really hate it
when guys are too available.
They do?
Shit.
Yeah. You got a lot to learn here, Graham.
[both laugh]
Do you know any good tutors?
I might.
♪I wish I could save her ♪
♪But I can't behave her ♪
♪And she's twisting,
shapeshifting on a Saturday night ♪
♪Will she waste into
the kind of woman everyone likes?♪
♪She's an industry professional
at telling you lies ♪
♪Works hard for her money
and still can't get by ♪
♪She's a California keeper
if she just plays pretend ♪
♪And you'll love her 'til you leave her
'cause she's sick in the head...♪
Good game.
Now you just gotta win 16 more.
Thank you for that.
There she is!
The star, the icon.
I still think it was rigged.
[laughs] They didn't rig the pop showcase.
- Whatever, Bethany paid someone off.
- She absolutely did.
- But second place is the new first anyway.
- Right?
And I got an internship.
Paid internship.
Which deserves a drink. Who wants a drink?
I will accept the drink.
Mm. Four piña coladas, please.
[Allie] Hey, Walker.
Hey, can I get three shots of tequila, please?
Thanks.
- Hey.
You did a nice thing.
- What?
- Getting them back together.
No, they got themselves back together.
With help from you.
And me.
- You're welcome.
- Mm. [chuckles]
I get it now.
You love love.
That's what you said you wanted, right?
That night at the fire pit.
So, I came here to tell you that, uh...
I didn't complete the assignment.
What?
- Why?
- Because I like you.
I like us.
I know that's not what we said,
but I was hoping--
Hey, no, Dean.
- You can't.
- And yet, I am.
No, I mean, like,
you have to complete the assignment.
- Because--
- Because why?
Because I did.
Okay, somebody tell me
why we aren't drinking over here.
I swear, it didn't mean anything.
I-- Joanna set me up with this guy,
like a total stranger at a bar.
Oh, shit.
[door opens]
♪I don't mean to cause a scene ♪
♪But respectfully, I...♪
Oh, shit.
[Beau] Allie, is that who you...
♪Looking at your knee-high boots ♪
♪You looked at me and said ♪
♪"I'm gonna make a man out of you"...♪
Him?
No.
Yes.
Do you know him?
♪I think I'm gonna ♪
♪Come to my senses
realize that I'm in...♪
- [Allie] Dean.
- [Beau] Dean.
- The fuck are you doing here?
- I heard your team needs saving.
Yeah? Get the fuck out.
Hey, uh, Logan,
you said this was his idea.
You-- You said what?
Dude, you didn't.
- Hey, what the hell is going on here?
- You weren't there? I had to make a call.
I'm not skating with this prick!
Aw. What, are you scared
I’m gonna dust your ass again?
- You wanna try? Yeah?
- Yeah, I do.
- I'd like to see you fucking try.
- Get the fuck out of my face.
- [Garrett] Hey! Hey, Dean! Hey!
- [Tucker] Whoa, whoa!
[Garrett] Come on!
[Tucker] Hey! Whoa, whoa!
- Come here!
- Fuck you! Get the fuck back!
- Fuck you!
- Drama, drama, drama.
I knew this would get messy.
What is happening? Who is that guy?
Great question. Beau, who is that guy?
That is Hunter Davenport.
[all shouting]
And that's our new starting line.
[“Bad Thing Rush” by Devon Again playing]
♪I got a feeling
they want me in the background ♪
♪I know they need me in the front ♪
♪It doesn't matter
'cuz I know what will happen ♪
♪They won't believe it when it comes ♪
♪Uh-huh, all I ever needed
was to give it all I got now ♪
♪Maybe I'm just in it for the rush ♪
♪Taking my percentage
better give me what I want now ♪
♪Thank you very much ♪
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪Gimme
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪I got a feeling
I'm 'bout to do a bad thing ♪
♪I know they know that I'm the one ♪
♪Back me up into a corner
I'll come atcha ♪
♪I like to watch 'em when they run ♪
♪All I never needed
was to give it all I got now ♪
♪Maybe I'm just in it for the rush ♪
♪Taking my percentage
better give me what I want now ♪
♪Thank you very much ♪
♪I wanna
bad thing rush ♪
♪Gimme